Chapter 969: Mysterious Fantasy’s Coach

The age problem. Chen Guo could understand this problem the easiest because she also had this problem. When she was just playing around for fun, age wouldn’t really affect anything. But once she started delving deep into the game, this problem instantly stood out.

"If you’ve discovered so many problems, shouldn’t you talk to them about it?" Chen Guo said.

"Of course I will. Aren’t I currently organizing everything right now?" Ye Xiu said.

Chen Guo looked. It turned out that Ye Xiu was taking clips from today’s match. Then, he would talk about these problems with everyone. Now, she could finally feel at ease.

"Is there anything I can do to help?" Chen Guo asked.

Ye Xiu felt his pockets. He nodded his head and looked at Chen Guo eagerly: "Yeah, help me buy a pack of cigarettes."

Black lines went down Chen Guo’s head. She turned around and left. She originally wanted to directly go back to her room, but before she closed the door, she saw Ye Xiu working in front of the computer. Her heart softened. In the end, she couldn’t steel her heart and ran to buy Ye Xiu a pack of cigarettes. When she returned, she gently placed into beside his hands and then quietly left.

When she returned to the room, Tang Rou still hadn’t gone to bed. She was also in front of her computer. Chen Guo walked closer to take a look. Tang Rou was browsing through Battle Mage related material such as videos.　　

Chen Guo smiled. Ye Xiu was right. Their Team Happy members didn’t need consolation or encouragement. Everyone was actively working to face their problems.

"Don’t sleep too late. Go to bed early." Chen Guo was originally going to chat a bit with Tang Rou, but seeing how she was focused on studying Battle Mages, she softly said a few words and didn’t bother her anymore.

"How’d you guys sleep yesterday?" Ye Xiu smiled as he asked everyone.

Everyone looked at each other. For a moment, no one said anything.

"We’ve been strolling through the Challenger League with ease the entire time. We only considered Excellent Era as our final opponents and overlooked our other opponents. In the last match, we’ve paid the price for that because with this loss. Our current situation in Group B is grim. We must do our best and win points in our following two matches. We can’t be even the slightest bit careless." Ye Xiu said.

"Understood." Everyone nodded their heads. The atmosphere was unexpectedly solemn. It was truly a bit different from the usual atmosphere at Happy.

"Then let’s first first review our previous match!" Ye Xiu said.

It was just like what Ye Xiu said. Winning concealed their problems. Losses exposed their problems. When they dominated their first match, Ye Xiu didn’t really review the match much, but this time, the match review took up the entire morning.

The team was a whole. Every individual’s problem was the team’s problem. As teammates, everyone needed to understand each other’s characteristics. This included weaknesses and strengths. Only by completely understanding one another could they coordinate well with each other. As a result, Ye Xiu directly took out every individual’s problem and discussed it together with the team. An individual’s efforts and the team’s help would make solving the problem half the work with twice the results.

In the morning, the team analyzed the problems that happened during yesterday’s match. In the afternoon, they underwent the usual training. The next day, Ye Xiu had already put together information on their next opponent, and they began making preparations.

In the blink of an eye, three days passed. The fourth round would begin Friday night.

Group B. Team Happy versus Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion, Team Mysterious Fantasy versus Team Trader, Team Ten Steps One Kill versus no team.

Team Ten Steps One Kill only had 3 points and had already been eliminated early. Today, they didn’t even come to the stadium to watch. As for Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion, they had one last hope. This one last hope was originally no different from disappointment, but after seeing Team Trader capsize Team Happy, Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion’s spirits were high. They were ready to put their all into this fight.

How could Team Happy give their opponents any chance? Like breaking a dead branch from a tree, they crushed Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion. After just half an hour, Team Happy ended today’s match.

But in this round, Team Happy still lost a point.　　

In this Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion, there was an Assassin called Brilliant Move . He was mediocre in every aspect, but he had extremely good mastery over Life-Risking Strike. In the match versus Team Mysterious Fantasy, he had also been the one who won them a point.

This Brilliant Move clearly wasn’t good in the group arena, so in their confrontation versus Team Happy, he appeared in the individual competition.

Ye Xiu had pointed out this person during their preparation stage. But in the individual competition, Tang Rou was still cheesed by him. Tang Rou was incredibly depressed with the result. Tang Rou liked to fight face to face. She didn’t like fighting dirty. She had trouble facing players like that. This match reflected another one of her problems.

As a result, after this match, Team Happy had 21 points. Team Cloud Viewing Pavilion was eliminated early as well.

On the other side, the match between Team Mysterious Fantasy and Team Trader was still underway. Because Team Happy lost quite a few points against Team Trader in the second round, their chances of making it out of groups went down. The outcome of this match was very important for Team Happy. After finishing up with their match, they directly headed over to watch that match. Chen Guo was a spectator, so she could pay attention to both sides. Her expression was not looking good.

The match between Team Mysterious Fantasy and Team Trader had already entered the team competition. In the individual competition and group arena, the results were unexpected: 2 to 3.

In the individual competition, Team Trader actually took 3 points from Team Mysterious Fantasy. If they beat Team Mysterious Fantasy in the team competition, they would have two upset victories under them, completely displaying their colors as a dark horse. With 8 points, they would be guaranteed to make it out of groups. In the final round with Team Happy versus Team Mysterious Fantasy, one of the teams would be eliminated.

But even if Team Mysterious Fantasy won against Team Trader in the team competition, would that make it any easier for Team Happy?

Ye Xiu glanced at the player seats. A person caught his eye. He had a little notebook in his hands, and he also looked over at Happy. When he saw Ye Xiu looking at him, he let out a smile.

"Hey! Great Gunner." Ye Xiu greeted.

"Haha, I wouldn’t dare call myself that." The other side laughed. He turned his head back and continued to watch the match.

This person wouldn’t go on stage, but in reality, he was the true core of Team Mysterious Fantasy.

Zhang Yiwei. He was a pro player, who joined the Alliance in season two. That year, he was an extremely famous Sharpshooter. However, nowadays, his glory had been masked by the younger generation. Nothing could be done about that. Zhang Yiwei’s successor was too dazzling.

Most of Zhang Yiwei’s career had been with Team Samsara. His character was Cloud Piercer, which was now the Great Gunner. It was the character currently being used by the number one player in the Alliance, Zhou Zekai. Ye Xiu called him Great Gunner, but Zhang Yiwei didn’t dare to call himself that. He wasn’t being modest. When he was still playing on Cloud Piercer, it hadn’t been called Great Gunner yet.

Having such a successor was a blessing to the team, but for the senior, it was a rather sorrowful matter. Zhou Zekai’s dominant performance with Cloud Piercer made him seem incompetent.

After Zhou Zekai succeeded Zhang Yiwei, he sadly left Team Samsara and drifted for two seasons. In the end, he announced his retirement in season six. He had a beautiful turn around though and became Team Mysterious Fantasy’s coach. It could be said that he flipped a new chapter in the history of Glory. Before him, pro teams didn’t have a coaching position. That year, the new Team Mysterious Fantasy successfully remained in the Alliance. Others immediately took after them. The next year, the new Team Bright Green also hired a coach to help the team.

Zhang Yiwei was responsible for at least half of Team Mysterious Fantasy’s achievements. As a result, Team Mysterious Fantasy’s true core member wasn’t on stage, but on the side as the coach. Even when the team was relegated last season, it looked like the owner of Team Mysterious Fantasy had confidence in Zhang Yiwei and had him stay on the team.

" It seems like Team Mysterious Fantasy’s situation is quite good?" Chen Guo asked Ye Xiu curiously. In the team competition, Team Mysterious Fantasy held a stable lead. It didn’t seem like the dark horse Team Trader wouldn’t be able to stay dark.

"As long as they aren’t careless, Team Mysterious Fantasy shouldn’t lose to Team Trader." Ye Xiu said. He glanced at Zhang Yiwei again.

"That’s good." Chen Guo smiled.

"Good? What’s good?" Ye Xiu asked.

"If Mysterious Fantasy wins, won’t that it make easier for us in the final round?" Chen Guo said.

"Look more carefully at the points please!" Ye Xiu said.

"What?" Chen Guo was startled. She started calculating the points according to the current situation.

If the outcome turned out as expected and Team Mysterious Fantasy beat Team Trader, the final score would be 7 to 3. With that, after the fourth round, Team Trader would be completely done with their four matches. They would be in first temporarily with 28 points. Team Mysterious Fantasy would be done with three out of four matches and would be second at 26 points. Team Happy would be done with three out of four matches and would be at third at 21 points. The other two teams didn’t matter.

In the final round, Team Trader would not have to play. Team Happy would be against Team Mysterious Fantasy. The other match didn’t matter. The final point total made Chen Guo pale.

Team Trader’s 28 points wouldn’t change. The point total for Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy would change though because of the final round. Team Happy was behind Team Mysterious Fantasy by 5 points and behind Team Trader by 7 points. In the final round, how many points did Team Happy need to win?

"8 points..." Ye Xiu gave the answer.

Only with 8 points would Team Happy have 29 points and make it out of groups. If they had one fewer point, Team Mysterious Fantasy would take first with 29 points. Team Happy and Team Trader would both have 28 points, but according to the tournament rules, if two teams had the same number of points, the match between the two tied teams would be looked at. Team Happy had lost to Team Trader 3 to 7, so Team Happy would be eliminated.

In this match, Team Mysterious Fantasy’s advantage became more and more obvious. They still had all five players, but three players on Team Trader had already been killed. Zhang Wenyi let out a satisfied smile. He turned his head and looked at Team Happy again.

Chapter 970: Desperate Times

The fourth round of the match had come an end.

Team Mysterious Fantasy ended up defeating Team Trader in the team competition, winning this round seven to three. The two teams left the stage. Team Mysterious Fantasy’s players seemed in high spirits, though the players of Team Trader didn’t seem too down from their defeat either. As a grassroots team made up of normal players, Team Trader had the best performance among all the grassroots teams. Despite being seen as nothing but canon fodder, they had managed to snatch 10 points in total from two strong teams. After the four matches, the were in the lead with 28 points in a group thought to be a lost cause. An average score of seven per round was already very amazing. Group A’s pro team Jade Dynasty had only managed to gain a total of 29 points after four rounds.

Team Trader had already done the best they could and the audience applauded for them. After Team Trader’s players accepted the liberal applause from the audience, they left the stadium with their heads held high.

Many people had already began to understand what the situation of Group B was like. Many people reveled in Happy’s misfortune, jeering at them. Chen Guo couldn’t spare any energy to be angry. The situation was very worrying.

"We should go, too!" Ye Xiu called out and Happy’s members rose to leave as well. Yet, they managed to bump into Team Mysterious Fantasy on the way out through the participant’s passage.

Despite how this last battle would decide their respective fates, Team Mysterious Fantasy’s players all seemed very relaxed, as if they had this in the bag already. The coach, Zhang Yiwei, looked over and saw three familiar faces from the past. However, these three were both top Gods back then and as for Zhang Yiwei? He might have been a core member of Team Samsara, but the Samsara back then wasn’t the champion team it was now. As a core member, he couldn’t compare to these top Gods.

Yet now, these big shots of the past had been tightly suppressed by him. This was a delightful feeling he had never had before. Zhang Yiwei hadn’t ever though he’d be able to have such an experience in the Challenger League and he looked to be the happiest out of all the Team Mysterious Fantasy players.

"Hey there, you guys!" This guy even greeted them personally.

Happy’s members looked at him, silent.

"It’s the last round! Keep working hard, everyone!" Zhang Yiwei’s words were directed at all of Happy’s members, but his gaze was fixed on the three old Gods.

　

"If you accidentally get eliminated by Trader, then you would be a disappointment to all this attention you’ve gained!" A member of Team Mysterious Fantasy cut in from behind Zhang Yiwei. In the Challenger League, Happy was definitely the team that gained the most attention, if you didn’t count Excellent Era. Meanwhile, Mysterious Fantasy hadn’t gained any sort of attention ever since they had fallen to the Challenger League, making them a bit jealous. Now, seeing how this popular team was close to being swept miserably out of the competition, the team members of Mysterious Fantasy were no less delighted than their coach, even though it was directed at something different.

"We won’t be eliminated," Ye Xiu replied calmly.

"Haha, as expected of God Ye Qiu, you’re so confident. Have you calculated how many points you have to get in the last round yet?" Zhang Yiwei asked, smiling nicely.

Wei Chen then took a step forwards, staring directly at Zhang Yiwei. "Brat, are you trying to play some dirty trick on us?"

Zhang Yiwei had been a core team member once, having been a part of the Alliance for several years. Wei Chen’s threatening demeanor didn’t scare him at all, and he instead stared right back at Wei Chen. "What on earth are you talking about, Captain Wei?" He used Wei Chen’s old title when referring to him.

"Do you think I can’t tell?" Wei Chen asked.

　

"So what if you can?" Zhang Yiwei sneered, "I’m only choosing the best result for Mysterious Fantasy. Not only for now, but in the future, too. Your strength is undeniably above that of Trader’s, so it’d be in my best interests if you were squeezed out of the competition."

"Heh, don’t talk as if you’ve already won!" Ye Xiu suddenly said.

"It’s the last round, keep working hard, everyone," Ye Xiu returned what Zhang Yiwei had said before to Mysterious Fantasy verbatim. "If you accidentally get eliminated by Trader, then you would be a disappointment to your ex-pro status!

"Heh," Zhang Yiwei laughed lightly after hearing this. A veteran player like that wasn’t easy to enrage, as expected. "Then let us see what happens!"

"See you at the match."

"See you at the match!"

The two teams returned to the hotel. Though Happy hadn’t at all been at a disadvantage in the clash just now, it was undebatable that the last round of the competition did. Returning to the hotel, none of them could calm down enough to rest and soon enough they found themselves all gathering in the hotel Internet cafe, one by one.

Chen Guo saw their unity in this unspoken gathering, and was quietly excited.

"In the last round, we have to get eight points and wipe the floor with Mysterious Fantasy." Chen Guo didn’t bother to lead in, going straight for the kill and encouraging their morale.

Yet then she heard Mo Fan, who was in the corner, say stoically without even raising his head, "We won’t be able to wipe out Mysterious Fantasy with just eight points."

"What?" Chen Guo paused in shock and the others all turned their head to look. They had never thought it would be Mo Fan to respond first.

"Yes, that’s right. If it’s just eight points, Mysterious Fantasy would get two points and tie with Trader at 28 in total. However, they had won seven to three in their match again Trader, so then it would be Trader that’s eliminated, according to the rules." Ye Xiu said before glancing over at Mo Fan. "I wouldn’t have thought you cared."

Mo Fan didn’t respond.

"Do you want to play this round?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I can." Mo Fan’s answer wasn’t "I do," but "I can."

Everyone stared at Mo Fan. They might not have interacted with him much, but they had lived together for a quite some time and everyone was used to having this emotionless, silent guy in the training room. Mo Fan wasn’t exactly their friend, but he was still a part of their team, that’s what everyone thought. As for Mo Fan’s skill in Glory, everyone acknowledged it. Even though he might have not been able to integrate himself into the team at first, he had become part of the system after teamwork training in the new dungeons and training against the pro players. However, his personality meant that he would never really be a team player and Ye Xiu wouldn’t force him on that front.

Being a team player had nothing to do with having a place in a team. So long as their tactics were reasonable and they were able to carry them out well, a non-team player could also be a very important part of a team.

Tactics were also something that depended on people. Mature teams already had a tactical system they were used to, so finding players that suited their set of tactics was a big benefit for them. However, Happy was a new team so they didn’t have their own set of tactics. This was why they needed to build up their own set of tactics according to the individuals where everyone could work efficiently.

Hearing Mo Fan’s response, Ye Xiu smiled and nodded and then looked towards Luo Ji. "In the last round, we need to make sure we win by as large of a lead as possible, so I’m afraid you won’t be able to play for now."

"I understand." Luo Ji nodded, though he was still a little dejected. In these critical moments, he was unable to contribute to the team. It didn’t feel good.

"Continue to work hard!" Ye Xiu said. The reality of Luo Ji’s skill wasn’t any sort of taboo for Happy, so Ye Xiu could easily announce his arrangements at times like this without needing to make any excuses.

Then, Ye Xiu’s gaze turned to Sun Zheping. "Are you alright with taking part in this round?"

"If I don’t take part now, why am I even here?" Sun Zheping replied.

　

Ye Xiu smiled. Sun Zheping wasn’t Happy’s future, so Ye Xiu would usually give him less chances to take part although those matches probably wouldn’t be any trouble for Sun Zheping. However, if he didn’t have Sun Zheping take part in these critical moments, then there would be no point to his presence.

"Are you alright with participating in both the individual and team competitions?" Ye Xiu asked. He wasn’t very clear on Sun Zheping’s injury.

"I’ll have no problem dealing with these characters," Sun Zheping responded.

"Ok, then you can take on the first individual competition!" Ye Xiu said. Being the first to participate would allow him to have more time to rest before the Team Competition.

"Then the second person had better prepare earlier. The match will probably end quickly," Sun Zheping said.

Ye Xiu didn’t say anything about his underestimating of their opponents. This was his pride and freedom. A veteran like him wouldn’t make the rookie mistake of truly underestimating their opponents.

"Mo Fan, you’ll be second," Ye Xiu decided.

Mo Fan nodded.

As for the third… Ye Xiu was a little hesitant. He had narrowed it down to two choices, Wei Chen and Wu Chen. Wei Chen had expended a lot of energy against Team Trader that day and had yet to fully recover; Ye Xiu could tell he wasn’t in top form. As for Wu Chen, he had good skills. His form had been preserved quite well after coming to Happy, but the character he was using, Dawn Rifle, didn’t have very good equipment. Compared to the fortifications done to the other characters, Dawn Rifle wasn’t a character that Happy put importance on. After all, Wu Chen didn’t come to Happy to continue being a pro player.

"The third competition is very crucial. So it seems like this is something only I can shoulder." That was when Wei Chen shamelessly recommended himself.

　

Ye Xiu smiled and accepted this arrangement.

"Group arena, Steamed Bun, Little Tang, me."

Steamed Bun and Tang Rou nodded, seeming to have guessed that they would be in this arrangement.

"And lastly, the team competition." Ye Xiu looked over the gathered

"No healer? That’s crazy!" Even Sun Zheping was shocked at the team competition arrangements.

"You sure this will work?" Chen Guo was even more worried now.

Ye Xiu looked towards An Wenyi. "We’ll be using as fast of a pace as possible in the team competition, so the current you might not be able to keep up."

"Ok," An Wenyi nodded calmly. He could accept any arrangement, so long as there was logic behind it.

"We have two days. Let’s practice this formation as much as possible!" Ye Xiu finally said.

Chapter 971: God Setting Out

The weekend passed by quickly, and the Pro League continued to attract a lot of attention. However, Challenger League’s offline tournament entered its most crucial time, so in this week’s Monday Esports Home, there was an additional half a page.

The suspense in Group A and D had ended after the fourth round. The two pro teams, Jade Dynasty and Excellent Era, had locked into first place in groups. The teams that had reached second place in groups stood out as well.

However, Group B and C entered into a greater state of chaos in the fourth round. In terms of suspense, Group C’s matches were decent. All five teams still had a chance of making it to next round. Real suspense was when one would need to go through the matches in the last round in order to determine who would win. As for Group B? Although there was a chance for all three of the teams, Happy needed to snatch over eight points from Team Mysterious Fantasy this round. Quite a lot of people believed that Happy had no hope. On the forums, players that looked down on Happy finally found a topic to express themselves, so there were all kinds of ricidules being flung around. As for people who put their hopes in Happy, they constantly brought out the evidence that Happy had swept away Everlasting to prove the former’s possibilities. However, their voice was weaker compared to the ridicule.

In the Esports Home issue on Monday, there were two complete reports that specifically analysed Group B’s situation for the readers. In this round, Team Mysterious Fantasy only needed to get two points to get by safe and sound. If they got one more point, they could kick Happy away. They had a greater psychological advantage, so the two believed Team Mysterious Fantasy had higher chances of winning. However, the Esports Home represented the country, not of a certain region, so they couldn’t show too much of their personal preferences. Contrary to this, the regional evening reports for Team Mysterious Fantasy gave a positive report on the team’s excellent situation. They didn’t even try to hide their genuine praises and expectations.

While in City H, where Happy was located, the media had previously praised Excellent Era highly. If Excellent Era had stayed in the Pro League this season, then the media would definitely give more positive compliments towards such an eye-catching team in the Challenger League coming from their city. Unfortunately, Excellent Era happened to join Challenger League this season, so the two teams became opponents who had to fight to the death. Furthermore, Happy challenged Excellent Era when it came up, so this situation was hard for the media in City H. When Happy and Excellent Era were compared, it was obvious that no one would think of them being equals. However, before the both sides even have a chance to clash, Happy was already stuck in a dangerous position of being eliminated. The media from City H could finally speak up for the local team. However, what they said was nothing new. What the media could find was the fact that Happy had beat Everlasting. With this as evidence, they hoped that Happy could perform a miracle once more.

"Miracle?" When Ye Xiu saw this word constantly pop up in the report, he laughed. "They’re using this word already! What word would they use when we beat Excellent Era. I’m pretty worried for them!"

"Hahaha..." Chen Guo laughed dryly. The past few days had been hard on her. She was anxious and worried in every way possible. Especially after seeing Ye Xiu’s confident plan of not including a healer Chen Guo wouldn’t be herself if she could stay calm. Although she knew that Ye Xiu’s Lord Grim had a bit of skill in healing, but just having level 20 and under healer skills didn’t mean he could take up the healing responsibilities of a real Cleric or Paladin. Chen Guo was worried over making such a bold strategic move at such a crucial moment. Chen Guo feared that they would slip up like when Ye Xiu decided not to join the team match in the round against Team Trader.

However, the morale within the whole team was pretty good for the past few days. Chen Guo didn’t want to speak out her concerns and create an unexpected change of mood. Even though the day of competition had arrived, Ye Xiu still had the mood to mock the words in the report. Chen Guo couldn’t find any way to be at ease.

"Alright, call on everyone to set off!" Ye Xiu got up and exited through the door. This was followed by the sound of a door opening and locking in the corridor. Team Happy set out.

In this last round, the stadium for this offline match was much more packed compared to the previous rounds. After going through some random interviews, it was found that many of the audiences in the stadium came to watch the match between Happy and Mysterious Fantasy.

"I’m not a fan of Mysterious Fantasy, but I’m definitely not a fan of Happy. I hope Mysterious Fantasy can get three points this round, so Happy can just f*ck off!"

This was the majority of the responses from the random interviews. However, at the same time, everyone found that a new banner appeared on site: Welcome back, Ye Xiu!

Now that Ye Xiu’s Ye Qiu matter had been cleared up, nothing went out of hand under the protection of the league. It was said that Ye Qiu was a name Ye Xiu came up with when he joined the competitive scene, just like a stage name. As for now, he finally returned by using his actual name.

The final confirmation of his identity verified the hot news of "God’s return". The influence of the first God on the competitive scene was obviously immense. His action of creating a team to fight to the death against Excellent Era in Challenger League attracted a lot of resentment from many Excellent Era fans. However, there were still a lot of players who liked this God, but felt nothing towards Excellent Era. Many of these fans were extremely welcome towards God’s return.

There were even fans from other teams who started to try to help their team recruit Ye Xiu. Although it was wishful thinking, they called for God to join their team. There was an increase in all kinds of analysis having to do with "Reasons Ye Qiu should join XX team" online.

Among all this, there was one tragic Tyranny fan. He cried out for Ye Xiu to join Tyranny so that the most extravagant team in the history of Glory could be formed. However, he received attacks from Tyranny’s diehard fans. It was evident that, as a loyal fan of Tyranny, Ye Qiu was the most hated pro player in Glory. The diehard fans even seriously threatened Tyranny that if they recruited Ye Qiu, they would boycott all of Tyranny’s future competition as a form of protest. It was as if Ye Qiu joining Team Tyranny was already a reality…...

As a result, at the site of Challenger League, supporters of God Ye Qiu gradually gathered. This was the most relieving thing for Chen Guo to see for the past few days.

At the same time, Sun Zheping appearing in Team Happy also attracted a lot of attention, especially fans of Team Hundred Blossoms. There were all kinds of astonishment and awe. The journalists contacted Team Hundred Blossoms. However, the clubs expressed that they didn’t know about Sun Zheping’s return. They also didn’t express any intentions of contacting Sun Zheping at the moment. This meant that the future of Hundred Blossoms still revolved around Yu Feng as the ace.

Surrounding news and events continued to emerge, but for Happy, their current match was what mattered most. The round between Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy would be played live on the side. This was a match in the offline tournament that had things to watch for.

The competition started at eight o’clock sharp. Since there were seven other matches going on at the same time, they couldn’t put too much of their focus on one particular match. The match between Happy and Mysterious Fantasy wasn’t able to get more part on screen. It was obvious that they wouldn’t announce the list of the contestants’ names whom were playing. After all, there were eight matches going on the same time, they wouldn’t be able to broadcast them all.

The list was shown through the electronic screen. As for Happy, first up was Sun Zheping.

This created a stir in the stadium. After all, for an old Glory fan, this name held brilliant radiance.

"Finally going on stage?" Zhang Yiwei spoke. His face was filled with confidence, and he turned his head to see the members of Happy. The seats for the two competing teams in the match were quite close, so they could interact directly with each other.

"There are still a lot of "finally" moments to come. Take it easy on that word." Ye Xiu said.

"Haha, I’ll be looking forward to it." Zhang Yiwei laughed. The first player from Mysterious Fantasy was also announced at the same time: Fang Daxu. He was a Knight player who had been in Mysterious Fantasy’s roster for the last two seasons. When Mysterious Fantasy was eliminated, he didn’t receive invitations from any other teams. It could be seen that his skills weren’t too outstanding.

The two player entered into the match, and started to load in their characters. Zhang Yiwei turned his head to look at Ye Xiu. "Is Sun Zheping’s hand injury alright?"

"What do you think?" Ye Xiu said.

"I say he should use it more cautiously." Zhang Yiwei said.

Chen Guo was alarmed when she heard this. He even knew about this? Could there be traitors on the team?! However, Ye Xiu remained cool. He laughed and didn’t reply. He knew that although Zhang Yiwei wasn’t an outstanding player, he had been in the circle for quite some time, so was experienced and had knowledge. Sun Zheping’s condition wasn’t hard to guess, but he wasn’t able to confirm about it. Ye Xiu wouldn’t let him worm that fact out.

"This matchup is quite good." Zhang Yiwei laughed.

"Seems like you’ve done your research!" Ye Xiu said. Teams wouldn’t normally reveal the player’s playing order before hand. As a result, guessing the opponent’s order, and making targeted arrangements was one branch of study in a match. Judging from Zhang Yiwei’s look and expression, it seemed like he guessed that Happy would send Sun Zheping to play first.

"You guys are in a hurry to snatch the points. If Sun Zheping doesn’t play, then there would be no point for him to be in your team. If there’s pressure from his hand injury, it’s better if he plays earlier. Then, he would be able to rest for a bit longer before he plays in the team match." Zhang Yiwei said.

Chen Guo was startled, why would the opponent know all of these? Is it really from guessing?

"So you sent a Knight on stage. It seems like you are planning to drag on the fight?" Ye Xiu said.

Zhang Yiwei laughed without speaking, and focused his gaze on the competition’s screen. The two characters had finished loading. Both sides pressed ready and were about to be loaded into the map.

There were no home and away games, so they were no home and away teams. The maps in the offline tournament were all chosen by the league. All of the maps were made specifically for competitive Glory. No team would have the chance to practice with it beforehand, so it was relatively fair. The map would also be used for the other matches. This was confirmed and announced on the first day of the competition, so people could download the maps. From that moment onwards, every team would train with the map they would use.

The two loaded characters started to head towards the map’s center. Since Sun Zheping was a God, the broadcast commentator would definitely emphasize mentioning and introducing him. The commentary introduced his previous glory, playstyle, and achievements, while feeling pleased. It was much easier to broadcast a match with professional players because they had stories and content to talk about. Contrastingly, he could only dully explain the match for the teams made of online players. There were no spice to it.

The two characters met before the commentator could finish introducing Sun Zheping’s background. He could only stop hurriedly, and pay attention to the match.

"Oh, the two sides have met."

"Seems like Mysterious Fantasy’s Fang Daxu is putting out a defensive stance, and prepared to strike back."

"Sun Zheping is fighting straight on."

"Wow! A big move! He started with a big move the moment the fight started. This confidence is worthy of a former God!"

"Combo! Oh, it’s linked up beautifully. It seems that despite not fighting in competitions for so many years, Sun Zheping didn’t lose any of his abilities."

"Fang Daxu is at an absolute disadvantage!"

"A wave of combo with twelve hits! Although the hits weren’t heavy, the damage output is very impressive. It’s concise and practical! Eh..."

"The attacks have connected, here comes another wave... the one from before was a fake combo, so the combos were disconnected according to the system’s calculations. However, the attacks still connected. Fang Daxu must be having a hard time, isn’t he?"

"Fang Daxu’s situation is very passive!"

"Fang Daxu should hurry up and come up with an idea."

"Fang Daxu’s situation is dangerous..."

"Fang Daxu..."

"Dead..."

"Uh... Let’s continue to talk about player Sun Zheping’s situation after the matches..." The commentator started to sweat. He didn’t even have another chance to continue to talk about Sun Zheping’s past because the round had ended.

Chapter 972: Extreme Contrast

It was impossible to know the reactions of those watching the live broadcast, but the audience present was silent like the grave.

Most of the audience had been watching this match closely, so what they saw was the two characters meeting and then Sun Zheping’s Another Summer of Sleep attacking, attacking, attacking and then his opponent died.

Did Fang Daxu’s Knight even use any skills?

Everyone’s memory of it seemed blurred. Even if skills had been used, they didn’t seem to have done anything, buried amongst Another Summer of Sleep’s attacks.

One minute and seventeen seconds...

This was the amount of time the first Individual competition had taken. It wasn’t until the statistics were shown that the audience went crazy.

This was a pro level match right? Even though Mysterious Fantasy might not be the strongest, they were still a pro team, right? Even though Fang Daxu hadn’t been taken in by any of the other pro teams, he still managed to stay in the pro circle a full two years, no?

One minute seventeen seconds? And a Knight as well? He just lost with seemingly no resistance like that?

Most of the audience came to see Happy humiliated, but in this moment, they couldn’t help but boo Mysterious Fantasy.

They had seen fast, but not this fast. A tanky Knight being wiped out in one minute and seventeen seconds, did he grab the wrong equipment and go up in cloth armor?

Amidst the booing, Sun Zheping had already come down from the stage. He had immediately stood and left as soon as the result was out.

"So fast." Ye Xiu smiled, stretching his hand out to Sun Zheping.

"I wanted to rest earlier." Sun Zheping high fived Ye Xiu before returning to his own seat, turning to glance over at Zhang Yiwei, tilting his head up and saying, "A Knight, huh?"

Zhang Yiwei’s face was clouded over and that was when he saw their team’s Fang Daxu walk out from the stands in bewilderment, listen to the booing increase by several decibels with further bewilderment, and come down from the stage with even more bewilderment. Seeing the dumb look on his face made Zhang Yiwei irritated and he wanted to go up and kick some sense into the player. However, he knew that this was nowhere near appropriate. He had to keep calm, otherwise it could affect the morale of the entire team. Having been a coach for two years, Zhang Yiwei understood the ins and outs of leading a team. In his heart, he might’ve been about to erupt, but after Fang Daxu came down, he only said, lightly, "You were too impatient."

"Ah?" Fang Daxu who’s mind had cleared a bit was bewildered once more. Had he been impatient? However, before he could say any more, Zhang Yiwei was already continuing, "Go and take a break!"

Fang Daxu sat to one side dumbly. He had no idea that this was one of Zhang Yiwei’s leadership techniques. He had been clearly and completely suppressed by the opponent, yet from Zhang Yiwei’s mouth it sounded like Fang Daxu had simply underestimated his opponent. This way, he didn’t let the opponent’s spirits rise too much and reminded the other players to not lower their guard either.

"Luo Tian, it’s your turn," Zhang Yiwei then called for the second player to go up. His tone calm and keeping his inner shock well hidden. He understood very clearly that Happy’s reasons for arranging Sun Zheping to play first didn’t just stop at the fact that Sun Zheping needed rest. At the same time, they were hoping that Sun Zheping would score them an overwhelming victory for the opening match and boost their morale while striking at their opponent’s.

Zhang Yiwei wasn’t hoping for Fang Daxu to score a point when he arranged for Fang Daxu to be their first player, but for him to utilize the Knight’s defensive capabilities to their fullest, thereby dragging the match on and forcing Sun Zheping to expend more energy on it. At the same time, they could minimize the impact of their opponent’s fierce arrangement. This was killing two birds with one stone. Yet in the end, Fang Daxu didn’t do a good job, unable to achieve any of his goals. So all Zhang Yiwei could do was use his own composure to minimize the impact this defeat would bring to their team.

Zhang Yiwei’s actions helped calm the players of Mysterious Fantasy quite a lot, as expected. However, Luo Tian, who was up next, didn’t seem to be adhering to expectations. The effects of Sun Zheping’s overwhelming performance couldn’t be completely neutralized by just a few words and a calm attitude from Zhang Yiwei.

"Do your best." Zhang Yiwei didn’t say too much. The more he said, the more nervous he’d seem. If he was too serious about a match where they only needed to get two points, it might have the opposite effect of making the players panic.

Luo Tian nodded and took a deep breath before heading to the stage.

As for Happy, Zhang Yiwei looked around and saw Mo Fan standing up.

"Hm, this guy hasn’t seemed to have played any matches before? How come he’s become restless today?" Zhang Yiwei said, trying to strike at Mo Fan emotionally. However, he got no visible response, not even a glance before Mo Fan walked away and onto the stage, making Zhang Yiwei suspect that his voice just now had been too quiet for notice.

"Haha, don’t be offended. He’s always like this. He even ignores me, usually," Ye Xiu said.

　

"Hahaha…." Zhang Yiwei laughed dryly, evidently not believing Ye Xiu’s words. On the other hand, Happy’s other members felt like Ye Xiu was sticking gold on his face. Mo Fan ignoring him? More like absolutely hating him!

　

The players of each side had already entered the stands, and their characters were loaded into the map.

Mysterious Fantasy’s Luo Tian had played as a core member for two years, using an Elementalist character.

After the commentator gave some vague background information on Luo Tian, he couldn’t be bothered with this unimportant and small character from a relegated team anymore. His interest was more on Mo Fan, enthusiastically regaling everyone with the tales of Deception in the Heavenly Domain

"Hey, hey, don’t forget your impartiality!" As the commentator spoke excitedly, the program director hurriedly gave him a yelled reminder. The commentator snapped out of it and hastily added, "Of course, this sort of behavior shouldn’t be encouraged. We hope that everyone can play fairly and peacefully…"

"Okay, the match has begun, let us turn our attention to the match." The commentator knew that his ramble about scrip-picking wasn’t very appropriate, so he quickly stopped himself and turned to the match.

After the defeat last round, Mysterious Fantasy’s player was much more careful. Compared to Luo Tian, Mo Fan had very little fame in the pro circle, but Luo Tian didn’t dare underestimate him at all. As he had his character move forth, he continuously used small skills to test out his surrounding, guarded against being closed in on.

　

Ninjas weren’t the best at close combat, but they were very good at hiding their movements and getting close to their targets without being seen. From this point of view, Ninjas had an advantage over classes like the Elementalist that feared being closed in on. It was because of this that Elementalists would put priority on guarding against this. The current Luo Tian was cautiously having Elementalist move forwards, using different moves and techniques, yet he never caught even a glimpse of Mo Fan.

　

The audience was much more clear on Mo Fan’s whereabouts. From the start, Mo Fan had chosen a roundabout path, preparing a sneak attack on his opponent as expected.

　

Currently, Deception was already watching Luo Tian’s Elementalist from the shadows, but Luo Tian had yet to realize this. Everyone was on the edge of their seats, thinking that Deception was about to find a chance to close in, but all Deception did was patiently follow the Elementalist around, as if waiting for a chance.

Everyone had no choice but to continue waiting.

"Chance!"

"Chance!"

"Chance!"

The commentator had already yelled out "chance" thrice, but Mo Fan continued to abstain from action. The commentator didn’t dare yell it anymore. This thunder without rain put him in an awkward position with his yelling! However, even if he didn’t yell aloud, he would still keep track in his heart. It wasn’t just him, but the entire audience that was keeping tracking of Mo Fan’s opportunities.

"He didn’t strike…"

"He still hasn’t struck…"

"Fuck, that was a great opportunity, but he still didn’t take it?"

Slowly, more and more people began to lose their patience. This Deception seemed to be merely following Luo Tian’s Elementalist, making Mysterious Fantasy’s members anxious as hell. Yet this guy never struck. It was as if just continuing to stalk his opponent would give him a victory.

Mysterious Fantasy started out anxious, but slowly became impatient as well. Zhang Yiwei turned his head around, smiling falsely. "I say, this player of yours sure is careful!"

Careful? This was something the commentator had also said, but now it didn’t seem appropriate to use this word anymore. If this was considered "careful", then "careful" must be feeling very pressured.

"He just has enough patience," Ye Xiu said with a smile.

　

"Is that so? Then why don’t you tell me how long he can wait? If you don’t tell me, then I’ll really have no way of knowing," Zhang Yiwei said.

"Don’t worry, he’ll strike when the time is right. Don’t think too much about it. Go and think about what to say to your team after your second consecutive defeat!" Ye Xiu replied.

"I wouldn’t do something unnecessary like that," Zhang Yiwei said, turning his head back and ignoring Ye Xiu.

On the field, Deception was still following his target. Luo Tian had carefully moved all the way until he finally arrived at where Deception had started out, but still didn’t find his target. Luo Tian immediately hesitated, not knowing where to go next. He helplessly turned around, choosing another path and following it carefully like before.

The audience was being driven crazy.

The previous match had been extremely direct, with the opponent being cut to pieces almost instantly. Although the result wasn’t ideal, it was at least satisfying to watch. Now the second match was an extreme contrast to the first. Last match was a swift one minute seventeen seconds, and now it had become an unending stall.

It had been three minutes since the match had started. At a pro level, this was enough time for the match to have come to a close. Yet in the current match, the two sides hadn’t even clashed once.

Luo Tian’s Elementalist was already wandering around aimlessly. Yet the target he was trying to find, Deception, was following after him closely without him knowing.

The boos started again, all yelling for Mo Fan get out. However, Mo Fan didn’t adhere, continuing to follow Luo Tian.

"Patient, huh?" Zhang Yiwei turned around again, sarcasm on his tongue.

　

"Yup, patient." Ye Xiu nodded in affirmation.

"So he’s just going to be patient like this forever?"

"Of course not. Haven’t you seen that many people have already lost their patience?" Ye Xiu pointed at the jeering crowds. "Those without patience will only lose."

　

As Ye Xiu’s words fell, Zhang Yiwei startled, turning to the match. As expected, Luo Tian had already begun to lose his patience, his technique becoming more and more mechanical.

The opportunity had arrived!

Chapter 973: A Scrap Picker’s Talents

Luo Tian's half-hearted wariness made Zhang Yiwei feel the urge to rush onto the stage and whip that guy. You're in the middle of a match! How can you become so relaxed?

In reality, patience wasn't something that could completely disappear all of a sudden. Patience had to be gradually worn down. Luo Tian was no exception. The crowd was also no exception. Even Zhang Yiwei was no exception. If he had been patiently and calmly watching the match, he would have noticed Luo Tian's movements losing shape long ago. He wouldn't have abruptly noticed it just now.

The expression on Zhang Yiwei's face suddenly changed. Right when he was about to cry not good, Mo Fan's Deception finally moved.

Ninjutsu - Disappearing Body Technique!

During these 30 seconds, Ninjas could climb in all sorts of angles like a spider, allowing them to attack from a blind spot. In the beginning, Luo Tian had been wary of this, but his guard had already gone down. Mo Fan had thoroughly checked the surrounding terrain. His figure slowly inched closer to Luo Tian's Elementalist in a strange manner.

It was a very ordinary strategy, but the patience and concentration displayed by Mo Fan was quite frightening. It wasn't just strolling down the road towards his target. He had to ensure that he wouldn't be noticed, so he couldn't be careless at all. Due to his long scrap picking career, Mo Fan was a master in both of these aspects. Most pro players didn't have that type of experience. As time passed, Luo Tian's movements started to become sloppy, but Mo Fan still didn't show himself. When concentration faced carelessness, the result was obvious the moment Deception made a move.

Ninjutsu - Shadow Dance!

When Deception began his assault, he immediately started off with a high-level skill. Countless shadows of Deception suddenly appeared in front of the already jittery Luo Tian. Let alone figuring out which shadow was the core, Luo Tian wasn't even able to react to the incoming attack in time. The shadows pounced on him, and the combo count skyrocketed. Mo Fan had been patiently waiting for an opportunity to the extent that everyone had started feeling annoyed, but as soon as he attacked, his agility didn't lose to Sun Zheping at all. This was also a habit acquired from scrap picking. If he wasn't so decisive, he would have turned into scrap who knew how many times throughout his scrap picking career.

But because of his habits from scrap picking, while Mo Fan acquired several strengths, he also acquired several flaws. Although Mo Fan's offensive was very fierce, he lacked the ability to consistently extend his combos. It felt a bit like Cheng Yaojin and his three axe strokes*. When he scrap picked, even if he attacked to kill his opponents, he would usually only choose characters who only a sliver of health left. As a scrap picker, picking a fight with a group of full-health players was just asking for his own death.

Frequently killing these types of low-health targets led to Mo Fan being exceptional at short bursts of damage, but his attack afterwards felt rather weak.

Sun Zheping destroyed a Knight in 1 minute 17 seconds. On the other hand, after Mo Fan successfully closed in on the Elementalist, he was unable to quickly end the battle in a short period of time. In comparison to his sudden ambush with several high-level skills linked together, his following attacks made it feel like the offensive had a strong start but weak finish**.

Normal players might not be able to notice such a minute difference, but Zhang Yiwei was a former pro player with a wealth of experience. He immediately noticed it.

"It's an opportunity! Steady, steady!" Zhang Yiwei couldn't help but blurt out. He completely forgot that Luo Tian couldn't hear him at all. However, Luo Tian didn't disappoint him. After being caught off guard, he started steadying himself.

"Don't feel too delighted just yet." Zhang Yiwei turned his head to glance at the relaxed and smiling Ye Xiu.

"Hahaha." Ye Xiu laughed. Zhang Yiwei turned his head back and suddenly froze.　　

After Deception's three axe strokes, his offensive instantly became weak. Luo Tian steadied himself and, right when he was about to launch his counterattack, he saw that Deception was running away.

Yes, running away!

The battle wasn't over yet. Luo Tian's Elementalist hadn't started his counterattack yet, and Deception was actually running away already. Luo Tian hadn't predicted this would happen. When he started chasing after him, Deception had already disappeared without a trace. Luo Tian suddenly also froze in his seat.

"Happy's Mo Fan is really surprising." The commentator was also stunned, but he couldn't be idle, "But I have to say, this is truly a scrap picker's style of fighting."

Deception had disappeared, but that was only from Luo Tian's perspective. Everyone else could see Deception's location from the god's view on stream. He had gone into hiding again. It was just like in the beginning. He was following Luo Tian's Elementalist closely. The match once again circled back to the very beginning. It was just that this time, Luo Tian wasn't nearly as calm as before; he was searching frantically for traces of Deception. On the other hand, Mo Fan was as calm and patient as ever. His previous burst of attacks didn't seem to make him feel fired up.

This was another characteristic of a scrap picker: restraint.

Let's say there was an extremely precious piece of equipment in front of your face. How many players could restrain themselves from picking it up? Most would rush forward to give it a try even if they ended up dying, but Mo Fan would never do so. He would always wait for the right opportunity before acting, even if he wasn't able to get it in the end as a result.

When he felt like the situation wasn't suitable for him to continue, he wouldn't continue even if the crowd's boos instantly erupted. This type of playstyle was clearly unpopular.

Unfortunately, these boos didn't help Zhang Yiwei feel any better either.

Even if Mo Fan failed to win over the crowd, he would at least win over his opponent. This 1 point was already on the verge of being lost in Zhang Yiwei's eyes. Even if Luo Tian learned from his past mistakes and didn't dare to be as careless, his mentality had already tipped the scale. In this situation, it wasn't just patience that was necessary. Calmness was needed too. However, Luo Tian wasn't calm at all. He treated every tree and blade of grass as an enemy, throwing his magic around aimlessly.

"He's lost it." Ye Xiu shook his head.

It was as if Mo Fan heard this evaluation. He suddenly made his move.

"Ah! Mo Fan didn't choose to use Disappearing Body Technique to find an opportunity to move closer. Instead, he's directly revealed himself." The commentator cried out.

Luo Tian was surprised by this sudden appearance, but he immediately followed up with a bunch of attacks delightedly. His Elementalist staff waved. However, not even a spark flew out from it.

"What is Luo Tian doing? Is he posing?" The commentator was puzzled.

Luo Tian wanted to cry. After putting in the correct inputs, he heard a system notification: on cooldown.

Such a low-leveled mistake actually happened to a pro player. The extent of Luo Tian's instability could be seen from this. He hastily chose another skill and couldn't help but check which skills were on cooldown and which skills weren't. He had been throwing out magic spells randomly along the way. It was just like Ye Xiu said. He had completely lost it. There was no purpose or decision-making in his "cautious" choices. He didn't even remember which skills were on cooldown.

As a result, Mo Fan once again took the initiative. At the same time, this wave of attacks left Luo Tian in despair. His ability to resist fell to zero so much so that he couldn't even steady himself like before. He was like a noob, randomly throwing skills trying to escape from the predicament.

Against this type of defense, even if Mo Fan was lacking in his ability to follow up, he was more than good enough to deal with it. As a result, he didn't retreat this time.

A short moment later, Luo Tian's Elementalist fell. The second round of the match concluded.

The post-game statistics on the screen made the entire crowd boo loudly. 8 minutes 12 seconds. This match actually took 8 minutes and 12 seconds. In the individual competition, this was absolutely considered an anomaly.

In any case, Happy pocketed that 1 point.

Mo Fan quietly went off the stage.

"Not bad." Ye Xiu clapped. The others from Happy applauded his performance. Mo Fan didn't say anything and quietly returned to his seat as if nothing had happened. His eyes were fixed on the stage. Who knew what he was truly thinking.

Team Mysterious Fantasy's Luo Tian went down from the stage too. His face was pale, and he stumbled on the way over.

"You lost your calm!" Zhang Yiwei hastily covered his inner thoughts and said to Luo Tian.

"You actually found his weakness, but you didn't do a good job turning that into an advantage." Zhang Yiwei followed up. Unlike before with Fang Daxu, he didn't find an excuse like you were just too impatient. This time, Zhang Yiwei really had seen an opportunity for Luo Tian to make a comeback. Unfortunately, Mo Fan immediately chose to run away, making Luo Tian instantly feel lost.

"Next time." Zhang Yiwei patted Luo Tian, telling him that he could take a break.

For the third match, Team Happy's Wei Chen came out. A look of pride showed up on his grizzly face. He glanced at the player seats for Team Mysterious Fantasy and waved his hands: "This senior's about to go on stage. Is there even a need to play this match? Why don't you just forfeit?"

Zhan Wenyi ignored him. He nodded his head towards the player, who would be playing for this third match. That player stood up and headed over to the stage with his head held high.

"There's really no need to play this match! You guys only need 2 points. What's the point of fighting for this 1 point? My recommendation is that you just play around and save your time and energy." Wei Chen followed up.

The referee immediately ran over from the stage and threw a yellow card at Wei Chen.

"Inappropriate remark. First warning. If you violate the competitive integrity of Glory a second time, the committee will rethink your qualifications to compete." The referee said gravely.

"F*ck, I can't even make a joke?" Wei Chen defended himself. The referee didn't care though; he turned around and went back on stage.

"Their demands are so strict nowadays, ha." Wei Chen said angrily towards his teammates and then walked onto the stage.

Chapter 974: Forced Into Helplessness

The third round of the individual competition began. The characters on both sides loaded into the map and prepared to fight.

It was just like Wei Chen said. In theory, this round was pointless for both sides. This single point wouldn't affect the overall outcome of the match. However, competition was not as simple as adding two numbers together. This point wouldn't have any effect on the outcome of the match, but the winner of this round could affect their team's momentum in the following sections of the match.

Team Happy had won two rounds in a row in the individual competition. Their morale was undoubtedly at a high. As for Team Mysterious Fantasy? Losing two rounds in a row in such an extreme manner was a heavy blow to their morale. Zhang Yiwei pretending that it wasn't a big deal wouldn't be enough to neutralize the effects.

Neither team dared to overlook how this round would affect their morale.

The characters quickly finished loading into the map. Wei Chen's Windward Formation was without a doubt the character in the spotlight in this year's Challenger League. Although Team Excellent Era had One Autumn Leaf, Life Extinguisher, and Dancing Rain, these were all All Star characters. Players were used to seeing their greatness, but Windward Formation? This character had come out of nowhere and appeared with eight pieces of Silver equipment. In the pro scene, most subs didn't have characters that enjoyed such beautiful equipment.

Team Mysterious Fantasy had been a bottom-tier team in the pro scene. Let alone subs, their team didn't have a single character even among their main roster that had eight pieces of Silver equipment. Facing Windward Formation, it was Team Mysterious Fantasy that looked like a grassroots team.

The commentator joked around and introduced these two players in this way.　　

"Okay, the match has started. In the previous two rounds, Team Happy won in surprising ways. Will they surprise us again this round? Wei Chen. I think the older folks might be familiar with him. He was Team Blue Rain's very first team captain. The number one Warlock, Swoksaar, was actually created and brought into the Alliance by him. Those who have watched his matches in the past definitely have a certain impression of him because he has a... yes, yes... very distinctive personality. Next, let's enjoy this round."

"Little demon, bring it on!"

Wei Chen typed out in the all-chat at the start of the match and then just stood there. Windward Formation didn't seem to have any intentions of advancing and simply waited for his opponent to come to him.

This Team Mysterious Fantasy player didn't know. He just treated it like an ordinary provocation and had his character charge ahead at full speed. Halfway through, he still hadn't seen Windward Formation. He felt like something wasn't right.

Usually, at this point, both sides should have already come across each other in the middle of the map! Why was there no sign of him?

Not good!

This Team Mysterious Fantasy player was using a Sharpshooter. He turned around nimbly and raised both of his guns, cautiously pointing to the left and right.

The crowd was waiting for him to hurry over to Windward Formation's spawn location and start fighting. Who would have thought that this guy would start admiring himself and stop halfway there. At first, they were puzzled. Then, they realized what he was doing and suddenly roared with laughter.

This scene clearly illustrated why every round in a match wasn't as simple as counting points. This player had clearly been affected by the previous match. After not seeing any traces of his opponent on his way over, he thought the opponent had employed a strategy similar to Deception's and immediately began cautiously checking his surroundings.　

It didn't stop there. After looking around and failing to notice anything, he extended his search radius. He didn't hurry forward and began spinning around in a circle.

The crowd roared with laughter again, but after laughing, they started feeling a bit tired of it. How long was this guy going to stay overly suspicious?

The crowd's laughter made everyone on Team Mysterious Fantasy feel very embarrassed. However, they had no way of telling the player on stage. They could only continue watching with faces flushed with embarrassment as their Sharpshooter spun around, not moving towards Windward Formation's location.

"Ha ha, little child, you think you can find this senior just spinning around like that?" A message from Wei Chen suddenly popped up in the all chat.

The crowd went into an uproar. In theory, this guy shouldn't know anything about his opponent's movements. However, he had been standing in the same place for quite a while. The other side still hadn't appeared. It wasn't hard to guess that his opponent was running around in circles, but this guy took advantage of it and put on an act. This was too much like trying to hit a snake with a stick, but seeing the snake curl around the stick.

When Team Mysterious Fantasy's player saw these words, he became even more nervous and started searching even more frantically for Windward Formation.

Where was Windward Formation? He had finally started moving, but he wasn't moving towards his opponent. Instead, he walked over to a big rock near his spawn location and quietly crouched down behind it.

Despicable! Too despicabe!　　

The rules didn't forbid this type of strategy, but pro players valued their images. There would be so many people watching them every round. In the eyes of the spectators, this strategy was too shameless. This wasn't just playing dirty. It was being dirty.

Even the commentator noted it. After seeing Windward Formation's move, he also felt powerless. As a professional commentator, he had done his homework beforehand. He obviously had some understanding of Wei Chen's background, but he didn't have that much time. He had only skimmed through a few articles relating to Wei Chen.

Shameless, unscrupulous…...

The information that he had seen was filled with all sorts of synonyms for this words. It wasn't convenient for him to directly say these words as a commentator, so in the end, he just said that Wei Chen had a very distinct personality. Now, he finally witnessed this distinct personality. He couldn't even make any comments on it.

As a result, the entire stadium was silent. Wei Chen's Windward Formation just sat there, hiding behind a rock. Team Mysterious Fantasy's Sharpshooter continued to looked at everything suspiciously. The commentator didn't know what to say. The crowd was speechless. Was this a match or a farce? Seeing how Wei Chen would say a few words in the all chat from time to time, everyone in Team Mysterious Fantasy felt a bit regretful. Maybe they should have listened to Wei Chen and just forfeited. Wasn't that actually a good suggestion?　　

The other side was calm and unruffled in the midst of chaos. He didn't seem to be embarrassed at all, hiding in a corner. On the other hand, their player was being overly suspicious. He had told himself that he would try very hard. After the initial fun and embarrassment, Team Mysterious Fantasy started to feel some sympathy and bitterness. It would be better to just lose this round, than to watch their teammate keep trying and making a fool of himself.

Zhang Yiwei could feel his team's emotions. He turned around and said a few words to a player.

"Forfeit?" Tang Xin heard his coach's decision. He was still astonished. Even though he had thought about it, he still gave up on it, but now, the coach had actually decided on it.

Tang Xin was Team Mysterious Fantasy's captain. The Pro Alliance hadn't approved of a coach position. The team captain had a lot of power. Coaches did not enjoy that same authority. For example, if the team wanted to forfeit right now, besides the player playing on stage, only the team captain had the power to make that decision. As a result, only the team captain could go and talk to the referee. If Zhang Yiwei went to the referee with his position as a coach and told him that his team would forfeit this round, the referee would simply ignore him.

"Are we really going to forfeit?" Tang Xin hesitated. Even though the team captain had that right, it was still an individual competition. The player on stage hadn't given up yet. Making this decision would certainly hurt the player who was trying so hard.

"It's fine!" Zhang Yiwei made his decision.

What he wanted this round wasn't a victory because that one point wasn't important. Zhang Yiwei had wanted to utilize this match to win back some morale to the team, but their player was just being toyed with. The other side was happily waiting for his exhausted opponent. If this continued, their chances of losing were very high. This result would be an even greater blow to their morale. Even though winning in this situation would certainly be a huge momentum swing for their entire team, Zhang Yiwei wasn't willing to gamble because he could already tell that giving up on this match would be freeing for the entire team. This round was too sullen and depressing.

"Okay….." In Team Mysterious Fantasy, their coach was supreme. Tang Xin could only respect Zhang Yiwei's decision and walked over to the stage.

No one was allowed on stage in the middle of a match. When Tang Xin got close, the referee blocked his path. Tang Xin told him what he had come over to say. The referee was startled. He made one final confirmation with Tang Xin. After confirming it with Tang Xin, he returned to the stage and went over to Team Mysterious Fantasy's player.

Tang Xin didn't return to his seat. He had to pick up his player here. He was certain that this decision would definitely make his player very disappointed with himself. He had to do his best to console him.

Soon afterwards, the referee told the Team Mysterious Fantasy player on stage that the team had forfeited this round. And just like that, with neither side meeting each other, Team Mysterious Fantasy's player left the stage. The referee announced Team Happy's victory.　　

"What?" Wei Chen was still hiding behind the rock, thinking of what else to say next, when he suddenly saw a notification that the other side had left the match. He was puzzled. In a match, there were times when you were aware that you were outclassed and admitted defeat in a stylish manner, but the two sides hadn't even seen each other yet and the other side already forfeited?

Wei Chen got up from his seat and saw Team Mysterious Fantasy's player leaving the stage. He walked down from the stage filled with bewilderment and looked at Team Mysterious Fantasy's side: "Now you forfeit? What were you doing before?"

We didn't know you'd be so shameless!

Team Mysterious Fantasy's players were all cursing in their hearts. They revealed all sorts of unfriendly looks towards Wei Chen. However, just like Zhang Yiwei predicted, this loss actually made everyone else ease up quite a bit. The player who had been forced to forfeit was sitting in a corner, staring blankly into space. No one knew what he was thinking. The team captain, Tang Xin, was sitting next to him, trying his best to console him. Then, everyone heard Wei Chen's words after he returned to Team Happy's seats: "How was that? I played pretty well, didn't I?"

Chapter 975: Gun Fu

Cough cough cough cough…...

Wei Chen's remark sent Team Happy into a fit of coughs. Everyone used this method to dodge the question. They all refused to answer it. However, Gods were still the mightiest. The look on Ye Xiu's face didn't change. He calmly replied back: "You typed pretty well."

"Hahaha, that's what I meant." Wei Chen laughed, sending Team Happy into another fit of coughs.

The individual competition was over. Team Happy won all three rounds, taking three points for themselves. Having not won any points in the individual competition, Team Mysterious Fantasy needed to win either the group arena or team competition. As for Team Happy, after winning these three points, the group arena wasn't as stressful. The deciding battle would definitely be the team competition.

But since Team Happy needed to win more than 8 points to qualify out of groups, they already knew that they needed to win the team competition, so their mentality was no different than before. Winning all three points in the individual competition made their morale soar. As for Team Mysterious Fantasy, after two losses in the individual competition, the third round made a turn for the better. When things moved to the extreme, they could only move in the opposite direction. In the third round, Wei Chen beating their player in such a manner made Team Mysterious Fantasy furious. Under the instigation from the experienced Zhang Yiwei, their morale ignited once more. It was only a pity that this third player could only become a sacrificial pawn for Zhang Yiwei's morale boost. At this moment, Zhang Yiwei didn't have the time to console this player.

The break between the individual competition and the group arena was rather long. After both sides made their preparations, they went into battle once again. The fires of the competition grew increasingly stronger.

"Okay, Team Mysterious Fantasy versus Team Happy. The second round's group arena will soon start." On the broadcast, advertisements would be played during the break time. Just before the group arena began, the broadcast returned to the program and the commentator began his work once again. In the previous battle, the commentator practically didn't utter a word near the end. Usually, this could be considered as a broadcasting accident, but it was unprecedented this time. The commentator didn't speak when he was meant to. It seemed like Wei Chen's super shamelessness had stunned everyone. Everyone understood the commentator's reaction and forgave him.

"The players on both sides have now entered the stage. On Team Happy's side, the first player to go out is Bao Rongxing. This player is the definition of a rookie. He'll frequently make extremely low-level mistakes. Who knows what type of performance he will give in a crucial match like today's? On Team Mysterious Fantasy's side, the first player to go out is Tang Xing. This arrangement is a little unexpected! As Team Mysterious Fantasy's captain, Tang Xing cold be considered their team's best player. According to the usual convention, this type of player should be the last one in the group arena. I wonder why Team Mysterious Fantasy made such an arrangement. We all know that Team Mysterious Fantasy has their own dedicated coach to guide them. There should be a reason for this arrangement. We'll only be able to figure out what his intentions are from watching the match. Okay, the match has officially started."

The commentator had been awkwardly silent in the previous round. It was as if his words had been transferred to this one. He talked non-stop as soon as he started.

'The characters on both sides are moving forward. Neither of them are employing any tactical moves. Are they planning on directly confronting each other?"

"Oh, Tang Xing has changed his pathing. He's started to take a roundabout route. It looks like he's planning on catching his opponent off guard."

"Okay, Tang Xing has successfully circled around to the side of his opponent. Bao Rongxing hasn't noticed him yet."

"Tang Xing is moving closer step by step. He can already start attacking at this distance! But Bao Rongxing still hasn't noticed him. He's still moving forward like before. That shouldn't be happening. It's already been this long and he hasn't encountered his opponent. Shouldn't he know that the opponent isn't just charging forward?"

"Tang Xing is by Steamed Bun Invasion's side. He still hasn't attacked... Uh, at this moment, I think many people are thinking the same thing as me. Remember the second round of the individual competition? Is Tang Xing planning on using this method to fight eye for an eye?"

"Oh, he's not doing that! Tang Xing has attacked. He's taken the initiative." As the commentator shouted, the two sides started their first exchange.

Tang Xing's character was a Sharpshooter. It was the class that their coach Zhang Yiwei once used. Zhang Yiwei also placed a lot of hope and expectations on him because of this. Under his guidance, hints of his past self appeared in Tang Xing's playstyle.

Gun Fu!

This was what Zhang Yiwei had been most proficient in. After become the coach for Team Mysterious Fantasy, he had done everything he could to help Tang Xing. He could be considered one of the rare bright spots in this weak team.　　

Gun Fu didn't mean that the Sharpshooter would go up close and start brawling, but it also didn't mean that the Sharpshooter would move too far away from the opponent either. The crux of this playstyle revolved around the four words "having room to maneuver". What exactly this entailed depended on every player's skill level.

Tang Xing's Gun Fu maintained about 5 units from the opponent to freely move around. It was a rather ordinary level for Sharpshooters proficient at this playstyle. He was very far away from a top God like Zhou Zekai, who maintained about 3 units .

One unit was the length of one step taken by a character moving normally, so Gun Fu was usually divided into X Steps. How many steps was the best depended on each player's preference, but those who could use Three Steps Gun Fu could also easily do Five Steps Gun Fu. However, those who could only use Five Steps Gun Fu would find it extremely difficult to do Three Steps Gun Fu. Every step required a faster reaction time and higher technical skill.

Tang Xing had limited talent. After receiving Zhang Yiwei's guidance, he became specialized at Gun Fu. Unfortunately, he could only reach Five Steps and couldn't go past it. There was nothing Zhang Yiwei could do about that. In the past, his Gun Fu had also only reached Four Steps. He couldn't advance any further. He was fully aware of the helplessness of lacking talent, so he couldn't demand Tang Xing to breakthrough to Four Steps. He could only have him continue improving his utilization of Five Steps Gun Fu.　　

Five Steps Gun Fu was more than enough to deal with a rookie like Bao Rongxin.

Tang Xing's Sharpshooter rushed forward and quickly entered a five step radius. Zhang Yiwei nodded his head in satisfaction at Tang Xing's skillful Gun Fu.

Steamed Bun looked somewhat panicked after being ambushed. It looked like he had no plans on resisting. Steamed Bun Invasion stumbled about from Tang Xing's Sharpshooter. Running away seemed to be the only thing on his mind.

Zhang Yiwei laughed loudly. That was too much of a rookie's reaction. He had no idea what to do when caught unprepared. He didn't have the experience to make any subconscious decisions. The only thing he could do was run.

"I truly don't understand why you keep using a player like him again and again." Zhang Yiwei looked towards Ye Xiu.

"What's the problem?" Ye Xiu asked back.

"What the problem? Do I really need to point it out?" Zhang Yiwei saw Steamed Bun Invasion's sorry figure.

"I think the problem is with you. Isn't running away the correct way of dealing with Gun Fu?" Ye Xiu said.

The smile on Zhang Yiwei's face suddenly froze.

Ye Xiu's words were simple, but he understood his meaning. In more professional terminology, running away translated to constantly moving and altering the distance between the two sides.

The crux of Gun Fu was distance. If Tang Xing controlled the distance, Gun Fu's characteristic of freely maneuvering around would be fully utilized, but if he couldn't control the distance, Gun Fu would be disrupted, giving the opponent an opportunity to counter attack.

Steamed Bun Invasion was running and stumbling while being chased by Tang Xing's Sharpshooter. That along with him clearly being a rookie made it difficult to connect it with tactics. After listening to Ye Xiu's words, he looked more carefully. Steamed Bun Invasion was running away like a dog, but he was successfully dodging attack after attack. Because Tang Xing needed to chase his opponent, he was unable to control the distance between them.　

Is he intentionally moving like that? Zhang Yiwei looked left and right. He couldn't help but think it didn't seem to be the case. If it was intentional, why did it need to look so ugly? But then again, this kind of ugliness would very likely lower Tang Xing's guard. From the individual competition, it could be seen that Team Happy's players didn't care about their images at all. They had no intentions of trying to gain the crowd's favor. They used whatever methods they could to win.

For a team like that, pretending to be a fool to make the opponent lower his guard was as easy as pie.

Tang Xing! Don't fall for it! Hurry up and see through it!!

Zhang Yiwei started to worry. He had placed Tang Xing first to establish a psychological advantage because he knew that Team Happy certainly put God Ye Qiu last in the group arena. If the two sides fought evenly in the first two rounds, God Ye Qiu would determine the winner of this group arena. Even if they had their most outstanding player Tang Xing go last, Ye Qiu wouldn't be afraid of him at all.

Thus, he might as well just put Tang Xing first and hopefully have him beat more Team Happy players. That way, they might be able to have their remaining two players face Ye Qiu. Wouldn't a 2v1 give them a psychological advantage?

But now, Tang Xing might fall into a trap. How could he not worry?

"Not good!"

He was roaring at Tang Xing in his heart to notice, fearful of the consequences, but then, an opening appeared in Tang Xing's Gun Fu. Zhang Yiwei, who was also an expert at Gun Fu, and immediately noticed it.

And closely following it, a brick whistled by.

Chapter 976: Steamed Bun’s Vanishing Step

Thwack!

The sound of a brick smashing into a skull was clear and crisp.

This brick was an expected follow-up in the eyes of Ye Xiu, Zhang Yiwei, and other skilled pro players. It was something that should have happened. However, in the eyes of normal players, it was completely unexpected. What they saw was Steamed Bun Invasion being chased all over the map like a cowardly dog. Tang Xing's rhythm had become passive, creating an opening. This was pretty high end, so it wasn't something just anyone could see.

Yet this rookie who was completely unworthy of the pro stage in Zhang Yiwei's eyes not only saw it, but managed to grasp it. It was just that this Brick was as inelegant as always, as if he had only managed to achieve it through pure coincidence.

Was it a coincidence or...

Zhang Yiwei was a little doubtful at first, but that doubt soon disappeared because the Brick was only the beginning. After that, Steamed Bun Invasion, who was originally at a disadvantage, unleashed his counterattack. Brawler skills came one after the other, instantly becoming a combo of skills. Tang Xing's Sharpshooter's health plummeted. The advantage he had obtained through Gun Fu was soon turned around by this wave of counterattacks.

Steady now! Zhang Yiwei secretly wiped away some sweat. Tang Xing wasn't Mysterious Fantasy's captain and the player Zhang Yiwei gave the highest regard to for nothing. He might not have been able to take the counterattacks, but he quickly steadied himself after that. He threw out a grenade and then jumped backwards with the help of an Aerial Fire, hoping to create some distance between them. Who would've expected his opponent to be so fast to prevent this. After avoiding the shockwave from the explosion of the grenade, he charged forth with an attack readied, swiftly tossing a fistful of sand at the other.

Tang Xing turned his view hurriedly. He could take the damage from Sand Toss, but not the blind it would induce. Yet just as his view turned, he heard another thwack of a Brick becoming intimate with his Sharpshooter's head.

So fast?!

Tang Xing was shocked. The Brick had come immediately after the Sand Toss. This was a speed that even Tang Xing could only be ashamed of not having. This seemingly noobish rookie wasn't as simple as he had initially imagined.

With the Brick smacking into the back of his head, it had the priority of an attack from behind and the Sharpshooter immediately entered a dizzy state. Steamed Bun Invasion's next attack quickly followed, an Uppercut launching the Sharpshooter up into the air.

The dizzy state wore off as soon as the attack hit. His character was already airborne, but Tang Xing didn't panic, turning his view and hoping to continue his offense. The aerial combat skill of Gun Fu was very impressive as well, especially if you managed to combine it with Aerial Fire, you could create amazing combos and attacks. Tang Xing wasn't skilled enough for that, but he could add a little into his mechanics every now and then. Yet, turning his view all the way round, he was surprised to realize that he hadn't seen Steamed Bun Invasion at all.

Where was he?

Tang Xing was wondering in surprise, but then took another hit from Steamed Bun Invasion.

The shock he felt from this couldn't compare to his shock at getting hit by a few Bricks.

He was here, but unseen. This technique… this was the legendary Vanishing Step. Even in the pro circle, this was a skill at the cream of the crop and very few could master it. Yet now, a rookie, a rookie that often made rookie mistakes no less, was somehow able to use such a high end technique?

Tang Xing was dumbstruck. Zhang Yiwei, in the audience, was also dumbstruck.

Spectators often wouldn't be able to tell when Vanishing Step was being used. However, Zhang Yiwei had experience and judgement, and he was also very familiar with Tang Xing. Seeing Tang Xing's Sharpshooter look around, he had been silently praising the other for being so calm in such a disadvantageous situation, but then he realized that after turning his view, Tang Xing's Sharpshooter didn't take any action and seemed to have no intentions of attacking Steamed Bun Invasion.

Zhang Yiwei immediately managed to figure out that it wasn't that Tang Xing missed the opportunity, but that he had none in the first place. After turning his view around, he never found Steamed Bun Invasion.

Then what could it be? Obviously Vanishing Step.

Alighting on this thought, Zhang Yiwei forgot to close his gaping mouth. He subconsciously glanced at Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu's smile looked very enigmatic.

　

So Happy really would do anything for victory, huh?

Even an expert who could accomplish the high end technique Vanishing Step was pretending to be a complete noob. What couldn't they do?

Pretending to be a swine to eat a tiger*! Zhang Yiwei's head was filled with this phrase. His mental representation of Steamed Bun Invasion became more and more towering. What was this person's true strength? His original research and understanding seemed to be completely wrong; what should he do?

Zhang Yiwei was extremely anxious, but even if he thought of something now, what could he do? He couldn't communicate with the in-match Tang Xing. Once the match started, everything relied on the player.

Tang Xing was obviously also caught completely off guard by this Vanishing Step, getting beaten to the ground by a round of combos from Steamed Bun Invasion, even taking two sweeps. Tang Xing had even forgotten how to use the basic Quick Recover.

Zhang Yiwei's mood fell further. However, he didn't blame Tang Xing. This unimaginable strength of Bao Rongxing's was something completely out of their expectations. Going up against an expert that had mastered Vanishing Step was a bit too much for Tang Xing.

However, Tang Xing soon steadied himself.

His stupor just now was because of surprise. He was already used to being intimidated. Mysterious Fantasy was a weak team and he was a player with limited skill. In his two years with Mysterious Fantasy, he had been continuously engaging with players whose strength was beyond his. This was the story of Tang Xing's pro career.

He was very experienced with fighting stronger opponents. What this experience gave him, was mostly calm in facing such perilous situations. If he really could use this to win, then he wouldn't be such a weak player.

Seeing Tang Xing steady himself again, Zhang Yiwei sighed. He knew that this was something brought to Tang Xing by Mysterious Fantasy's situation in the Alliance. However, after he sighed, his eyes lit up.

The calm that Tang Xing had when going up against experts allowed him to occasionally grasp some opportunities, especially those who were proud and underestimated their opponents, or the young and inexperienced.

Bao Rongxing being proud and underestimating them? Of course he hadn't. To win against them, he didn't care about how inelegant he had to be, was there any pride in that? As for inexperienced, this newbie who had barely experienced any pro matches had pretty much no experience. The experience from PKing in the arena was completely different from pro match experience.

Bao Rongxing was a player that Tang Xing could win against! Seeing Tang Xing calm down and engage the other again, Zhang Yiwei suddenly found a new hope, staring at the match intently.

An opening!

　

Zhang Yiwei's eyes lit up, but it seemed as if Tang Xing hadn't seen it and the opportunity passed.

Zhang Yiwei shook his head and sat up straight. Yet it hadn't been five seconds before his heart leaped again.

　

Another opening!

　

Yet Tang Xing still wasn't taking advantage of this opening. Or rather, he didn't even try.

What on earth?

Zhang Yiwei couldn't understand. The first opening came and went quickly, so it was normal that Tang Xing wouldn't be able to grasp it. However, the second opening was a big one; there was no reason that Tang Xing wouldn't be able to use it.

Could it be...

Zhang Yiwei glanced at Ye Xiu on Happy's side. This guy still had the same smile on his face as before.

　

Those two openings were traps!

　

Zhang Yiwei felt enlightened. Pro matches were always like this, full of feints and traps. Everyone was trying to find openings, but had to be careful that the opening they found wasn't actually bait. Realizing that Bao Rongxing wasn't a simple character, then what else could those mistakes be? Did this even need an explanation?

Tang Xing was doing the right thing; he had to maintain this calm. Zhang Yiwei nodded in approval.

Thus, the calm Tang Xing continued to stall with Steamed Bun, not daring to be impatient and waiting for a better chance to turn the tables.

There was a song that was appropriate for the current situation: Waiting and seeing, fading away quietly.

Tang Xing's Sharpshooter's health began to fade quietly, just like that. This was because he never managed to find "a better chance to turn the tables". The openings that his opponent gave all seemed fake to him, like there was a label "trap" pasted on it. In addition, he, who had positioned himself in the place of the weaker player in his mind, gave up on attacking directly, and instead went on the defensive, making sure he was as safe and secure as possible. Defending and counter attacking was the usual strategy of the weak.

Unfortunately, this time, his strategy wasn't very appropriate. No matter if it was him or Zhang Yiwei, they had both deeply misunderstood Steamed Bun. What sort of player was he, really? Their understanding was continuously changing.

Currently Tang Xing thought that Steamed Bun was an expert, so he went on the defensive, immediately receiving a round of vicious smacks from Steamed Bun Invasion. Steamed Bun was having so much fun smacking him that his attacks became full of openings. Yet Tang Xing, over here, shook his head telling himself no, these aren't openings. Such ridiculous openings had to be traps.

He continued to wait and see. Disregarding his slowly fading health, he himself ended up desolate and heartbroken as well.

Zhang Yiwei was much more experienced than Tang Xing, understanding what was happening after watching for a while.

This Bao Rongxing was actually like they had originally thought!

He wasn't pretending or anything. Upon being ambushed by Gun Fu, something he couldn't deal with, he ran. While running, he found an opening, so he counterattacked. His counterattack hit, so he made a follow up combo. This was something every player of Glory should be able to do. As for that Vanishing Step, it might really have been a coincidence that he moved into Tang Xing's blindspot with a step.

Then all the openings now were real?

So seeing that Tang Xing was letting all these opportunities slip away, Zhang Yiwei was anxious to the point where he wanted to stomp his feet. He hoped that Tang Xing could quickly figure out what was happening. However, Tang Xing's mind was set this time. In the end, he never found the "opening" he wanted and was wiped out by Steamed Bun Invasion. When he came down from the stage, his was still wearing a perplexed expression. He felt exactly how he felt against the experts and gods he had faced in the past. Though he had lost, he had done all he could.

Zhang Yiwei wanted to cry. This was no expert! He really was just a rookie!

Chapter 977: Main Target

Seeing Tang Xing standing calmly in front of him, Zhang Yiwei didn't know what to say. In the end, he could only let loose a deep sigh.

"What?" Tang Xing still hadn't comprehended what had just happened.

"You worry too much." Zhang Yiwei shook his head. He didn't mention how he had been worried too. However, he soon realized it.

"That guy really is a rookie. You placed too much importance on him." Zhang Yiwei pointed to the stage.

"Ah?" Tang Xing was astonished, "But….."

Zhang Yiwei laughed bitterly and shook his head. He knew what Tang Xing wanted to say.

"Sit down and just keep watching!" Zhang Yiwei said to Tang Xing. Then, he told the second player, who would be going on stage: "Be aggressive. Punish him for his mistakes."

Tang Xing sat in a daze on the side. He saw his teammate walk onto the stage and fight with Bao Rongxing. He launched an aggressive offense at the very start and won with just a sliver of health left.

Tang Xing glanced at his coach in bewilderment. He didn't know what Zhang Yiwei wanted him to see.　

Zhang Yiwei's face was ashen. If the player coming down from the stage had been his player, he would have given him a fierce scolding. You went in at full health to fight someone at half heath, yet you almost died. That performance had been too trashy. As for Team Happy's Bao Rongxing, Zhang Yiwei was also puzzled. This time, he wasn't full of holes like he had been in the previous match. When he fought against this Team Mysterious Fantasy player, he would sometimes make a sudden move, which even an experienced veteran like Zhang Yiwei couldn't comprehend at all.

Has this Bao Rongxing reached a level so high that even I can't understand it? Zhang Yiwei noticed Tang Xing's confused gaze, but he really couldn't give him an explanation at this moment either. This Bao Rongxing had completely befuddled him.

Next up for Team Happy was Tang Rou. She quickly and easily cleaned up that nearly-dead Team Mysterious Fantasy player. This player came down stage dejectedly. Zhang Yiwei wasn't able to scold him for his trash performance. Their third player stood in front of him with fear, waiting for guidance!

How could he not feel afraid?

He originally thought that they would face God Ye Qiu with a numbers advantage and build a psychological advantage, but everything was reversed right now. The other side still had God Ye Qiu leisurely sitting there! On stage, there was still a practically full health Soft Mist. Let alone God Ye Qiu, Tang Rou wasn't a player to be taken lightly. Battle Mage and Ye Qiu's teammate. Those two phrases f*cking put together were terrifying enough. Then, there was Tang Rou herself. Her technical skill was impressive, and her fighting spirit was inextinguishable. Just these two points made her a headache to play against. And she was also super beautiful? Don't think that such a stat had no effect during a match. When facing a hot girl, players would sometimes have a mentality that they shouldn't have in a match like holding back, showing off, teasing, etc. All of these could lead to a tip of the scales.

And even if this player could beat her, he would have to face God Ye Qiu next. Towards this player, Zhang Yiwei couldn't say anything but "Good luck." Did you not hear what Tang Rou said to Team Happy when she was about to go up? She asked Ye Xiu: do you need to warm up…...

Ye Xiu just laughed. He didn't reply to her question. As a result, Tang Rou didn't give him an opportunity and killed her nearly-dead opponent without fooling around. Not only was Team Mysterious Fantasy able to build any sort of psychological advantage, the confidence of these two formidable opponents caused their third player to utterly collapse.

The group arena ended shortly afterwards. Team Happy only needed two players to beat all of Team Mysterious Fantasy's players. After this round, Team Happy had won all five points. The situation had now become a you-die-or-I-die scenario. The outcome of the following team competition wouldn't only decide the winner of this match, but who would make it out of groups. At this point, it was impossible for Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy to both make it out. The loser of this team competition would have their journey cut short.

The notion spreading around before the match of how Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy would have a tacit agreement to send Team Trader out of groups had now been completely dispelled. But then again, in this group with five teams, one team would have no opponent to play against every round, so it was easy for a hole to appear. For example, in this round, if Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy really did make a tacit agreement before, there was nothing Team Trader could do.

It didn't happen in the end. Both teams were fighting to the death, but at this point, Team Happy's psychological advantage over Team Mysterious Fantasy was quite obvious.

The team competition had been the section of the match that they needed to win from the very start. They had mentally prepared themselves for this a long time ago. However, Team Mysterious Fantasy thought that they could end this battle in the individual competition or group arena, yet the life of death match had dragged onto the team competition. It wasn't like they hadn't considered the possibility of this development, but there was no way they would be as certain as Team Happy. The pressure on them suddenly multiplied. The entire team was quiet. Even Zhang Yiwei couldn't squeeze out a smile. In the end, he also thought that their defeat was imminent.

But he knew that he was the pillar of their team. At this moment, he could not collapse no matter what. Even if he was only pretending, he had to show his unwaverable confidence in the team.

Zhang Yiwei looked at everyone in Team Mysterious Fantasy one by one. He noted everyone's expression. He didn't immediately say anything. Encouragement needed to be done at the right time. The situation and the words mattered. Zhang Yiwei had been a coach for two years and was quite proficient at his job.

He gave the players some time. After digesting their current situation, Zhang Yiwei clapped to get everyone's attention. Then, he began admonishing them: "Did we already lose? How come I seem to remember that there's still five points waiting to be taken?"

"We didn't perform as well as expected in the individual competitions, but that doesn't mean we need to be discouraged. Next up, it's time for us to show our team's strength. Do I need to repeat what our advantages are? We are Team Mysterious Fantasy. We've always been challenging opponents far greater than ourselves, but when did we ever fear them? Everyone has been too relaxed because of the Challenger League. Have you guys forgotten about the courage that you've always had? That's perfect then. It's time to summon up that courage. Happy is very strong? What about Excellent Era? Such a powerful opponent is waiting for us in the later stages. If we get discouraged, how are we going to challenge Excellent Era? How are we going to make it back to the Alliance?

"We can lose, but no team can scare us. We came here to challenge Excellent Era. We're not even scared of Excellent Era. So does Happy count for anything? Forget about those previous losses. The match has only just begun. Focus. Go on stage and beat Happy."

"YES!!" The players in Team Mysterious Fantasy heard Zhang Yiwei's speech and their spirits instantly surged. These players were about to go on stage. Under their captain Tang Xing's lead, they lay in wait.

"I hope you guys haven't forgotten our arrangements for the team competition." Zhang Yiwei said.

"Of course." The team competition players nodded their heads. They looked towards Happy at Happy's Cleric, An Wenyi. For Team Mysterious Fantasy, he was their target. The experienced Zhang Yiwei saw through the weaknesses in An Wenyi, so he formulated a strategy targeting their healer.

"Players on both sides, get ready to go on stage." When it was about time, the referee called out to the players.

"Go! Beat them." Zhang Yiwei and the other players, who wouldn't be going up, cheered on their six players. On Team Happy's side, Ye Xiu personally led the team onto the stage. He heard Zhang Yiwei's shout and even turned his head to smile at him.　

Zhan Wenyi was thinking about some way to respond to Ye Xiu's smile, when his six players turned their heads to look at him. They were in utter disbelief.

　

What's wrong? Zhang Yiwei didn't know what had happened. He saw the six turn around and followed their gazes…...　

An Wenyi was still sitting in Team Happy's seats.

This... Zhang Yiwei was shocked. He hastily turned to look at Happy's players. One, two, three, four, five, six. Six? Yes, six. Zhang Yiwei counted again and confirmed it. Team Happy had sent out six players in this team competition, but they actually weren't bringing a healer?

The team competition hadn't even begun yet, but just looking at the players sent out, Zhang Yiwei was already dumbstruck. It was only until the players next to him called out to him did he wake up. He saw that the referee was urging the six players to hurry up and go on stage. They were currently walking slowly onto the stage stalling for time. They turned their heads every three steps, looking hopefully at him.

An Wenyi wouldn't actually be playing in the team competition. Their original plan had been completely messed up. They were hoping that their coach would hurry and give them some sort of instruction.

Zhang Yiwei understood. He wasn't allowed to say much right now though. He could only point towards Happy and say: "Steamed Bun."　　

The six players heard his words and nodded their heads. Steamed Bun... that was obviously Steamed Bun Invasion.

The two sides went to their respective seats. They swiped their cards and logged into the game. When they entered the competition interface, the six players saw the other side's arrangements and suddenly wanted to cry. An Wenyi had been their main target, but An Wenyi didn't go on stage. Steamed Bun became their new target, but the other side put Steamed Bun as their sixth player. At this point, they couldn't look for their coach for any guidance anymore. For a moment, the six players didn't know what to do.

Zhang Yiwei saw the display from the stream and also froze. He could already figure out what his six players on stage were thinking, but there was nothing they could do because there were still no rules in the Alliance regarding coaches. According to the rules, his usage as a coach in a match was very limited. He could only study the opponents and make some arrangements before the match. As soon as the match started, the players could only rely on themselves. In the current Glory competitive scene, coaches changing their planned strategy right before the match wasn't a thing, so when an unexpected situation occurred, Zhang Yiwei could only feel powerless. As a result, he usually made a few backup plans, but this time, he could never have imagined that the other side would play the team competition without a healer.

Chapter 978: Flimsy Tactics

"Hello friends, let's return back to the stage. Happy versus Mysterious Fantasy. This match will determine who will be eliminated during this knockout tournament. On the screen now is a list of the players who will be going on stage from Team Happy. Looking at this list, I'm sure those who have been paying attention to Team Happy must have realized something." After the ad break, the broadcast returned to the competition stage, and the commentator incessantly started talking.

"Yes, Happy's team composition doesn't have a healer. What a bold move! To dare to make such a move in a life and death battle, we have no choice but to recognize Happy's courage. I think this arrangement is surely a huge surprise to Mysterious Fantasy. I hope that their plans won't be thrown into disorder because of this!" It wasn't good for the commentator to be biased towards one side, so after admiring Happy, he gave his blessings to Mysterious Fantasy to make up for it. Unfortunately, the commentator's remark was spot on. Team Mysterious Fantasy's plans had been completely thrown into disarray because of Team Happy's surprise move.

After the five second countdown, the battle began.

Zhang Yiwei didn't want to look at the screen. Happy's unexpected team composition had disrupted his arrangements. As a result, his value as a coach couldn't be shown in this team competition. Everything depended on the players on-stage to resolve.

And for Team Mysterious Fantasy, without the guidance from their coach, they had undoubtedly lost their main pillar of support. When the battle began, Team Happy's five leading players rushed towards Team Mysterious Fantasy's location like wolves. The players on Team Mysterious Fantasy still hadn't moved yet. They were currently discussing what to do in the team chat.

An Wenyi's Little Cold Hands wasn't there. Steamed Bun Invasion wasn't there either. Who should they target among Team Happy's five players?

Ye Xiu, Sun Zheping, Wei Chen?

Even if these three were Gods of the past, they were still towering mountains compared to them.

Qiao Yifan. He had come from Team Tiny Herb. Even though he didn't seem to have made any accomplishments in Team Tiny Herb, just being accepted into Team Tiny Herb made him appear more precious than them. Being a part of Team Mysterious Fantasy truly meant that they were the bottom rung of the pro scene. Getting noticed by a top team like Team Tiny Herb was only a dream to them.

Besides these four, there was only Tang Rou left.

She was an extremely beautiful girl. They had cast their glances on her not just a few times off stage, but right now, in this life and death battle, they placed their attitudes towards beauties aside. Even though Tang Rou wasn't someone easily provoked, compared to those four, her background seemed the least impressive, no? If you had to pick a persimmon, pick a soft one. Tang Rou was soon recognized as their new main target.

Afterwards, the Team Mysterious Fantasy players finally shifted into formation. After confirming their target, it wasn't hard to execute their practiced tactics.

Zhang Yiwei saw his players begin to move. Every character was methodically arranged. It looked like they had a clear plan in mind.

What were they planning on doing? Zhang Yiwei could no longer remain calm. He anxiously stood up, staring at the screen.

The players on both sides began their first exchange. Team Happy was in an X formation. Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep and Tang Rou's Soft Mist stood at the front. Wei Chen's Windward Formation and Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash stood at the back. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was positioned in the middle. It was a very ordinary and unsurprising formation.

After Team Mysterious Fantasy saw Team Happy's formation, they quickly adjusted their formation. They shifted towards their main target, Soft Mist. Their captain, Tang Xin, quickly spoke in the team channel: "Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire! Heroic Leap to split them apart. Cloud Grasping Fist to grab her!"

Team Mysterious Fantasy's first five players consisted of a Sharpshooter, Elementalist, Knight, Qi Master, and Paladin.

Two long-ranged offensive classes, one mid-ranged class, one close-ranged defensive Knight, and one healer and defensive Paladin. The cautiousness of a weak team was completely revealed by their team composition. This team composition didn't have much close-combat ability. It was clearly because Team Mysterious Fantasy didn't dare to directly confront other teams. Because of this, they needed to use other methods to obtain victory.

After their captain finished giving out instructions, the five Mysterious Fantasy players rushed towards Happy. They took the initiative and launched the first attack.

"Too impatient!" Zhang Yiwei stomped his feet in worry. He had brought this team up with his own hands. As soon as he saw their formation, he could already see through their intentions. However, attacking first wasn't their Team Mysterious Fantasy's strength. What's more, their team composition didn't have powerful surprise attack capabilities.

It had to be said that the strength of Team Mysterious Fantasy's players was limited. In terms of tactics, because of the existence of their coach Zhang Yiwei, the players were used to listening to his orders. Their ability to create their own strategies became even weaker. The thinking behind their plan had some clear problems. How could such crude tactics not be cleaned up by Team Happy? Team Happy had Ye Xiu, the most senior of the Four Master Tacticians. Numerous Glory tactics had been invented by him. Zhang Yiwei himself didn't dare to say he was more capable at tactics than Ye Xiu. Right now, these Team Mysterious Fantasy players, who were used to relying on someone else's tactics, went up to battle against Ye Xiu. A dull gray once again consumed Zhang Yiwei's heart.

But Team Mysterious Fantasy's players couldn't feel their coach's current emotions. They had already started their attacks. The Elementalist cast a Heavenly Lightning Earthen Fire. The Knight used Heroic Leap, directly splitting the line between Soft Mist and Lord Grim to separate Soft Mist from the rest of her allies.

Bang!

A gunshot sounded. Mysterious Fantasy's Elementalist hadn't noticed at all. Lord Grim's attack forced him to cancel his spell cast. The Knight had already rushed forward with Heroic Leap, but while he was still in the air, he was suspended where he was.　　

Soft Mist's spear was raised high in the air, stabbing him and making him appear like a piece of clothing hung out to dry.　　

That was just the visual impression in that instant. Circle Swing didn't give any time to pose for a picture. As soon as the spear struck him, he was flung down without any delay. At this moment, Mysterious Fantasy's Qi Master had successfully executed Cloud Grasping Fist and dragged her towards their Knight. The others weren't able to protect her. This grab struck, and Soft Mist was dragged over. The Knight pierced by her spear, as well as the remaining arc of the Circle Swing, were pulled over to the Qi Master as well. The Qi Master crashed into the ground, struck by his own allied Knight, who had been smashed down by Circle Swing.

The crowd erupted with laughter. That scene was too funny! The Qi Master using Cloud Grasping Fist reaped what he had sown.

In the first exchange alone, two players from Team Mysterious Fantasy had been knocked into the ground. Their opening move was going extremely poorly. Tang Rou's Soft Mist was full of life though. She didn't panic after being pulled into the enemy ranks by Cloud Grasping First. Instead, she took the opportunity to attack. The two on the ground hadn't gotten up yet, and the Sharpshooter and Paladin were already being forced back by her. They had originally planned on grabbing Soft Mist and killing her, but after she was grabbed, they were the ones being forced into helplessness. Team Mysterious Fantasy's first wave of attacks looked very embarrassing.

Tang Xin's Sharpshooter stepped back five steps. It was the distance that he was most familiar with. Following afterwards, he was just about to unleash his Gun Fu, when a Hexagram Prison suddenly erupted from the ground. Tang Xin hastily jumped out of the way in fright. Windward Formation's Hexagram Prison had been avoided, but Lord Grim's Anti-Tank Missiles were still flying towards him. Tang Xin wanted to dodge again, but Soft Mist had already reached him.

Not only was their target Soft Mist not beaten black and blue, she became the dagger that was lodged in the chink of their armor. At this moment, Tang Xin deeply felt like his plans had been terrible. The other side took advantage of it and turned the tides in their favor.

　

Tang Xin's Sharpshooter was pressed on both sides and had no path for retreat. Fortunately, he had teammates to help him. The Knight got back up and rushed over with a Shield Strike. Soft Mist had no choice but to dodge it. The Qi Master punched and sent a Dragon Wave flying over.

But then, he saw a figure descending from the sky. Another Summer of Sleep had landed with a Collapsing Mountain. His body ate the Dragon Wave, and his sword slashed fiercely towards the Knight.

The Knight raised his shield to block it, and a loud muffled sound erupted. While making his declaration, another fierce character from Team Happy had approached. Sun Zheping's experience was far richer than Tang Rou's. Compared to Tang Rou, he knew more clearly how to make things difficult for Team Mysterious Fantasy. His first strike was blocked by the shield. He didn't mind. He began ferociously slamming down on the Knight's shield, forcing the Knight to take step after step backwards. The shield could greatly reduce knockback effects. However, it couldn't completely resist Sun Zheping's frenzy. The knockback from skillfully linked attacks, forcibly broke through what the shield could take. The Knight continued to be forced back, giving Soft Mist a new path to maneuver around in. With a Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Soft Mist sent the Qi Master flying far away.

Tang Rou didn't have her Soft Mist chase after him. She turned around and began attacking the Knight, along with Sun Zheping.

That Knight was unable to get away from Sun Zheping. He could only watch helplessly as Soft Mist attacked. He could only hope that his teammates could break through and rescue him. However, when he turned his head to look, their Elementalist was jumping like a rabbit under Lord Grim's gunfire, and their team's Sharpshooter was being suppressed by Windward Formation's long-ranged curses. Their Sharpshooter wouldn't be able to escape for awhile. Warlock attacks weren't as simple as just damage. Many of their skills were catered towards control. As for their Qi Master, he was still trying to get up after being sent flying away by Soft Mist's Dragon Break the Ranks! As for their Paladin? Oh, their Paladin was still there. Furthermore, Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist were pushing him towards his own Paladin! This... they wanted to get rid of both him and the Paladin all at once!

Chapter 979: The Greatest Weakness

Happy's playstyle surprised even the coach, Zhang Yiwei, let alone the Mysterious Fantasy players on stage. They dared to fight openly like this without even bringing a healer? What kind of arrogance and confidence was this?

However, when they saw characters Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist push their Knight towards their Paladin, Zhang Yiwei reacted at once. Happy still had a strategic target; their first target was still the healer. This was a very traditional, standard, and unsurprising fighting style. However, by spreading out, scattering Mysterious Fantasy's formation, and then switching targets, the thought process behind their tactics were much more elaborate and ambiguous. In comparison, the way that Team Mysterious Fantasy's characters started to cut in by throwing three skills at Soft Mist was straightforward, rough, and crude.

Happy's fighting style was rich in variation, so when their true intentions were revealed, it was very likely that it was already too late for the opponent to stop them. This match was exactly like that. Mysterious Fantasy's Knight served as Happy's tactical cover. After pushing him for some distance, Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist immediately ditched him. They rushed towards the Paladin, who was not far from the Knight, in unison.

Mysterious Fantasy's Paladin had been actively healing the entire team. The Knight became his main target, after being pincered between two people. However, the two characters that had been pincer-attacking the Knight in the previous second had now turned the points of their weapons towards him.

The Paladin obviously wouldn't stand still to fight back and resist head-on. However, when he turned around, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had managed to sneak behind him. He didn't know when that had happened. An Ice Boundary was cast and it trapped the Paladin within it. Smaller boundaries were connected by larger boundaries. While the Paladin was suppressed, Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist arrived and started their wave of attacks.

The Paladin had nowhere to go, so he could only use his skills head-on. First, he used a Holy Shield Technique to protect him from the front, then a Life Activation to immediately recover some of his health. This was followed by Angel's Might, which put the Paladin at the center as a ray of light stretched out in 360 degrees, so it not only delivered damage to targets within the lit area, but it would also create a strong knockback effect, which allowed him to be immune to knock downs.

Neither Sun Zheping nor Tang Rou's classes had no way of negating Angel's Might's knockback effect, but both of them did their best. Although Angel's Might had a knock back effect, but as an interrupt skill, it would only be effective towards skills that required the user to be immobile while casting. In comparison to other interrupt skills, it was fairly inferior when compared to the types of grabs.

Another Summer of Sleep wasn't able to stop himself from sliding back. He carried his Greatsword on his back, and his surroundings turned red. The Greatsword boiled like blood, as it continued to swell and get bigger. When his sword was drawn down, the blood erupted and cloud of bloody mist immediately spread out. This was the big, Level 70 skill of the Berserker: Crimson Storm.

As for Soft Mist, her spear transformed into a dragon when she swung it. Although she was retreating, her transformed spear's magical battle aura surged ahead. Its blast managed to strike the Paladin.

Although Angel's Might managed to force Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist back, it couldn't avoid either of the two's big moves. The summoned Holy Shield Technique couldn't resist the two skills at all. The shield was blasted to bits, and the erupting, boiling red color of the magical battle aura completely swallowed up the poor Paladin in an instant.

After Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash was finished with his support as a Phantom Demon, he didn't stand around and do nothing. He attacked with his katana to help dish out damage.

"Too fierce. Happy's response is truly fierce. We need to remember that they didn't bring a healer. When faced with the Paladin's Angel's Might, they continued to deal damage despite having to bear the damage taken." The broadcast commentator exclaimed unstoppingly.

"This Mysterious Fantasy player is in danger. He's in between Happy's pincer attacks, so he can only pray for his teammates to arrive quickly to save him. Now, where are his teammates?"

The broadcast screen switched to the other members of Mysterious Fantasy. The Knight had been heavily targeted by Another Summer of Sleep and Soft Mist, but now it was his turn to proactively intercept the two. The Qi Master, who had been blasted away, was now rushing forward. Since he had mid-ranged attacks, he punched out a Sky Piercing Strike towards Soft Mist and Another Summer of Sleep.

However, with a flicker, Another Summer of Sleep circled around to Soft Mist's front. He used his body to take on Qi Master's Sky Piercing Strike. Soft Mist wasn't interrupted by the attack, so she continued to attack the Paladin furiously.

The Paladin's Angel's Might wasn't able to turn the tides. After giving himself two instant and strong heals , he used Firm Will to boost his defence. He then spun his view around in an attempt to see if any of his teammates could quickly come to his rescue.

Unfortunately, before he could wait for his teammate's attacks to arrive, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim and Wei Chen's Windward Formation had found some openings to throw some skills his way. The Paladin could only rely on his class' powerful defense to stay alive. Finally, the Knight from his team rushed to his side and activated Holy Punishment. Tang Rou's Soft Mist had to avoid it. The moment she moved aside, Sun Zheping appeared with his greatsword and parried the Holy Punishment head on.

"Using an attack to parry Holy Punishment!!!" The broadcast commentator uttered in disbelief. Luckily, the audience could only hear his voice, and not see his face. Holy Punishment's attacking rhythm was controlled by the controller, so it didn't have a set rhythm. In addition, its damage could layer on top of another and increase. The commentator didn't know whether using an attack to parry such a skill was courageous or insane.

The clanging of weapons between the two characters rang incessantly. Mysterious Fantasy's Knight couldn't really believe what was happening. Someone actually dared to use pure technical skill to take on Holy Punishment. Was he... being looked down on?

Even a clay person had a bit of temper*. Such an abnormal scene was happening to him. His self-esteem took a lot of damage. He started to focus on Holy Punishment while disregarding everything else. All in all, it was difficult to hold back Holy Punishment with just technical skill in the first place. After Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep had parried for a bit, he couldn't keep it up after the opponent increased his speed. Normal attacks couldn't parry Holy Punishment, so he had to counter it with skills. However, all skills would have a cooldown time, so while Holy Punishment wouldn't have this problem, Another Summer of Sleep eventually used up all of his skills. When he could only use normal attacks to counter it, Mysterious Fantasy's Knight felt really at ease, and attacked again and again. The numerous consecutive attacks pushed Another Summer of Sleep to the point that Another Summer of Sleep couldn't hold on any longer.

"You idiot! Watch where you are going!!!" However, the Knight's oppressive attacks towards Sun Zheping angered Zhang Yiwei to the point that he cursed out loud. The Knight furiously pursued Another Summer of Sleep with attacks, and gave up the chance to protect the Paladin, who was left there by himself. What other possibilities were there, for an exposed healer, except to get beaten up?

The broadcast followed the Knight's crazy Holy Punishment, but the position he had left was even more exciting. Soft Mist's battle spear turned and stabbed fiercely towards the Paladin. Although Mysterious Fantasy's Qi Master picked out a chance to do something, it wasn't a class that specialized in fighting at close distances. The advantage in mid-range attacks and support couldn't save the Paladin. In Mysterious Fantasy, the one that had the best chance in saving the healer was the Knight, but this guy had been led away by Sun Zheping's forceful response.

When the broadcast switched back to this scene, the commentator suddenly came to realise the truth. Amid the courageousness in Sun Zheping's attacks, there was also a devious trick!

The Knight player only managed to realize what happened after the Holy Punishment had finished. He hurriedly tried to turn back to save the healer, but how could Sun Zheping let him off the hook so easily? He pursued the Knight with a chain of wild slashes. All the advantages he gained from the Holy Punishment was taken away after a few attacks. They had a healer with them, so theoretically, exchanging blood shouldn't be a disadvantage. However, the problem was that they were about to lose their healer.

Lord Grim and Windward Formation on the other side exchanged positions. Under the coverage of Lord Grim, Windward Formation managed to summon Death's Door.

Players who wanted to step ahead had to consider again. Being captured by Death's Door couldn't be countered by mere controls. At least, low-ranked pro players in the league like the ones in Mysterious Fantasy didn't have this confidence. The crucial issue of saving the healer was changed into breaking Death's Door. Since Death's Door's caster was under the coverage of Lord Grim, members of Mysterious Fantasy all switched their firepower that way.

Zhang Yiwei once again sighed. He couldn't even curse. It could clearly be seen just how little hope he had left. Happy was leading his team by the nose. The disparity between the two teams in terms of tactics already put in Zhang Yiwei in despair. In his heart, he faintly felt like even if Happy hadn't come out with something unexpected leading to his plans being ruined, even if his tactical arrangement had been in place, the other side had Ye Xiu leading Team Happy, while he himself was off stage unable to do anything. Team Mysterious Fantasy would have fallen either way.

He continued to look for holes in Team Happy. Sometimes it was because the healing wasn't enough. Sometimes it was because Steamed Bun was a novice. However, Team Mysterious Fantasy's biggest weakness had been grasped by the other side.

Coach…...

For Team Mysterious Fantasy, their wins were because of the coach; their losses were also because of the coach. Because of the difficulty in coordinating with the team, the effectiveness in coaching was limited. Mid-match, the coach's plans might fail. It was also possible that unexpected things could lead to changes in the situation. In a normal team, the team captain would make immediately adjustments. However, Team Mysterious Fantasy depended on their coach. Their tactics would immediately crash down. Their defeat was simply logical.

Zhang Yiwei, who had been uneasy and nervous the entire time, calmed down at this moment. He already knew what the results would be. No matter if the outcome was good or bad, it at least gave him a peace of mind. Team Mysterious Fantasy's journey stopped here.

Zhang Yiwei was upset. If he hadn't overthought things, if they had won one more point than Team Trader, if they had maintained a qualifying spot the entire time. Unfortunately, it was all too late. Team Mysterious Fantasy would be eliminated.

Chapter 980: New Competitive Format

Glory!

When the team competition was replaced by this massive word, Zhang Yiwei had completely collapsed on his seat.

Although he had seen the lack of initiative Mysterious Fantasy had during the team competition and guessed the results, with the match still ongoing, he still bore hope for a miracle in his heart. It was only until now that Zhang Yiwei's hopes finally turned to ashes.

Excellent Era was in this season's Challenger League, which was quite the blow for those who wanted to return to the Pro League. In truth, Mysterious Fantasy had long since been prepared for an extra year in the Challenger League. Now, however, they had been eliminated without even meeting Excellent Era. That was inexcusable. Zhang Yiwei was the true core of Team Mysterious Fantasy. In successes, he contributed the most; in failures, he couldn't escape the responsibility; and this match had completely revealed to him how little control coaches like him had over the situation under the current rules. Zhang Yiwei felt that his future was even bleaker than Mysterious Fantasy's.

The players of both teams came down from the stage one by one. Mysterious Fantasy's players gathered around of their own volition, yet their coach didn't say a word sitting there so silently, it was scary. They didn't dare make any noise either, just standing there with their heads bowed, quietly waiting. Yet, next to them, laughter and celebration filled Happy's player stands.

　　

At the same time, in the audience, the few Happy fans as well as the Ye Qiu fans were cheering in excitement. In the media seating area, Chang Xian was almost jumping in joy.

"They won! Happy won, Brother Cao!!" There were quite a few reporters around them so Chang Xian stayed discrete, simply pulling on Cao Guangcheng, who sat next to him, and sharing his joy.

"Heh, not bad." Cao Guangcheng squeezed out a smile. He was surprised that Happy had really managed to obtain such a one-sided victory and guarantee Mysterious Fantasy's elimination. Could this Happy really pose a threat to Excellent Era?

Cao Guangcheng couldn't help the anxiety in his heart. However, looking at his fellow reporters, he found that they were rather happy that Happy was advancing to the next round. It was just that they were happy for a different reason. Chang Xian was happy because he had feelings for Happy and hoped that this team could do better and walk further. As for the other reporters, they were hoping for a drama-filled clash between Ye Qiu and Excellent Era so none of them wanted Happy to be eliminated too early.

"10 to 0, Happy eventually defeated Mysterious Fantasy with such a huge lead. This result was probably very unexpected to most people, right? However, you have to admit that this is an appropriate conclusion to this round. Team Happy is the biggest surprise of the season for the Challenger League, and two ex-pro teams have already fell to them. Who knows what other surprises they'll bring us in the following events? Let us wait and see!" The commentator for the broadcast was finishing up on his commentary for the match. The other seven matches had either already finished or were nearing their end.

The final rankings of each group would be decided today and on the electronic screen, facing four different directions, the rankings for each group was show on each on. Those groups that still had a chance were at their most nervous, but this had nothing to do with Mysterious Fantasy anymore. After standing around and staring at their coach for a while, they finally heard their coach speak.

"Let's go!"

　

Zhang Yiwei stood, calmly calling his team over.

Admonishment? That would do nothing now. Encouragement? That could wait until after he secured his own future! They hadn't even advanced past the group matches. Zhang Yiwei was very clear that this wouldn't satisfy their boss. Especially since this match had exposed a lot of problems. There was a big question mark on if he could still stand with these team members in Team Mysterious Fantasy.

Team Mysterious Fantasy left silently like that and not many people noticed the departure of these failures. The audience was all watching the remaining matches while keeping an eye on the rankings. Group B was the first group to settle on its advancing teams. Happy was first and Trader was second.

The second group was Group D. Excellent Era's first place in this group had been set in stone from the beginning and ended up with a full 40 points, showing off Excellent Era's absolute advantage in the Challenger League. Everyone in this group could only hope for second. As the last two matches ended, Group D's second advancing team was decided, a team called The Limit of Heat.

　

The third group that had its advancing teams decided was Group A. Jade Dynasty obtained first with a small lead and the second team was one called Scorching Fields.

And this team, according to the rules of the Challenger League, would be Happy's next opponent.

Group C's matches still hadn't finished, but not many people cared. Their half had Excellent Era and no one believed anything that happened in this group would affect Excellent Era's dominance.

　

The eight quarter finalists were all decided on this night, and the next round's match arrangement would be automatically generated.

The following matches for the Challenger League would continue in a knockout-style best of one game with no difference in home or away. The map would be decided by the hosting party, all made by the Glory game company specially for the following games. With a match every week, the champions would be decided in three weeks. As for the competitive format, it would go by an entirely new format which would be used for the first time ever in the Challenger League offline tournament.

The new format decreased the three parts of the game to two. The individual matches would be removed, leaving only the group arena and team competition. However, the group arena would be changed from three on three to five on five.

The scoring system would be the all new headcount scoring system.

For example, if, in the group arena, someone was overwhelming enough to wipe out all five members of the other team, they would get five points. If two people managed to destroy all five, they would get four points; three people and they'd obtain three points; four people and they'd get two; five people and they'd get one. If all five people went up and weren't able to defeat the other team, they would lose and would get no points.

The team competition would be the same. The points depended on how many people were left on your side, a point per person.

The final score would be the total of the two.

Because of the change in the scoring system, the format was all too new. After the Alliance leaked this, experts immediately began pointing out that this would lead to a revolution in Glory tactics. As opposed to simply pursuing the final victory, players needed to consider a lot more under this format. The game would become a lot more complicated and there would be much more to it. For the analysts who wouldn't be hurting their waist when they stood and talked, they admired the new rules. However, for the actual participants, the pros, changing their habits would be something extremely annoying. So it didn't matter if the change made things better or worse; they wouldn't welcome it no matter what. It was just that when it made things worse, they could reasonably complain about it, but this sort of format where they couldn't pick out any major flaws, they could only go and get used to it.

The Alliance planned to first test it out in the Challenger League to see how things went. If it was alright, they'd implement it in the Pro League playoffs. As for if the regular season needed changing or not, they'd have to do some more research.

The new competitive format wasn't some sort of big reveal for everyone. When they started looking into it, the Alliance had gone to the clubs to see their opinions on it, as to avoid making some absurd rules and causing a riot. Being able to share this plan of theirs meant that the clubs wouldn't have anything to say against it. As for the participants of the Challenger League, they were insignificant and powerless and could only go along with it.

Because of the addition of the headcount scoring system, the new format would be more complicated as experts had analyzed. But no matter how complicated the competition was, they could still make certain of their victory. If you won both the group arena and the team competition, then there was no need to take the headcount into account when deciding a victor.

The headcount would only be necessary if the victors of the group arena and team competition were different. Those who thought the headcount scoring system was only for deciding a victor under these circumstances were too naive. If a victor couldn't be decided, they could add another match. The Alliance welcomed more matches for more spectators. Otherwise, why would they have two rounds? They'd just have each match be a team competition and leave it at that, simple.

Not doing that was naturally because one on one duels were an irreplaceable format that the audience loved. However, this sort of amalgamation of different match styles of the past had caused matches to end early. Especially with the appearance of such a situation in the finals of the last season, the Alliance was resolute in wanting to change this.

In theory, the same thing could happen with the new format. For example, if one team got five points in the group arena and then killed two of their opponents in the team competition, then the match would end early.

However, the probability of this happening was extremely low. In the Pro League, one versus three was already a very rare event, so while one versus five might not be impossible, the probability of something that happening couldn't be lower. Anyways, five points, four points, even three points would be highly unlikely in the group arena. After all, the group arena was a fair, one on one sort of fight. Getting one or two points in the end should be the most common conclusion.

　

However, the team competition would be different. It would be easier to gain points in the team competition than the group arena because the team competition was only fair at the very beginning. When the disadvantaged side began to lose players, the gap would grow. The advantaged side keeping two or even three points would be common. Only one point would be less common in this circumstance.

Considering all these factors, the team competition wouldn't be affected much if one team could only get one or two points in the Group Arena. That meant, with the new rules, the team competition was a heavy deciding factor. However, this was under the assumption that you didn't let down your guard during the group arena. With each part tying to the other, the game's competitiveness and viewership were assured, while reducing the chances of an early finish to the minimum. The Alliance was full of confidence to this new format. The eight quarter finalists of the Challenger League would be graced with the chance to be the very first to try the new format out.

Chapter 981: New Stage and Final Stage

There would be ten days of rest after the completion of the group stage. The next stage of the tournament would begin on 5/16, a Friday night. There would be three rounds over the next three weeks until the Challenger League champion was crowned.

The teams eliminated in the group stage returned home one after the other over the next few days. Many player teams felt very satisfied because they had managed to reach this step. They received quite a chunk of prize money from the Alliance. Their trip could be considered worthwhile. The team most unwilling to leave was Team Mysterious Fantasy. After the end of the second day of the group stage, the press released news that Mysterious Fantasy's coach, Zhang Yiwei, had stepped down from his position. Reporters tried to contact him, but all of their requests were declined. The official statement from Mysterious Fantasy said that from their three seasons of experience, they felt like coaching wasn't suitable for the current Glory competitive scene.

The following 5/9 issue of the Esports Home also published this piece of news. However, most of the news was focused on Team Happy, the team that had eliminated Team Mysterious Fantasy from the tournament.

Chang Xian prepared a detailed introduction on Team Happy long ago. What's more, he had revised it multiple times after consulting Team Happy. Now that Team Happy had attracted so much attention, Chang Xian finally had the opportunity to bring out the article that he had been holding onto for so long. Team Happy had finally been introduced on the front page. Apart from that, how could they not want to know the team's thoughts? In the same issue, Chang Xian also did an interview on Team Happy. Chang Xian had finally made it into the spotlight this week. Through his relationship with Happy, he alone took up half of the space given for the Challenger League. The other two reporters, that had come specifically for the Challenger League, were filled with envy.

They had also grabbed onto Team Happy. They had looked to do interviews for Happy and had written also introductions for them, but how could they know as much as a team reporter like Chang Xian? The final articles chosen to be published were all Chang Xian's.

Becoming a team reporter for an Internet cafe grassroots team? In the beginning, the two had laughed at Chang Xian's decision, but now they couldn't even force a smile. "Let's see how long his pride will last!" The two thought venomously, and began cursing for Team Happy to hurry and get eliminated. If they couldn't profit from it, then the material was worthless in their eyes.

As for Cao Guangcheng, he deserved to be an experienced reporter. He didn't even try and fight with Chang Xian for Team Happy. He continued to insipidly write about his specific topic. This week, he analyzed Team Excellent Era's situation with the new tournament format.

The Challenger League entered the next stage, while this season's Pro League had entered the final stage.

5/10. The 34th round of season nine of the Glory Alliance. Team Tyranny and their four heavenly kings had steadily held the lead since the start. Even now, their position at the top of the regular season standings remained unshakeable. In addition, with their efficiency at earning points, breaking the record for total number of points won in a season was no problem for them. However, trying to beat Team Excellent Era's season two record would be practically impossible. That season, Team Excellent Era won a total of 276 points. It didn't seem like a very high number from a total points perspective, but that was because the Alliance only had 16 teams at the time. Back then, there had only been 30 matches in a season. Thus, comparing their total points would not be a good comparison, so comparing the average number of points won per match would be more fair. In that case, Team Excellent Era won 9.2 points per match on average during the second season. This record was ridiculous to the point of being untouchable. With only four rounds left the season, it was already hopeless for Team Tyranny to challenge it.

However, just being able to vie for the record already showed Team Tyranny's unquestionable dominance this season.

In second place was last season's champions, Team Samsara. This season, they strived to defend their title. Even though they had been suppressed by Team Tyranny in the regular season, the playoffs and the regular season were unrelated. Team Blue Rain pushed them down last year too, but who won the playoffs in the end? The regular season had more matches over a longer period of time. It tested a team's consistency, but the playoffs was an elimination tournament. Two matches would determine the winner. It tested a team's explosiveness.

Third, fourth, fifth place was Team Blue Rain, Team Wind Howl, and Team Tiny Herb respectively. The number of points between the three teams was very close, so it was not possible to distinguish which team was better than the other through placings. However, Team Wind Howl failed to even make it to the playoffs last season, yet now they had turned a new leaf this season, becoming a powerhouse no weaker than Team Blue Rain and Team Tiny Herb. Tang Hao's transfer had already been considered last summer's most successful transfer .

The fight for the last three playoff spots for the sixth, seventh, and eighth place team were very extremely intense. Team Misty Rain was in sixth place. They had no strong teams in the next four rounds, so their situation was looking up. Team Hundred Blossoms was in seventh place. They had lost too many points during the start of the season. They only started catching up after they managed to recover. Their situation was somewhat grave. Team Void was in eighth place. The ghost duo had lasted for so many years. They had always placed neither low nor high as if they were stuck at a bottleneck. Their performance this season had its ups and downs. Even though they still held onto their playoff spot for now, many people considered them as the team most likely to disappoint. If they lost their playoff spot, they might just keep falling from there.

What were the chances of Team Void losing their playoff spot? It was actually quite likely. Team 301 was biting at their heels. Team 301 was the model example of an average team. Their players weren't the best and their characters weren't the most powerful, but the team operated extremely well. Their team's performance was very consistent, and they frequently made it to playoffs. Their performance this season had been affected by Xu Bin's departure. If not, they might have forced the inconsistent Team Void out long ago.

The teams closely behind Team 301 were some of the great mysteries of the season.　

Radiant, Conquering Clouds, Heavenly Swords, Parade. These four teams moved up and down the rankings together. They were neatly in order from 10th to 13th place. It was truly surprising. In the beginning, their initial impression was that they should be pacing back and forth between the relegation zone. Instead, they had actually run past it into the middle zone. It was even possible for them to make it into playoffs. Teams with All Stars like Royal Style and Seaside had been forced behind them. The original tenth place team, Team Thunderclap, also surprised many. Now, they had been pushed aside too.

These four teams benefited the most from the new game update. However, only the club guild elites competing for wild bosses in the game knew the real reason why they were performing so well. However, as the season proceeded towards the final stage, the focus of the teams shifted again. Many pro players withdrew from the game and began focusing more on their matches, especially the teams bordering on the edge like Hundred Blossoms, Void, and 301. How could they dare to be careless now?

...….　　

As soon as these teams started focusing on the matches, those four teams obviously met with trouble. From a points perspective, they could still make it to playoffs, but in reality, these four teams knew in their hearts that they had only been profiting at the other's expense. Taking advantage of them was just a one-time thing. They still didn't have the strength to rival them on equal footing.

The Pro League and Challenger League had reached their most exciting stages. However, because there was quite a wide skill gap between different teams in the Challenger League compared to the teams in the Pro League, everyone's attention was more focused. Thus, apart from a few teams, the majority of the teams weren't under much pressure. Team Excellent Era's opponents wouldn't go so far as to not sleeping, trying to figure out a strategy on how to beat Excellent Era. Everyone would laugh at them, treating them as silly people with their panties in a bunch.

Ten days passed by quickly. It was finally match day. Among the eight teams, the highlight match would be between Team Jade Dynasty and Team Trader. Group B's Team Trader made it past a former pro team. They were clearly the biggest dark horse in this offline tournament. They had spectacular performances against Group B's Team Happy and Team Mysterious Fantasy. In this match between Team Jade Dynasty, no one could be certain that Team Jade Dynasty would win just because they had once been a pro team.

The dark horse's journey ended here though. The highlight match ended dully. From the group arena to the team competition, Team Jade Dynasty seemed to be following a routine. They kept advancing step by step until Team Trader finally fell.

The matches for Team Happy and Team Excellent Era were without any suspense. Player teams were easily beaten by them, so the most interesting match was the one between Group C's first seed and Group D's second seed. The strength between the two teams was quite close. Even though the quality of match wasn't that high, it was at least exciting to watch. Unfortunately, if this type of excitement was enough to satisfy the crowd, why would pro teams need to exist?

The quarter finals ended just like that. None of the matches made anyone's blood race. Even the media reports towards the matches felt dispirited. However, thinking of the next confrontations, everyone's spirits rose. In the top half, Happy and Jade Dynasty would clash. This should be a fairly high-quality match. As for the second half, players who supported Excellent Era and had yet to tire from them winning would continue to be in admiration as their Gods crushed enemy weaklings.

"Two more matches!"

On the morning of the second day, Chen Guo woke up from her dream with a smile. Sunlight had already filled her room. The joy from her dream had yet to recede. She looked to the side and noticed that her roommate Tang Rou was nowhere to be seen.　

She woke up so early?

Chen Guo muttered to herself. She got out of bed, washed up, tidied everything, and then left the room. The corridor was extremely quiet. Chen Guo reckoned that the others were still sleeping, so she didn't go to bother them. She went downstairs, ate breakfast, and then headed over to the Internet cafe practice room.

Excellent Era had booked their own hotel, while the liveliness at the start of the offline tournament was no longer as crazy. Of the nineteen teams at this hotel, only three remained. Everyone was together in the same place during this period of time, and everyone shared Glory as their passion. The players all loved to play the game, so even though they were here to compete against each other, they still became good friends off stage. Those who could make it to this stage of the Challenger League were outstanding players. As a result, Chen Guo was quite enthusiastic about recruiting these people for Happy.

But even if they were outstanding, many of them had their own foundations in the game. Most of them shrugged off her attempts to recruit them. Chen Guo had lots of experience with the game. She understood all of that, so she wasn't impatient. Her Chasing Haze added many friends in the game during this period of time. They could meet again in the Heavenly Domain!

In comparison, more people were more interested in Ye Xiu. What was surprising to Chen Guo was that Ye Xiu didn't seem to avoid many topics, even though he had always acted mysterious in the past.

"What's going on?" Chen Guo was puzzled.

"What do you mean? I was using someone else's name before. How could I not try to keep a low profile?" Ye Xiu said half jokingly.

Chapter 982: Team Jade Dynasty’s Consistency

Was the fake identity the reason why Ye Xiu had always been hiding? Ye Xiu didn't seem to be serious when he said that this was the reason, so Chen Guo wasn't certain. Before Chen Guo met Ye Xiu, if it was said that God Ye Qiu didn't accept interviews or do endorsements in order to focus on competing, Chen Guo would have believed it. She knew him better now though. Chen Guo always felt like even though Ye Xiu's dedication towards Glory wasn't false, he wasn't so dedicated that he would refuse to do anything else.

After knowing him for so long, Chen Guo felt like Ye Xiu must have many reasons for hiding. For example, in the beginning, he didn't want his family to find him after running away from home. Keeping a low-profile because he was using a fake identity was a very understandable reason too. Ye Xiu was probably too lazy to deal with that stuff anyways. These may all be reasons for why he had molded his image as this mysterious God. But now, his family problems weren't as serious as back then. His fake identity problem had been resolved. Thus, of those three reasons, two were no longer problems. It made sense that Ye Xiu would push the boat along the current and stop hiding.

Chen Guo continued thinking about it as she walked towards Happy's practice area. It wasn't empty at all. Everyone in Team Happy, including Mo Fan, had gotten up even earlier than her. All of them were busy in front of their computers.

"Why didn't anyone wake me up!" Seeing how enthusiastic everyone was, Chen Guo felt very ashamed and grumbled to Tang Rou.

"I didn't think everyone would be up so early either!" Tang Rou said.

"Was this all a coincidence?" Chen Guo said.

"Yup." Tang Rou nodded her head, "When I got here, Ye Xiu and Old Wei were already here."

"What's everyone up to?" Chen Guo looked around in a circle. The majority of them were practicing. Only Ye Xiu, Wei Chen, and Sun Zheping were circled around a single computer. All three of them had their hands crossed over their chests. Their expressions were grave as they stared at the screen.

There was a Glory match recording being played on the screen. After Chen Guo went closer to take a look, she could see that it was Team Jade Dynasty's match. The offline tournament had been going on for a month now. Not only did she recognize every player on the remaining teams, she recognized the characters on each team too. The screen was currently displaying one of Team Jade Dynasty's matches in the group stage.

Chen Guo watched for a bit, but she didn't see any problems. Team Jade Dynasty was heralded as a pro team, but their performance was always very mediocre. In their next match, more people actually favored Team Happy. After eliminating Team Everlasting and beating Team Mysterious Fantasy 10-0, no one doubted that Team Happy was the real deal. However, beating Team Excellent Era….. very few people believed that it could happen. But in many people's eyes, Team Jade Dynasty wasn't even as good as Team Everlasting or Team Mysterious Fantasy. When they fought against Team Happy, wouldn't they lose even more miserably?

However, Chen Guo saw how solemn the three Gods were as they watched Jade Dynasty's match. She felt like there should be a reason, so she was too afraid to rashly come out with her wise opinion on the matter. She watched along with them for awhile longer. This match ended with Jade Dynasty winning the team competition.

"What do you think?" Ye Xiu spoke.

"Your analysis is reasonable." Sun Zheping nodded his head.

"What's going on?" In the end, Chen Guo couldn't help but interrupt them.

"Oh, we're studying Jade Dynasty." Ye Xiu turned his head and saw Chen Guo. He gave her a quick explanation.

"Is there a problem with Jade Dynasty?" Chen Guo asked.

"Jade Dynasty's performance has always been quite mediocre, but being able to maintain that performance the entire time shows how terrifyingly consistent they are." Ye Xiu said.

"What does that mean?" Chen Guo didn't understand.

"It means that they've always been more than up to the task 1 *. They have the ability to win their matches in a more dominant manner, yet they only play at this current level." Ye Xiu said.

"Why is that?"

"I don't know." Ye Xiu shook his head, "Maybe it's because they're intentionally showing that they're weak or maybe it's because it's a way to practice their control over their rhythm."　　

"In short, this isn't Team Jade Dynasty's true strength?" Chen Guo said.

"It's just a guess. For now, all three of us acknowledge that it's a possibility." Ye Xiu said, while pulling out his QQ. He clicked on a profile picture in his friends list. His QQ trembled and then he sent a "Hello hello hello?"

Then, the QQ interface showed that the other side was typing, but no reply came after a long time. Ye Xiu waited patiently and typed again: "Is it that bad? Even your typing is this slow?"

Chen Guo moved closer to take a look. Her jaw dropped. The other side's name was "Yu Wenzhou".

Why did Ye Xiu look for Team Blue Rain's captain?

Chen Guo was puzzled. Then, she saw the other side's reply: "They should be suppressing their rhythm deliberately! But I don't think that it's because they're pretending they're weaker than they actually are. They should be playing slower and more patiently in order to play more consistently. Their playing looks as if they're out of practice. It's as if they're still familiarizing themselves with new characters."

"As I thought!" Ye Xiu replied.

"That's just my own opinion." Yu Wenzhou expressed.

"Okay, I've got it. Sorry! If you're sleepy, then you should go back to bed." Ye Xiu said.

"..."

Ye Xiu closed the chat window and then looked towards Wei Chen and Sun Zheping: "His opinion is the same as ours. It looks like that really is the case."

Chen Guo figured out what had just happened. She stood on the side, dumbstruck. These guys analyzing it was fine, but even pulling along Blue Rain's Yu Wenzhou and having this top master help them analyze it too?

"This this this... this is breaking the rules!" Chen Guo said.

'Breaking the rules?" Ye Xiu turned his head and looked at Chen Guo, "What rule did we break?"

"This this this...." Chen Guo didn't know what to say. There was no clause in the rules that talked about this, but Chen Guo felt like it was the big bullying the small. If Jade Dynasty knew about it, they'd probably be crying out of grievance.

Those three weren't even done yet!

"Should we go ask Zhang Xinjie and see what he thinks?" Wei Chen said.

"Him?" Ye Xiu checked the time. "He gets up from bed, washes, eats breakfast, exercises on a punctual schedule. You can't take away even a second from his routine. Let alone when he replies, we can't even count on him replying!"

"Isn't there another Master Tactician?" Sun Zheping said.

"Xiao Shiqin?" Ye Xiu asked.

"I think that's the name." Sun Zheping nodded his head.

"Can't you pay more attention to the younger generation? You can't even remember their names!" Ye Xiu looked at him disdainfully.

"Yeah….."

"What does yeah mean?"　　

"Stop wasting time. Go ask him!" Sun Zheping said.

"Do you not understand what the situation is! Do you know which team he's on?" Ye Xiu said.

"Which team!?"　　

"Excellent Era!" Ye Xiu said.

"Oh?"

"Oh? Do you not read news about transfers?" Ye Xiu said.

"Never." Sun Zheping said.

Ye Xiu actually already knew that. The person in front of him never cared about that stuff. For him, who cares if there are any changes in a team? Just chop them to pieces. What's the difference?

"Asking him probably wouldn't be too convenient." Ye Xiu said.　

"Yeah." Wei Chen nodded his head, "Who knows, he might just intentionally try to confuse us with his analysis." Wei Chen thought about Xiao Shiqin from a shameless perspective.

"Right." Sun Zheping nodded his head, "That's possible. People who play with tactics have dirty hearts."

"Yes yes, all of them are shameless." Wei Chen immediately expressed his approval. Sun Zheping's evaluation of tacticians clearly included Ye Xiu. After all, he was one of the four Master Tacticians!　　

"Haha." Ye Xiu laughed dryly.

"You're not even ashamed." Wei Chen shook his head and sighed.

"And you even think of it as something glorious." Sun Zheping also sighed. He looked at Ye Xiu like he couldn't be saved.

"Haha." Ye Xiu laughed again. "Says the two who were beaten by me."

"It looks like Team Jade Dynasty won't be easy to deal with!" As expected, Wei Chen switched subjects. The switch was stiff, showing his shamelessness.

"Yeah, from our analysis, Team Jade Dynasty might not be hiding anything in terms of their playstyle. What they've hidden is the strength of their characters." Ye Xiu obviously wasn't going to waste time arguing. He followed along and started talking business.

"The strength of their characters can't be considered weak." Wei Chen looked through the information he had. It was all the detailed information that could be found on the current Team Jade Dynasty. Chang Xian had organized it and handed it over to them.

There were already plenty of Level 75 players after five months. Level 75 Orange equipment naturally weren't as rare as before. For a former pro team like Team Jade Dynasty, even if they couldn't get it themselves, they could still use money to buy it. Orange equipment had a drop rate, after all. Their value couldn't be compared to Silver equipment. If a team set their sights on going pro, if they didn't even have the heart to spend some money on Orange equipment, then it was best if they disbanded.

Team Jade Dynasty hadn't given up after so many years. They could still invest some money into equipping everyone with Level 75 Orange equipment. If these characters were still hiding strength, then only Silver equipment could improve them.

"Does Team Jade Dynasty have such a backing?" Wei Chen wondered.

"I don't know….." Ye Xiu was also at a loss. If they weren't in the Challenger League, those in the competitive scene would have probably forgotten them already.

"Maybe... they got some sort of sponsor, so they have money to spend now?" Chen Guo interrupted at this moment. Her opinion was very reasonable. This came from her personal experience. Team Happy's outstanding performance in the offline tournament had already attracted several organizations, who wanted to discuss a partnership with Team Happy. Of course, no one had signed anything yet because all of the organizations still needed to wait and see. Just their current performance wasn't enough for them to want a long term partnership. But if Team Happy actually beat Team Excellent Era, their talks for a partnership would intensify.

The current Team Jade Dynasty seemed to be hiding their strength. Chen Guo suddenly thought: could this team have gotten this type of support?

Chapter 983: Happy’s Fanclub

Sponsorship?

Ye Xiu shook his head. A sponsorship was a business move. The sponsor needed to benefit from the sponsorship, so organizations usually looked for strong teams, teams with lots to talk about, or teams that would receive a lot of attention. The Challenger League viewership was very small. Few sponsors would gain any benefit from sponsoring Challenger League teams.

Happy receiving sponsorship talks was an exception. Even though Happy wasn't a strong team in many people's eyes, Happy also never lacked topics to talk about. Happy was receiving more and more attention too. Even so, no one had reached out for sponsorship yet. It was clearly because they felt like Happy still hadn't reached the level they wanted.

The business didn't want a short-lived night-blooming cactus, but a long-lasting partner. In the Challenger League, there was only way to achieve this: getting the final victory.

This time's Challenger League had Excellent Era. If Happy actually won, the attention that Happy received wouldn't be on the same level as the past Challenger League winners. The current interest towards Happy had much to do with Excellent Era. It was the existence of Excellent Era that gave them such value in this year's Challenger League.

Jade Dynasty's performance in the Challenger League had been very mediocre too. Even though they had Excellent Era as a touchstone, they should be in the same boat as Happy. They had to at least beat Excellent Era first before getting any sponsorship offers. Chen Guo's deduction wasn't logical.　　

But from this perspective, Ye Xiu thought of another possibility.

Jade Dynasty had switched owners.

Teams and clubs were similar to companies. They could be bought and sold too. If Jade Dynasty had been purchased and the buyer had a lot of money, having a strong backing all of a sudden was an extremely likely possibility.

"Why bother thinking about it so much?" Sun Zheping said, "Even if we can't see through them, we just have to prepare for them well. When the time comes, we just have to beat them."

"There's no other way." Ye Xiu nodded his head.

Since they couldn't get a read on Team Jade Dynasty's true strength, they had no way of preparing for them in a targeted manner. If they rashly came up with strategies, it was very possible that it would come back to bite them. As a result, this week's practice was just to work hard and improve without any big changes.

Jade Dynasty's players continued to go to the Internet cafe in the hotel to practice. When they saw Happy, they would smile and greet them. Everything seemed warm and friendly. At this moment, only these two teams were going in and out of the Internet cafe. The other team was up against Excellent Era next and had already given up. They might as well take the week off and have fun, so they had gone off to tour City B. They hadn't come to the Internet cafe a single time this week.

In the blink of an eye, it was match day. The Esports Home published biweekly. The Monday issue was after match day, so it introduced the contents of the match and commented on the predicted results. The Friday issue was before the next match day, so it was mostly trivial news, as well as predictions and preparations done by the teams. The Challenger League may be a small steamed bun, but it had juicy meat. There was no lack of things that needed to be written.

8 PM. Offline tournament stadium. The number of matches every week became fewer and fewer, but the number of viewers only increased. After Team Happy entered the stadium through the player passageway, they headed over to their seats. Suddenly, they heard a crash. A distance away, in the audience behind their player seats, was a huge banner: Team Happy! Certain Victory!!! Then, they saw a bunch of people sitting there and cheering loudly.

"Huh?" Chen Guo was surprised. Even though there had been a few Team Happy fans before, she had never seen this kind of support. Ye Xiu's personal fanclub had once gathered together and cheered them on, but who would have thought Team Happy would finally have a fanclub too!

Chen Guo felt delighted in her heart. But in the next moment, she heard a crash from nearby. Another banner had dropped saying: Team Jade Dynasty! Certain Victory!!!

It didn't matter whose banner was bigger. The typeface for Team Jade Dynasty was superior to Team Happy's. The fanclub over there looked at Team Happy's fanclub in delight. They started cheering loudly too. All of a sudden, Team Happy's fanclub had been drowned out.

But Happy's fanclub weren't afraid of this kind of challenge. They started shouting loudly too. There were even a few curses mixed in. Soon enough, just cursing out loud wasn't enough. They started throwing whatever they had in their hands like water bottles at Jade Dynasty's side.

This time, Jade Dynasty's fanclub looked as if they couldn't hold on. They didn't counterattack with weapons of their own. Even when Happy's fanclub had been cursing at them, not many of them cursed back. Right when Happy's fanclub were immensely proud of their victory, the stadium's security guards rushed over and surrounded them.

Chen Guo was very worried for them. She hastily ran over to talk to the security guards. Then, she saw the security guards give a harsh warning and picked out the guy who arranged the long-range attacks, preparing to escort him out of the stadium. This time, Happy's fanclub refused to cooperate. After another loud commotion, the security guards said something again and the commotion gradually died down. The lead instigator left, but he wasn't escorted out. He was simply placed in another seat. The turnout for the semifinals wasn't bad, but the Challenger League's popularity was limited, so the majority of the stadium was still empty. This lead instigator was thrown into a lonely and desolate section filled with empty seats.

As for Jade Dynasty's fanclub? They had victorious smirks on their faces as if they knew this would happen. Chen Guo saw this and was extremely unhappy, but Ye Xiu knew with just a single glance that Jade Dynasty's fanclub was experienced and organized. They had experience watching these sorts of matches and knew their limits. On the other hand, Happy's fanclub were much more wild. Creating such a commotion would obviously force the security guards to come out and stop them.

Team Jade Dynasty arrived too. They saw how the previous scene unfolded and couldn't help but look towards Team Happy and chuckle. The player seats for the two competing sides were located near each other. This time, the fanclubs on both sides had gathered behind them. They hadn't even started fighting yet, and a dispute had already arisen. Happy and Jade Dynasty was just an ordinary match with nothing to celebrate about. It was easy to imagine just how intense the struggle would be between two teams with a deep rivalry.

The players sat down in their seats. Someone from Jade Dynasty said something to the fanclub behind them as if to appease them. Chen Guo noticed this. She couldn't fall behind. She also stood up and turned around. Then, she saw the faces of the fanclub filled with expectations and suddenly didn't know what to say. A person suddenly jumped out from among the crowd, waved his hands wildly at her, and shouted: "Boss, boss, it's me! It's me!"

Before anything else happened, security guards immediately rushed over. That person immediately shrunk back, but he was still pointing fiercely at himself: "It's me!! Seven Fields! Seven Fields!"

"Ah?" Chen Guo was dumbfounded. For a moment, she couldn't remember who that was. The others already learned from Seven Fields and started introducing themselves.

"Guild leader, it's me, Cruel Shadows."

"It's me, Flying Ghost."

"Little Lobster."

"Banner Wastrel"

"Frozen Mast."

"..."

"It's you guys!!" Chen Guo blurted out. She had seen these names many times before, but they were a bit unfamiliar to her. All of them were members of the tenth server's Guild Happy. They were the first few to join the guild and helped build the guild up from scratch. A few of those guild members had reached the Heavenly Domain. A few continued to stay in Happy. Others started their journey anew after arriving in the Heavenly Domain, but there were also a few who stayed in the normal server and continued to play there. For example, the ones who had come from Full Moon Guild like Seven Field's and Sleeping Moon's group. They had originally been veterans from the Heavenly Domain, but had come to the new server after the tenth server opened. For normal servers, the end goal was to reach the Heavenly Domain.

Thus, it could be said that, in Glory, those who switched to the new server to restart their journey were dedicated to staying in the new server; they wouldn't go to the Heavenly Domain. Otherwise, it was all meaningless for them. Seven Fields and the others hadn't been from a club guild. They didn't come to the normal server to build and grow a certain guild. The reason that they came to the normal server was because they didn't want to play in the Heavenly Domain anymore and only wanted to enjoy the normal servers.

As veterans, their skill level was higher than all of the noobs in the new server, so they became Happy's backbone. The backbones of the guild always carried a certain amount of influence. The four had long since abandoned the Heavenly Domain, so they obviously didn't have any favorable impressions of the Heavenly Domain. Due to their influence, quite a few members of the tenth server's Guild Happy stayed in the normal server instead of leaving for the Heavenly Domain.

And now, they had come over to the stadium to support their team. Chen Guo didn't know where these guys were from, but all of them had gathered behind Team Happy, becoming a solid support group for them.

"You guys..." Chen Guo started to get emotional. She was someone who could easily make friends with others, but she didn't know what to say towards these "familiar" faces.

Ye Xiu quietly stood by her side. The players immediately became excited: "Ah! God Ye! Look!"

Ye Xiu had left the normal server too early, so a lot of them weren't very familiar with him. Seven Fields knew him though. They had met quite early on, even before Steamed Bun.

"Where's Little Moon Moon and the others?" Ye Xiu asked Seven Fields with a smile.

"Haha, Sunset Clouds and Drifting Water live too far away. It wasn't convenient for them to come visit. Isn't Little Moon Moon sitting over there?" Seven Fields pointed. The lead instigator, who had taken the lead in throwing a water bottle at the opposing fanclub and had been put under house arrest in an empty area, was Sleeping Moon.

"Hahahaha, it's actually you guys!" A person suddenly got up from Chen Guo's side. Steamed Bun had stood up on his seat and waved excitedly towards Happy's fanclub.

"Oh oh, it's Steamed Bun! That fool!" Everyone roared. Ye Xiu was a God. When they faced him, they always felt pressured and didn't know what to say. However, when they faced Steamed Bun, they immediately became close. Steamed Bun had come from Guild Happy, so they knew all him very well.

"Hahahaha, watch me f*ck these guys up." Steamed Bun pointed towards Team Jade Dynasty.

"1v5! Do you dare!!" Happy's fanclub shouted.

Chapter 984: Jade Dynasty’s Boss

The fanclubs for both teams had come, so the teams had to interact with them, of course. For Jade Dynasty, the team and fan interactions were peaceful and harmonious. The team thanked their fans for their support and the fans didn't stop shouting encouragements toward the team. For Happy, their team and fan interactions were rambunctious and like a riot. Nothing needed to be said about Steamed Bun and his pals, but they weren't unfamiliar with Tang Rou either! It was just that Tang Rou was extremely headstrong and fierce in game, so while she might've had a lady's voice, many people suspected. Now that they saw the player behind the character, they found that, not only was she really a girl, but she was also immensely beautiful. Everyone was rather embarrassed to speak for a moment.

Apart from those two, there was also Luo Ji, who had been a part of Guild Happy for a long time, becoming close with the other guild members and even provided them with many walkthroughs and the such. In the eyes of rookies and noobs, Luo Ji was also an expert among experts. Now, seeing that he was even part of the team, who wouldn't nod and say: an expert as expected.

Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash was usually being power leveled by a different person, so he hadn't had much interaction with Guild Happy's members. However, since his name was a part of the guild, he was one of them, so there would naturally be this sort of closeness.

　　

Over on Happy's side, there was a rowdy atmosphere, often catching the attention of the security guards. So Happy's players didn't dare to make any sudden movements. There was a gap between the audience seating and the players seating, and this was for the safety of the players. According to the rules, the audience couldn't enter the surrounding areas. However, sometimes fans would want autographs and after getting the permission of the players, the guards would let it slip occasionally. However, one of Happy's fans had already been dragged out today for overstepping their bounds, so they became the target of the security guards' watchful stare. Because of this, they obviously couldn't be as casual as they wanted to be. They were all chatting happily, but they could only yell across the gap at each other.

Jade Dynasty's polite interactions were done in a few moments. That was when they saw Happy's rowdy and laughter filled area, which didn't seem to be ending. They felt conflicted. They kind of envied Happy's closeness with their fans, but at the same time they were disdainful of their grassroots demeanor. However, their thoughts then changed. Even if they didn't consider anything else, with just God Ye Qiu's identity alone, Happy was far above their entire team. What sort of right did they have to be disdainful of the other's grassroots demeanor?

Jade Dynasty's players all felt a little down, dully sitting there and waiting for the match to start. Their fanclub had also gone quiet, sitting there and watching Happy's side. Talking about envious, it was the fans who were truly envious. The pro teams of today sat high above everyone, and their players were all celebrities, becoming more and more distant from their supporters. This sort of close and familiar interaction was something they could only dream of.

Seeing the cheers coming from Happy's side and comparing it to their own rather cool airs, one person sitting in Jade Dynasty's player stands turned and smiled at another, saying a few words to him. After that person nodded, the two stood up together and walked towards Team Happy with a smile.

Ye Xiu had long since noticed these two. These two had never appeared in Jade Dynasty's lineup before and today was the first time they had shown their faces. However, they couldn't be players either. The offline matches didn't allow the changing of your lineup mid tournament.

In addition, the person on the right seemed older, probably around thirty years old, while the one on the left was relatively younger, about twenty five or twenty six years old.

　

Seeing the two approach, Ye Xiu stepped forward to meet them. After the others noticed, they all stopped their conversations and turned to place their gaze on the two.

　

"Hello, God Ye." The two initiated greeting upon coming forth.

"You are…?"

"Zhang Jian." The relatively older one on the right introduced himself.

Ye Xiu paused for a moment after hearing this before giving Zhang Jian a closer look. Soon he remembered. "It's you? It's been quite a while, I didn't even recognize you."

"For insignificant people like us, it's already enough of an honor if God Ye has heard of our names before," Zhang Jian said with a smile.

"What are you saying?" Ye Xiu smiled as well.

Zhang Jian was also a first generation pro player and was Jade Dynasty's captain back then. For the first two years, he led Team Jade Dynasty from the very bottom of the Alliance. Compared to the captain that had led his team to gain two consecutive championships in both years, he was as opposite as could be from Ye Qiu in the Alliance. From this point of view, saying he was an insignificant person wasn't being modest for Zhang Jian.

However, considering his individual strength, Zhang Jian wasn't as insignificant as his team who always placed last. Yet in the pro league, strength didn't always mean a good record, and a good record was what truly proved your strength to people. With Jade Dynasty coming in last place for two years in a row, a record that couldn't be worse, he, as the captain and ace, took the blame for it.

　　

In the second season, the Alliance began to relegate teams and Team Jade Dynasty, at the bottom of the ranks, was relegated. However, Zhang Jian received some invitations from other teams. Just when everyone thought he was going to take the chance to escape the sinking ship, he stayed and pulled Team Jade Dynasty back into the Alliance against all of the pressure and friction against them. After that, he retired.

Then after that, there was no more news from this player. Back then, Glory wasn't so grand as it was now and pro players wouldn't make enough money. Retired pros lived normal and simple lives. As for a player like him, from a shitty team, there would be little effort made to seek out his circumstances and whereabouts.

　

Ye Xiu had never thought that, after all these years, he would meet this person again in the Glory circle. And he was even standing with Team Jade Dynasty which he had once fought alongside with. Could it be that he had gotten rich over these years and bought the team?

As Ye Xiu was wondering to himself, Zhang Jian introduced the young man beside him to Ye Xiu. "This is the boss of Team Jade Dynasty, Xiao Jie."

　

"Oh?" Ye Xiu was guessing if Zhang Jian was the boss, yet in the next moment, the boss had been introduced to him. Speaking of which, Ye Xiu really had no clue who Jade Dynasty's boss was. The information Chang Xian had given them didn't say much either. However, this man who was only around twenty-five or twenty-six, obviously couldn't have always been Jade Dynasty's boss. How old would he have been back then? Probably only sixteen or seventeen!

Yet after this introduction, An Wenyi made a surprising move by coming forwards to ask, "Xiao Jie? Is it that Xiao Jie?"

That was when the young boss nodded with a smile. "Yes, I'm that Xiao Jie."

"Who is this?" Ye Xiu and the others all looked to An Wenyi.

"He's a bestselling author," An Wenyi explained.

"Author?" Ye Xiu scratched his head. This identity seemed very distant and alien to him. Wei Chen was even more exaggerated, and took several big steps over in a rush upon hearing what they were saying. "Author? Where is he? Let me see! I haven't seen a live specimen before!"

　

As for Chen Guo, she was quite curious as well, but she wasn't as exaggerated as Wei Chen. This was because she saw a thick air of ignorance for everything non-Glory related coming from Wei Chen.

　　

"Greetings, author! It's an honor, an honor." Wei Chen came up and grabbed the man's hand, shaking it with vigor.

　

"Big Boss Wei. I watched a lot of your matches as a kid," Xiao Jie said with a smile.

"Oh oh, really! Do you want my autograph then? Hahahaha," Wei Chen said without any embarrassment whatsoever.

Xiao Jie smiled without saying anything in response. It was clear that he wasn't Wei Chen's fan. However, his words had already revealed some information; he was someone who had remained a fan of Glory for a long time.

"It seems like Boss Xiao is a fan of Jade Dynasty!" Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, I've always been one," Xiao Jie replied.

"You must not have had it easy then," Ye Xiu commented.

On that side, Zhang Jian rolled his eyes. These words were a little mocking, and yet it was the truth. Jade Dynasty wasn't anything impressive, yet they could still gain a fan that was so loyal to them throughout all these years. This was indeed not easy.

　

"Heh, that's true." Even Xiao Jie himself agreed. "Jade Dynasty's battle records have never been that good. It makes people rather worried. However, in the past, I could only be anxious about it and do nothing else. Now things are better. I have the power to help the team I support and I'm quite relieved with that."

　

"Jade Dynasty should be rather relieved, too, having a fan like yourself," Ye Xiu said.

"Haha," Xiao Jie laughed a little. He had wanted to say more, but saw the referee walking over. Seeing both sides look over, the referee waved his hand. "Go and prepare. The match is about to begin."

　

"Then let's talk after the match, yeah?" Ye Xiu suggested.

"We could also talk as the match goes on. I want to listen to what a god thinks and sees about the match," Xiao Jie said.

"No problem. We're sitting pretty near each other, after all," Ye Xiu agreed.

"Then please."

"Please."

They might've said please, but they didn't sit together immediately, but returned to the player stands to prepare for their upcoming match. As for words like "I wish you the best" they wouldn't say it. They were opponents after all. Wishing the other the best would be equal to wishing for your own failure. This sort of cliche words couldn't be more empty if said here.

Happy returned to their players' stands, but their hearts were in turmoil. They could tell what the situation was between Xiao Jie and Team Jade Dynasty through these few words.

Xiao Jie was a fan of Jade Dynasty from long ago and continued to support this team throughout the years. It was unfortunate that this team never lived up to his expectations. Yet this young man grew day by day and became a bestselling author, a successful person, so he bought the team that he supported. Such support from a fan was probably the first of its kind in Glory history. The only people who could be put on the same level were the people who played Glory and ended up making their own club and pro team to enter the Alliance like Heavenly Sword's five young masters.

This explained Jade Dynasty's miraculous history. However, this would be no help to the victory of the match. It was better to not get distracted by such trivial things.

Seeing that the match was about to start, Seven Fields stopped the others from bothering the members of Happy any longer and took command, telling the people who were meant to hold banners to hold banners, the people who were meant to be cheering to cheer, immediately beginning their support parade. Jade Dynasty's fans obviously refused to be beaten, immediately doing their own thing in order to compete with Happy's fanclub.

On Team Jade Dynasty's side, Xiao Jie sat in the seat closest to Happy, as expected. After glancing over with a smile, their team's first member stood to go up.

Chapter 985: Hidden Strength

With this new tournament format, how should the teams choose their pick order? The teams worried, and the players were also concerned as well. Everyone was vigorously researching and discussing such topics. Using the previous group arena strategy of placing the ace players at the end to hold the bottom line was too conservative and quite undesirable with the new rules.

However, directly placing these ace players at the front of the lineup also seemed excessive. In the competitive scene, 1v3 sweeps happened too rarely. The remarkable displays often seen in the group arena matches usually consisted of a two-player up-and-down.

This so called two-player up-and-down was a situation in which one player, after defeating their first opponent, also took their second opponent to half health; or possibly, after defeating their second opponent, they had little health left while facing the third and fell quickly. Even this was already considered a rarely seen success in the group arena. Thus, even if an ace player appeared first, they wouldn't necessarily bring their team a huge advantage.

The good steel still had to be used on the blade of the knife. While previously, the ace players had fought towards the end to guard the mountain pass, now they had to do their best to gain an advantage when there was an opportunity, in order to achieve victory. In this way, appearing on stage at the most optimal time was key. For example, if an opponent only had half a person remaining, sending out the ace player at that time would maximize the chances of victory.

After going through a lot of analysis, the current consensus was that, in this five person group arena, ace players should be placed in either the third or fourth position.

Except, even in this way, the group arena scoring was far more complicated than the team competition. The future development of the group arena should be stable. Teams should focus on not losing too many points in the group arena, and using the team competition as a tiebreaker. At present, the forecast predicted that the future competitions would head in this direction.

Except today, when Jade Dynasty went on stage, their first player was actually their captain, the Blade Master, Lin Yi.

Looking at the previous matches, wasn't Lin Yi Jade Dynasty's most outstanding player? Now, astonishingly, he was the first to step onstage. Did he have that much confidence, or was there another reason for such an arrangement?

Jade Dynasty's Boss, Xiao Jie, hid his smile the entire time. He turned towards Happy, making an inviting gesture towards Happy. Ye Xiu smiled, immediately patting the people next to him. "Forward!"

"Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh!!!" Immediately, Happy's fan club surged because of the person that stood up.

"Steamed Bun, 1v5!!!" Obviously the fans didn't care whether or not this was realistic. Either way, this was a cheer. If it wasn't grandiose, then how could it be called a cheer?

"Ha ha ha." Steamed Bun laughed. With his personality, he didn't care at all about what order his opponents sent out their troops. He waved his hand, turning to his group of in-game friends and pumping his fist in the air.

"1v5!" Steamed Bun yelled out. From the bystanders' point of view, this really was an arrogant and shameless guy. Jade Dynasty's fans had long started booing. After this was said, Happy's fans really felt too embarrassed to earnestly respond. Them shouting was just shouting, they obviously also knew that there was no way a 1v5 would happen. Using this to challenge other people, wasn't this just asking for their faces to be slapped?

Both sides' players immediately went onstage, swiping their account cards to enter the game. Happy's players all looked at each other. All of their screens were stopped on the character loading image. After the characters had finished loading, the screen would display the characters' equipment for the entire audience to see.

"Sure enough!"

Lin Yi's character, Blader Master Ten Thousand Swords, struck a pose. Just from the character's attire, everyone could see what was different from before. As soon as the equipment viewer was opened, a line of glittery silver names jumped out. From head to toe, Ten Thousand Swords had seven pieces of Silver equipment. Although this was one less piece than Windward Formation. In reality, Happy's Silver equipment wasn't evenly distributed. Wei Chen's Windward Formation had eight pieces, but the rest of Happy had far less than that. Furthermore, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim only had a single Silver weapon, Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. When it came to Silver equipment, Ye Xiu mainly prioritized his teammates.

Yet, most pro teams wouldn't be this ridiculous and heavily favor one character over another. Although the core characters would definitely consume more resources, they wouldn't go so far as to give one character eight pieces of Silver equipment while leaving another with only one. Adding onto Jade Dynasty's shaky foundation, Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords' Equipment level likely represented the average of the team. An average of seven pieces of Silver equipment… this armor surpassed the Alliance's average level. Sure enough, Jade Dynasty possessed a lot of hidden strength.

　　

However, of Ten Thousand Swords' 7 pieces of Silver equipment, not a single piece was level 75. After all, level 75 materials were very limited. Right now, in the Alliance, level 70 equipment were widespread. All of this was accumulated over the years while the level cap had remained at 70. If any team really wanted to upgrade their equipment over the course of a year, they would have to monopolize the Heavenly Domain's uncommon materials. Trying to do this would make any team go insane.

Jade Dynasty's circumstances were well understood. Thus, Happy's players maintained calm expressions. Jade Dynasty being able to acquire this many pieces of Silver Equipment so quickly probably wasn't due to financial resources alone. After all, Xiao Jie was only a young writer. No matter how well his books sold, there was no way he could compete financially with people like Luo Guanning. Moreover, Luo Guanning had a five man crew. Even with that, they had only managed to obtain a total of 20 pieces of Silver equipment when they had entered the alliance.

Although Jade Dynasty was in dire straits, when all was said and done, they had started off as a member of the pro circle. After so many years, they still hadn't given up. No matter what, they still had to have accumulated resources. Xiao Jie's investment this time had probably come at an optimal time, exploding forth all of Jade Dynasty's accumulated resources. Additionally, that guy Zhang Jian perhaps was also a crucial figure in breaking out Jade Dynasty's potential. Back in that era, he was a pro level player. If he still hadn't given up after all these years, then his achievements in Glory wouldn't be a small matter either.

As Ye Xiu waited for the people to realize Jade Dynasty's circumstances, onstage the first round of the group arena had finally begun. After the countdown finished, both sides' characters entered the map, and the competition officially began. Jade Dynasty's boss, Xiao Jie, had indeed done as he promised. As soon as the competition began, he gathered together with Ye Xiu to chat.

"I think your team's current player is really interesting," Xiao Jie said, his voice giving off a kind of pompous tone of seniority, but to tell the truth, Ye Xiu wasn't really at an age where he could be looked down upon. Twenty-five, twenty-six, there was basically no difference in age between the two.

"Your team's player also seems quite steady," Ye Xiu replied.

"A team captain needs to be like this," Xiao Jie sighed.

"It looks as if he still isn't the ace player of Jade Dynasty," Ye Xiu said.

Xiao Jie smiled, immediately asking, "From God Ye's perspective, which of our Jade Dynasty's players do you think is our ace?"

Ye Xiu also smiled, turning to look towards one of the players on Jade Dynasty. "Your ace player would find it difficult to guide your troops into battle as the core. He's instead acting as your final line of defence."

"God Ye indeed has a good eye!" Xiao Jie gave a thumbs up out of praise, also turning to look at this player within Team Jade Dynasty, the Cleric Lu Shilin.

"However, God Ye's statement that a Cleric isn't able to guide troops as the core, I think that's a bit old-fashioned." Xiao Jie said.

"Eh. Actually what I wanted to say was leading, not guiding. I used the wrong word. Sorry about that. I'm sure you know that I'm no writer." Ye Xiu said.

Xiao Jie stared blankly, suddenly not knowing whether to laugh or cry. Leading, guiding, these two phrases only differed by three letters**. The meanings were indeed a bit different. He had thought about picking a fight with Ye Xiu to prove he was superior. He didn't expect the other party to immediately use a wording error to cover this up, conveniently mocking his own identity as a writer at the same time.

"It seems that God Ye also has a card up his sleeve when it comes to responding to this threat?" Xiao Jie composed himself and continued to ask.

"In reality, as long as he's not the core player leading the team, there's really no need to specially respond," Ye Xiu replied.

"Really?" Xiao Jie smiled again, not saying anymore. He went back to his seat to continue watching the competition.

This guy really liked to smile, the dim, faint kind. At first, looking at these smiles easily created good feelings in people, thinking that there was a good reason for his modesty. However, after these kinds of smiles came time and again, they no longer conveyed that same meaning. Instead, there was pride and conceit. He used this kind superiority-filled expression to express his disapproval of the other party. From Chen Guo's perspective, it would be better if he directly said, "You truly are an idiot," to his heart's content.

"This guy's smile is truly annoying," Chen Guo said to Ye Xiu.

"He's annoying even when he doesn't smile, making this team to cause trouble for us. It's truly troublesome!" Ye Xiu said.

"..."

Offstage, the exchange stopped at this point. Onstage, Steamed Bun's Steamed Bun Invasion and Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords had already exchanged blows for quite a while. Neither side had specific tactics for this round, directly heading for the middle of the map. As soon as they met, they began to fight.

Mechanics, awareness, judgment, a battle without much scheming. With more experience, more solid tech skill, and better equipment, Lin Yi very quickly gained the upper hand. He didn't have the strength to completely suppress Steamed Bun, but his steady and unaffected state of mind nevertheless partially restrained Steamed Bun's derailment. Although from time to Steamed Bun would jump out with an ingenious move, it didn't have any psychological impact on Lin Yi. Though this kind of randomness couldn't possibly follow any rules, Lin Yi actually managed to use his steady mind to remain completely unaffected.

Ye Xiu glanced over at Jade Dynasty. Coincidentally, at that same moment Xiao Jie also happened to look over towards him with that same smile again. His superiority seemed to say: Look, I know.

The opponent's first player had been chosen as a tactical move with purpose. It seemed as if they had guessed Happy's intent. Although no one knew how skilled Xiao Jie was at Glory, as a fan of Jade Dynasty from the early days until now, he was clearly a Glory fanatic. It appeared that when it came to Glory, this guy also had some skill.

Seven Fields and the others had been wildly cheering for Steamed Bun in the beginning. At this point, they were feeling a bit depressed because they could all see that the present circumstances were quite unfavorable towards him.

If even the audience members could tell, then the circumstances were quite obvious. The commentators nearly announced the results.

"Haha, it looks like the outcome of this match is already clear." Xiao Jie moved closer to say.

"Everyone can already see the obvious, but there's still one more person who isn't so sure!" Ye Xiu said.

"Who?" Xiao Jie didn't understand. It was so obvious. Who couldn't tell?

"Look," Ye Xiu held out his hand, pointing towards the screen. "Our Steamed Bun is still fighting energetically."

Chapter 986: Crucial Point

On screen, Steamed Bun Invasion looked like he had just gone on stage. He was filled with energy as he continued to clash with Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords. From time to time, he would make a weird move that would be calmly received by Lin Yi. However, that was all. The situation stayed the same as before. Lin Yi firmly grasped the pace of the match. If not, how could even the normal audience members already be certain of who the winner of this fight would be?

Xiao Jie saw this scene and smiled.

"He's quite tenacious." He said.

"Tenacious? You're mistaken. That's not tenacity. He hasn't even started considering giving up or persevering. He's just continuing to keep his own pace. I won't deny that Lin Yi has the fight under control at the moment, but it's still too early to say who will win and who will lose."

"Haha." Xiao Jie laughed. He found it beneath him to argue. In his eyes, Ye Xiu was just believing in his own lies. Just look at the situation. You're saying it's still too early?

Xiao Jie's gaze turned back to the stage. Steamed Bun Invasion had once again done an incomprehensible move. When his Powerful Knee Strike smashed towards Ten Thousand Swords, Lin Yi had his Ten Thousand Swords calmly step to the side and prepare to counter attack. Who would have thought that Steamed Bun Invasion, who had whistled past him, would suddenly turn his head and shout at Ten Thousand Swords.

Brawler skill: Threaten.

Threaten didn't deal direct damage. It was classified as a spirit attack, and it reduced the target's attack power. Spirit attacks could not be avoided. It could only be defended by the appropriate resistance skills, or lowered or canceled by the Spirit stat.

Looking at it from the effects from this skill, Steamed Bun's abrupt Threaten didn't make much sense. Maybe he planned on trading blows with his opponent. He had caught his opponent off guard and lowered the opponent's attack power. His Powerful Knee Strike may have been dodged, but his target had been successfully Threatened. However, because of the momentum from his Powerful Knee Strike, he continued to fly past his opponent. Ten Thousand Sword's attack power might be reduced, but it wasn't like he was rooted or stunned. He continued to ready a counter attack and chased after Steamed Bun Invasion with a Downwind Sword Slash.

Steamed Bun's reaction speed was fast, but this Downwind Sword Slash had been timed perfectly and struck him.　　

Steamed Bun Invasion was hit and slid to the side. Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords immediately followed up with a Triple Slash, pursuing while also attacking at the same time, but who would have that thought as soon as Steamed Bun Invasion steadied himself, he would ricochet towards Ten Thousand Swords. Lin Yi was caught by surprise. He saw a sword light flash towards him. It was actually another Downwind Sword Slash that had come from Steamed Bun Invasion's Brawler this time. The priority on Triple Slash couldn't contest Downwind Sword Slash's priority. Not only was Ten Thousand Sword's momentum halted, he had been struck stumbling.

The stadium exploded into an uproar. Those who were a little slower might even be confused about Steamed Bun Invasion's class. How did he use Downwind Sword Slash too? Those who were faster had already recognized that this was the newly added Brawler skill: Tooth for Tooth.

Tooth for Tooth was an active ability. When attacked, the character would still take damage, but the character would remember which skill was used. That skill would appear on the character's skill list. The number of uses and the skill effects was determined by Tooth for Tooth's skill level. In addition, the amount of mana used for the skill would be double what it originally was.

Clearly, Steamed Bun Invasion had activated Tooth for Tooth earlier. When he was hit by Downwind Sword Slash, he remembered the skill and returned it back to its owner. From this point of view, another issue came up. He had used Tooth for Tooth, but he had also used Threaten beforehand, so the damage from the opponent's skill had been reduced when it struck. Thus, Steamed Bun Invasion's Downwind Sword Slash had also been reduced. Returning the strike had been a good move, but that previous Threaten still didn't make any sense.

But even so, the Downwind Sword Slash had caught Lin Yi off guard. Steamed Bun took this opportunity to strike back and begin his fierce assault.

Happy's fanclub's spirit revived at once . They shouted "Steamed Bun!" loudly and cheered for him, but at Happy's player seats, Sun Zheping had his brows furrowed. He was thinking back to that previous scene. It just so happened that the screen did a replay of Steamed Bun's counterattack. After looking at it again, Sun Zheping moved closer to Ye Xiu: "If that Threaten hadn't debuffed, then Downwind Sword Slash…...."

"Would have been faster and the knockback would be stronger. It would have sent Steamed Bun Invasion flying into the air after his Powerful Knee Strike missed. He would have been knocked back farther away, and he would have needed to Quick Recover. If he had used Downwind Sword Slash like that, he might not have gotten the same results." Ye Xiu said.

"So that guy..."　　

"Don't ask me if he did it on purpose. I have no idea either." Ye Xiu said. And this was why Steamed Bun's derailment playstyle was so terrifying. His completely unexpected move could be utter trash, but it could also be a brilliant turning point. When it was utter trash, you could laugh at it all you want, but when it became a turning point, it would be a deciding factor. And this deciding factor was impossible to defend against. Even someone as skilled as Sun Zheping needed to think about it after the event took place. When playing in a match, there was no time for so much thinking. How many people could instantly recognize the subtle involvement this move had?

The expression on Xiao Jie's face turned ugly when he saw Steamed Bun's counterattack. However, Lin Yi was a steady player. He quickly got out of Steamed Bun's assault and once again regained control of the situation. Steamed Bun's counterattack looked like one final desperate struggle. Xiao Jie let out a sigh of relief and glanced at Happy's side with delight. He saw Ye Xiu turn his head and look at him too. He immediately smiled: "He really knows how to surprise people!"

"And isn't that why he's so interesting?" Ye Xiu smiled.

"Yeah." Xiao Jie nodded his head. Suddenly, he heard a cry of surprise from the venue. Xiao Jie turned his head and saw that Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords was being slapped into the ground and beaten black and blue by Steamed Bun Invasion's Tyrannical Chain Punch.

What happened?

Xiao Jie was shocked. The situation had been stabilized just moments before. How did it flip all of a sudden?　　

It just so happened that the screen showed an instant replay.　　

Powerful Knee Strike. Another Powerful Knee Strike. This time, the distance between the two sides had been very close. Lin Yi's Ten Thousand Swords had been in the middle of a combo. He had used Headwind Strike, when Steamed Bun Invasion suddenly burst forth with a Powerful Knee Strike. Blood flew out from Steamed Bun Invasion as he slammed into the Headwind Strike head on. However, Steamed Bun Invasion forcefully broke through the sword prison just like that and followed up with a Tyrannical Chain Punch. The airborne Ten Thousand Swords crashed to the ground, following which was the current scene.

Xiao Jie was astonished.

For a final desperate struggle, it should be one last struggle. How could someone facing death do a final struggle again and again? If he kept on struggling, that only meant one thing. This person couldn't die.

Maybe claiming victory already really had been too early? Xiao Jie thought to himself, but he refused to accept it. In terms of equipment, they were stronger. In terms of players, they were more consistent. In terms of the situation on stage, they had always been winning. Just looking at their health bars, even though Steamed Bun Invasion had done two desperate struggles, he hadn't pulled it that much closer. He had taken Downwind Sword Slash full force. He had completely eaten a Headwind Strike too. The damage from Headwind Strike was quite high. In addition, Lin Yi had control of the situation for most of the battle. Ten Thousand Swords had 50% more health than Steamed Bun Invasion. Could Steamed Bun Invasion actually make a come back?

Impossible! Absolutely impossible!

Xiai Jie couldn't bother with going over to Happy and letting out a smile showing his superiority. He stared closely at the screen and saw their lead, yet he couldn't help but feel nervous.

Xiao Jie's nervousness was deserved. Steamed Bun started to slowly make a comeback. The steady Lin Yi was already having trouble controlling the fight. Whenever Steamed Bun went off the rails, he would always deal significant damage towards Ten Thousand Swords. Although Lin Yi was sometimes able to strike back, it wasn't as effective as Steamed Bun's attacks.

Xiao Jie became more and more uneasy. He was even somewhat angry. It looked like he wasn't happy with Lin Yi's performance. Unfortunately, his anger couldn't be transmitted into the fight. The health bars of the two characters grew closer and closer, bit by bit, all the way until both sides only had 8% health left.

Happy's fanclub had gone crazy. They took whatever they had that could make noise and started making as much noise as possible. Under Seven Field's lead, they cheered in unison "Steamed Bun!"

Steamed Bun didn't let them down. On the other hand, Lin Yi's performance was disappointing compared to the start of the fight. Jade Dyansty's fanclub was cheering on their team captain, but when Steamed Bun Invasion led with 5% health compared to Ten Thousand Sword's 3% health, they had trouble bearing it. He had such a huge lead, and he actually lost it?

But no matter if it was 5% health or 3% health, a single wave of attacks could end it for either sides. The match had reached this point. It just depended on who would grasp the final opportunity.

The fans on both sides and the players on both sides were standing up, staring closely at the match screen.　

Steamed Bun Invasion!

In the final moment, Steamed Bun Invasion once again made another strange, unconventional move, helping him grasp the final opportunity. Ten Thousand Swords only had 3% health left. He was unable to grasp the final opportunity. Steamed Bun Invasion had won the first round of the group arena.

"Oh oh oh oh oh!!!" Happy's fanclub cheered. The team also clapped in celebration. Jade Dynasty's side was rather quiet. However, this was a group arena, so with the other side only having 5% health remaining, from an overall perspective, it wasn't too bad. Even so, when Jade Dynasty's team captain, Lin Yi, came down from the stage, he was met with harsh rebuke from his boss, Xiao Jie.　　

"What was that? You had such a big lead, and your opponent actually turned it around? With that type of performance, what type of example are you setting for your teammates?"

"Sorry..." Lin Yi's face carried a trace of exhaustion, but he could only quietly accept the boss's fury.

Chapter 987: Who’s Mistake Was It

"What's with that guy?" Chen Guo couldn't bear Xiao Jie's behavior any longer.

If the match was played poorly, it was normal for post-match critique. It was just that when pointing out mistakes, it was best to console the player first and then calmly analyze why the match had gone the way it did. Everyone had their own way of communicating, but starting with criticism outright was no good.

Although Lin Yi lost the match, he had lowered his opponent's health down to 5%. That was still an acceptable result, However, he originally had complete control over the fight, but in the end, his opponent stole away the win. Such a fall was the true reason why Xiao Jie wasn't happy, which was why even though the outcome wasn't too bad, Lin Yi was still extremely indignant.

Chen Guo stopped watching. After all, this was the other team's matter. It wouldn't be good to butt in.

After being admonished, Lin Yi quietly sat to the side. The other players came over and patted his shoulders to console him.　　

As for Xiao Jie? After venting his anger, his mood seemed to have taken a turn for the better. He looked very satisfied with his strict way of handling the issue. He even had a smile on his face as he turned to say to Happy: "We actually lost with such a big lead. We've really made a fool of ourselves in front of God Ye."

"If it's just because of us making a comeback, you shouldn't blame him too much." Ye Xiu replied.

"What do you mean?" Xiao Jie said.　　

"If he had been picked to go first because you guys guessed that our first player would be Steamed Bun and specifically made preparations on dealing with him, then the person who arranged for him to go first should be the one responsible for bearing this loss." Ye Xiu said.　　

"What are you saying?" The expression on Xiao Jie's face changed.

Ye Xiu smiled. He had seen through it all. Usually, the team captain was responsible for the pick order. However, from Xiao Jie's bossy rebuke, it looked like the team owner not only guided the general direction of the team, he even interfered in the team's tactical arrangements.

An amateur leading experts was always a major fear. As for Xiao Jie, he couldn't be considered a complete amateur at Glory. After all, he had been a fan of Glory for so many years. Even if he hadn't eaten pork before, he had seen pigs run. Just because he didn't have pro-level technical skill, that didn't necessarily mean he didn't have pro-level tactics and theorycrafting. It was similar to how although a football coach might not be an outstanding football player, but the coach still had the qualifications to tell the team how to kick the ball. It was the same reasoning.

Since he was interfering with the team's matters, when something happened to the team, he should naturally have a clear idea of knowing where the problem lay. Was it because of a bad pick order or because of the player performing poorly?

Lin Yi lost the match. When he came down, he was yelled at by Xiao Jie. Chen Guo didn't like his conduct, but Ye Xiu didn't even put it in his eyes. Xiao Jie couldn't distinguish between right and wrong. Ye Xiu didn't know if Xiao Jie actually had the skill to control the team in such a manner, but from what he saw in the first match, if Lin Yi had been placed specifically to deal with Steamed Bun, then that had not been a wise move.

Sure enough, after pointing this out, the expression on Xiao Jie's face turned even uglier. It appeared that he really had been the one to make the arrangements, so when Lin Yi had control of the fight, he had been delighted, feeling that it was because of his own genius that allowed Lin Yi to suppress his opponent, but after a comeback was made, he suddenly became furious. He thought that Lin Yi failed to seize such a good opportunity. He had placed victory right before his eyes, yet Lin Yi couldn't even grab it. In his eyes, Lin Yi was utter trash.

But now, Ye Xiu actually said that it was problem with the pick order?

"What do you mean?" Xiao Jie glared at Ye Xiu. He didn't even act as polite like before.

"Judging Lin Yi to be Steamed Bun's bane is a mistake." Ye Xiu said.

"Based on what?" Xiao Jie called into question.

"Based on the results of that round." Ye Xiu smiled.

"What a joke." Xiao Jie sneered, "What does the outcome of a single round prove? What's more, Lin Yi had complete control of the match in the beginning. If he hadn't been careless....."

"Once is carelessness. Twice is carelessness, but being careless continuously? Have you not considered that there might be another reason for it?" Ye Xiu said.

"So you're saying that it was because of the pick order? Are you saying that he shouldn't be matched against an opponent that's too easy, so he won't easily underestimate his opponent?" Xiao Jie's voice was filled with ridicule.

"You should think about the specifics yourself!" Ye Xiu smiled. He didn't give him a detailed explanation.

"What? You don't know?" Xiao Jie sneered.

Ye Xiu said helplessly: "Don't tell me you're hoping that I'll help you analyze how to beat my team?"　　

"Then how about you enlighten me after we beat your team. When the time comes, it won't affect the big picture anymore." Xiao Jie said.

"You guys are going to need a lot of luck then." Ye Xiu said.

"Don't worry about it." Xiao Jie said coldly.

The current him had completely torn off his initial modesty. After this loss, his pride, his arrogance, and his conceit had been entirely revealed. From this perspective, Xiao Jie wasn't a sophisticated person. His ugly side took form with just a slight pull of the trigger.

On stage, the second round had already begun. A Ghostblade player from Jade Dynasty came out to battle. From a team composition perspective, Jade Dynasty had its own unique characteristics. Their team's main roster consisted of four swordsmen, a Berserker, a Blade Master, a Ghostblade, a Spellblade, as well as a healer.

This Ghostblade player was one of their main roster players. His character was called Anxious Ghost. He was a fairly standard Ghostblade player that walked the middle road, a Phantom Demon Sword Demon hybrid.

Steamed Bun's Steamed Bun Invasion only had 5% of his health left. The two sides clashed. Not waiting for anything surprising to happen, Anxious Ghost made quick work of him.

The previous round had a been a narrow victory over Lin Yi, but Happy's fanclub cheered as if Steamed Bun had done a 1v5. Nothing really happened this round and Steamed Bun was killed. Happy's fanclub immediately began jeering at him without mercy, and they even took something as unrealistic as a 1v5 to jab at him. It wasn't them being mean. It was because they viewed Steamed Bun as their friend, a brother who had once played with him in game. It was a form of teasing between bad friends.

Steamed Bun shook his head as he went down from the stage. He actually seemed a bit angry at his quick loss in the second round: "I only had that much health left. They didn't even give me some steamed buns to recover. Ai ai ai!"

Everyone on Happy's side laughed. They saw Steamed Bun sit down dejectedly. No one went over to console him though because everyone knew there was no need to. Sure enough, five seconds later, after hearing the fanclub's teasing, Steamed Bun turned his head and started chattering away. This guy even tried to climb over the wall between the players and the crowd, but the security guards stopped him.

The security guards were at a loss. They had seen fans rushing towards the player area, but they had never seen a player climb towards the fans. Was that in accordance with the rules? The security guards didn't know. They hadn't noticed in the rules whether a player was permitted to leave his seat and go to the audience. Who would think of doing such a thing?"

Not long after Steamed Bun went off stage, Team Happy's second player came up. It was coincidentally Team Happy's Ghostblade --- Qiao Yifan.

Qiao Yifan's Ghostblade, One Inch Ash, was a pure Phantom Demon though, which was a lot worse at 1v1s. He only had two pieces of Silver equipment too, while Team Jade Dynasty's Anxious Ghost was the same as their captain's Ten Thousand Swords. Anxious Ghost had seven pieces of Silver equipment. From just their characters, One Inch Ash was at a fairly large disadvantage.

But in terms of player skill, Qiao Yifan was much more consistent than Tang Rou and Steamed Bun. He had come from a champion team too, so he had solid fundamentals. Even if Team Tiny Herb never gave him a chance to play in a match, just from their practice quality, how could a team like Jade Dynasty, which had been relegated for so many years, compare to a champion team?

Moreover, after receiving wholehearted guidance from a God like Ye Xiu, his class change was a huge success. At this point, Qiao Yifan could already clearly feel the advantages from changing classes. He was like a fish swimming in water. His intuition and awareness were like a match made in heaven with Phantom Demons. He had never felt such comfortableness and freedom when he had played as an Assassin on Team Tiny Herb. As his skill level increased, this feeling of comfort became even stronger. Qiao Yifan simply loved this class too much.

His control over the class had reached a point where his character would move however he wished it to. For Qiao Yifan, it greatly made up for his confidence, which he had always been lacking. He no longer doubted himself. He firmly believed that he would become an outstanding pro player.　　

The fight began. Team Jade Dynasty's Anxious Ghost raised his sword and charged over. In the previous fight, he made quick work of the nearly dead Steamed Bun Invasion. Victory had been easy. It wasn't enough. The current him was in high spirits. His thirst for battle was also extremely fierce. He hated how he couldn't immediately start clashing with his opponent and fight a real battle.

Qiao Yifan did not directly rush towards Anxious Ghost and instead took a different path. He began circling around from the side. This battle would begin with an ambush from one side.

It had to be said that Qiao Yifan's difficult practice for half a year as an Assassin had helped him grasp the techniques of an Assassin. For example, a sneak attack was something that Assassins needed to be proficient at. Qiao Yifan wasn't great, but he had tried his best the entire time. His grasp of it might not be very high-level, but it was at least very solid. He wouldn't lose it just because he had changed classes. The Phantom Demon One Inch Ash's sneak attack route was extremely precise. He circled around diagonally. When he showed his head, he was already behind Anxious Ghost.

"Idiot! Behind you!" Seeing this scene, Xiao Jie suddenly cursed anxiously.

Qiao Yifan wasn't in a hurry to attack. He hid himself behind Anxious Ghost, observing his movements.

Chapter 988: Ghost Feast

Those who had been following Happy's matches all felt that this moment was very familiar. In the match against Mysterious Fantasy, Happy's Mo Fan and his Deception had followed their opponent in the same patient, careful manner, waiting for the perfect chance to strike suddenly. After gaining the upper hand, he didn't linger, but quickly retreated, before repeating this process over and over until his opponent was dead.

Seeing Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash also quietly sneaking behind his opponent, everyone couldn't help but remember the match that day. Though it was a different player, they were from the same team, so they might use similar playstyles. If that were true, then that would make things very boring, no?

Boos rose from the crowd. It was evident that Mo Fan's playstyle wasn't liked. If you managed to burst your opponent in a sneak attack, that would be pretty great to watch, but Mo Fan's repetitive playstyle, always doing a hasty retreat just as the match was coming to a crescendo, might have been familiar and comfortable to him, but the audience was always denied that last breath of relief because of his rhythm, and held it in uncomfortably.

With this experience in their minds, and seeing Qiao Yifan seemingly about to do the same thing, the crowd loudly expressed their displeasure.

Amidst the boos, Xiao Jie glanced over at Happy; now, he wasn't nervous anymore. This sort of stalling playstyle was rather annoying. However, this was a group arena and not an individual competition, so every player had the chance to fight multiple players. And this sort of stalling playstyle, while not very fun to watch, tested a player's skill and required them to expend a lot of concentration. In the group arena, players couldn't only focus on defeating their current opponent if they wanted their team to win. They also had to conserve as much energy as possible while defeating their current opponent, so as to do as much damage as possible to the next opponent. Therefore, this sort of playstyle that required a player to expend a lot of mental energy wasn't very appropriate for the group arena.

As if hearing the crowd's boos, the Jade Dynasty player onstage suddenly went on high alert.

　　

After rushing through a good portion of the map and not seeing the opponent, you would usually realize the other planned to ambush you. This was a very common tactic, but for Happy, they needed to be more careful. This was because they had Deception's endless stalking and Windward Formation's shameless and dirty hiding and sneaking. Both were rather disgusting to deal with.

　

But with Mysterious Fantasy testing out the waters for them, Jade Dynasty's players were prepared for this. Upon realizing that the opponent had such intentions, they didn't panic, instead heading resolutely towards Team Happy's spawn point. This was thanks to the experience they got from the match Happy had with Mysterious Fantasy. This was to prevent the other from finding some random place to huddle up and making them waste their energy and time for nothing.

Seeing his team's player reacting so quickly and accurately, Xiao Jie nodded in satisfaction. They had done careful planning on going up against Happy, and this sort of situation was the kind they put the most thought into. The decision the Ghostblade player had made was in accordance with Xiao Jie's thoughts, making him feel secure. Even though One Inch Ash wasn't huddled away at the spawn point, there would be no problem, so long as they followed the current strategy.

Just as Xiao Jie was thinking this, a blade flashed on the field and Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash attacked.

　

Although Jade Dynasty's player had prepared to head off to the spawn point to check, that didn't mean he had let his guard down. Qiao Yifan's sneak attack wasn't very well timed and Anxious Ghost rolled, easily dodging the strike. While he got up, he sent a Moonlight Slash back.

One Inch Ash jumped backwards to dodge, and the flash of energy swept past the tip of his nose. Anxious Ghost followed up with a Full Moonlight Slash. Moonlight Slash and Full Moonlight Slash were two different skills, but since the combination of the skills was cool and practical, one would follow the other more or less eighty percent of the time, as if they were two parts of the same skill.

One Inch Ash had dodged the Moonlight Slash, but was struck by this Full Moonlight Slash. After receiving the blowback, he rolled twice before managing to quick recover and steadied himself. Seeing Anxious Ghost approaching, blade in hand, he turned and ran.

"Hahaha." Seeing this, Xiao Jie immediately laughed aloud. This was exactly what failing to steal a chicken and losing a handful of rice* was, in his eyes. This ambush of Happy's was too weak. Not only did he fail to gain the upperhand, but he also fell into a disadvantageous position and was now being chased by their player. Xiao Jie was inwardly delighted and involuntarily glanced over at Happy.

Xiao Jie hoped that Happy's members would display a bit of anxiety on their faces! Yet when he turned to look, they were all sitting calmly as if waiting for a fish to bite, especially Ye Xiu, who was even smiling!

Xiao Jie wanted to say something, but seeing how no one turned to pay him any attention, he held back.

　

On the field, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash turned and darted into a small alleyway nearby. The map they were on was an ancient town. Under the fading light of the setting sun, One Inch Ash immediately turned upon entering the alleyway. His shadow was still stretched out and left behind him. When Anxious Ghost charged over, he immediately saw this and sped up to give chase.

"Tsk tsk, the small details are what decides victory!" Xiao Jie lamented. The current match, Happy versus Jade Dynasty, was being streamed. Currently, the different angles and shots included the streaked one. Just now, they had given a close up of the lengthy shadow stretched out behind One Inch Ash and the commentator was analyzing the mistake made by Qiao Yifan.

"You should have your back to the setting sun, not your face…" The commentator expressed. Yet he saw One Inch Ash stop, huddling behind a wall and setting down a Sword Boundary to increase his strength and intelligence, preparing his ambush.

"This… I believe that Jade Dynasty's player couldn't possibly not be ready for this." The commentator said with confidence. Using the corner to make a sneak attack was a commonly employed tactic, so how could a pro player not be prepared for such a happening?

As expected, Jade Dynasty's Anxious Ghost didn't walk along the wall when he came in pursuit, but used an extra two steps to send himself into a rather large pathing curve. This way, he could gain some distance and guard against an ambush. What pro player wouldn't know to do this?

Even so, One Inch Ash's tachi still swung up, a Moonlight Slash was sent at Anxious Ghost, character and sword flying at him.

"Tsk tsk, this ambush…" The commentator was about to comment on this ambush and Qiao Yifan's attack from before and how childish they were, but Anxious Ghost seemed to have become dumbstruck, lifting the tachi in hand, but not seeming to know what he was doing. One Inch Ash's Moonlight Slash struck its target.

After Moonlight Slash was a Full Moonlight Slash, the same combo, expect that Qiao Yifan followed the knockback effect with a Ghost Slash. Anxious Ghost's momentum in the air immediately increased, like a cannonball, flying head first into the mud. The Jade Dynasty player quick recovered, making Anxious Ghost's original head-into-the-ground into a diving forward roll. As he rolled, he turned. A flash of energy from his sword darted out from beneath his arm, sending out a Sword Draw as he got up.

Yet, the sword struck air since One Inch Ash hadn't even approached him. Over there, the edge of the blade was unsheathed and the power of Phantom Ghosts flowed out and under. Two consecutive Boundaries were cast.

　

The commentator was really busy now! Not only did he have to analyze the situation at hand, he was inwardly wondering how Anxious Ghost had been successfully sneak attacked by One Inch Ash just now. It shouldn't have been! Such a simple ambush, even he could dodge it if he were up there, no?

　

However, the two sides were locked in intense battle now, so there was no time to replay the previous scene. The commentator could only pay attention to the current happenings. Yet as he stared at the match and continued to speak and speak, he spoke until he was struck dumb by his own words...

　　

"Happy's One Inch Ash has lain his fourth Ghost Boundary, turning this small area into a Ghost Boundary encyclopedia. Jade Dynasty's Anxious Ghost doesn't seem to be able to do much. High walls surround his left, right, and back. The only escape route is blocked by One Inch Ash. Take a look, everyone, One Inch Ash hasn't thrown all his Ghost Boundaries in a pile together. There are layers to this arrangement. This way, if Anxious Ghost tries to charge out, he'll be stopped by one of the layers of Ghost Boundaries, making it hard to get a good rhythm down and making things easier for One Inch Ash. Sword Draw! Oh, Anxious Ghost still maintains a very good reaction speed, he dodged it. Huh? What's he trying to do… Anxious Ghost keeps moving forward, but that's a wall over there! Oh, he bumped into the wall. Oh, it's the Seed of Darkness, or the Dark Boundary, as it's more commonly known. Sorry, there's too many interwoven Ghost Boundaries that even I didn't notice it. When did One Inch Ash lay it down? Anyways, Anxious Ghost stepped into the Dark Boundary, and he couldn't see under its blinding effects, so he ended up walking into a wall… this… seems rather ugly…"

"Dark Boundary's effects have worn off, Anxious Ghost turns… Wow, he's frozen now, an Ice Boundary…"

"One Inch Ash has the absolute advantage here. To be honest, I want to just announce his victory now, but the happenings from before taught me a lesson, so let's finish watching the match first." The commentator continued to analyze the situation and even made a joke about himself. Last match, the commentator hadn't been able to help announcing Lin Yi would win, but ended up getting his face slapped. So, in this match, he didn't dare jump to any conclusions though Qiao Yifan had the absolute advantage.

　

"Anxious Ghost has been trapped there by One Inch Ash, unable to escape. Happy's player has used the terrain to its fullest, perfectly utilizing the advantages of a Ghostblade. Okay, now the scene we're giving everyone is One Inch Ash's skill situation. We have the production director to thank for capturing this scene. Look, everyone, all of One Inch Ash's Boundaries are currently in use. All of the Ghost Boundaries in his skill build are currently on cooldown. Seeing the rotation of these cooldowns, doesn't everyone think this is a beautiful rhythm? I feel like if there was some music to go with it, it would be even better."

"Oh, One Inch Ash has quickened his pace, sending out all his Ghost Boundaries. Now, there are a total of, one, two, three, four, five… Sorry, everyone, I can't seem to make it out clearly either, but with One Inch Ash sending out all these Boundaries, does he want…"

"Ghost Feast!!!"

"Amazing, One Inch Ash has activated Ghost Feast, making all the Ghost Boundaries erupt, immediately taking the rest of Anxious Ghost's health with them. One Inch Ash won! What a beautiful victory!" The commentator yelled, forgetting his composure.

Chapter 989: The Cautious Qiao Yifan

Amidst the silence, someone from the crowd started clapping, which quickly spread until applause erupted around the entire stadium.

Happy didn't have that many fans. There were even quite a few people who didn't like them. However, even people who had well-defined likes and dislikes appreciated brilliant performances. Everyone had seen Qiao Yifan's prowess in this fight on the jumbotron in front of them. Such a convincing performance truly deserved such wild applause.

They now had a completely different view of that rash and initial sneak attack. It was without question to lure the opponent into his trap. Its purpose was to draw Anxious Ghost into the necessary position.

"Friends, I don't think you guys have forgotten about the sneak attack from the corner. Let's take a look at it again." When the commentator reviewed the match, he impatiently had the stream cut to that moment.　　

The clip had already been prepared. However, the fight never stopped, continuing all the way until Anxious Ghost was killed. As a result, there had been no time to show the replay. It could finally be played now. Everyone watched the scene again from Anxious Ghost's perspective.

When Anxious Ghost chased after One Inch Ash to this little alleyway, One Inch Ash had already disappeared. However, at the corner of the street, a shadow extended on the ground. Anxious Ghost noticed it and immediately ran towards it. Before he reached the corner, he moved in an arc, putting distance between the two before rushing forward to attack One Inch Ash, who had been lying in wait.

The twilight from the setting sun shone down, making things seem real, yet unreal at the same time. From Anxious Ghost's point of view, only One Inch Ash could be seen. The swordlight had been completely hidden by the setting sun. Anxious Ghost wasn't able to see the attack coming. Then, he was thrown into a corner until his defeat.

"So it was like that..." the commentator gasped in admiration, "Happy's player cleverly positioned himself so that the sunlight directly shone on him and covered his attack. Everyone paid attention. One Inch Ash jumped when he let loose a Moonlight Slash. This jump put this swordlight in a position, where the sunlight would also conceal it. Everything had been planned accordingly. Happy had a clear strategy going into this battle. I'm sure everyone knows that even though the maps used in these matches are temporary, once the League started, all of the maps were available for download and use. The maps used in every match are announced beforehand so that the teams can prepare ahead of time. From the looks of it, Happy has put a lot of work in this area. What about Jade Dynasty? The player was also a Ghostblade. Even though he's a hybrid Phantom Sword Demon, he could have taken advantage of the map too, yet he didn't notice this point."

"That victory was beautiful. Let's all remember this player's name. Qiao Yifan! He truly should come out and accept our applause. Unfortunately, this is a group arena. He still needs to continue playing, but worry not. There's still a long road ahead of him. I believe that this player certainly has a bright future ahead of him. Speaking of which, Qiao Yifan was originally from Team Tiny Herb. For some reason, he never appeared on stage with them and left after being there for a season. Seeing Qiao Yifan's performance today, I wonder if Team Tiny Herb is going to regret their decision."

Amid the commentator's praise and the crowd's applause, Team Jade Dynasty's defeated player came down from the stage. The praise and applause was for Qiao Yifan. For him, it only made it that much harder to bear. He walked very slowly as if he didn't want to go back to the player bench. Their boss, Xiao Jie, was sitting down with a dark face. Seeing his player coming down slowly, he snorted coldly and ignored him. He called over Team Jade Dynasty's third player.

"Be more mindful. The opponent has a strong grasp of the maps. Be careful and don't make the same mistakes. And..." Xiao Jie instructed impatiently.

"I understand." The third player was Zheng Shengchao, a Berserker. His character Severed Yearning. After being given sincere advice from Xiao Jie, he headed towards the stage.

The third round began. The current situation was very unfavorable towards Jade Dynasty. One Inch Ash had consumed lots of mana, but he had only lost 20% of his health in the previous round. Happy had nearly a one person lead over Jade Dynasty. Even with a disadvantage, Xiao Jie was sat quite upright. He didn't smile as he turned his head over and talked to Ye Xiu.

The match began. Due to Qiao Yifan's outstanding performance in the previous round, the commentator couldn't help but reveal a bit of bias towards him. At the start, he talked about what Qiao Yifan might do since he wasn't at full health and he didn't have much mana left. After his concern for Qiao Yifan, he introduced Jade Dynasty's player, Zheng Shengchao.

It was somewhat awkward for Berserkers to play in group arenas because of their signature skill Blood Awakening, creating the unique health-trading playstyle. Because of how trading health changed the pace of the match, it made things too difficult for Berserkers. In a 1v1, they could easily make this decision, but in a group arena, if they traded away their health cleanly, how were they going to take down more than one opponent? Although Berserkers became stronger the lower their health, they weren't so strong that they could just instantly kill an opponent. Directly trade away 90% of their health at the start? That wasn't how trading worked. When they traded their health, they would lower their opponent's health to around the same range. If a Berserker's health was low, but the opponent's health was high, don't think that was the Berserker trading away his health. Ninety nine percent of the time it was just the Berserker getting destroyed…..

Their class's feature made it challenging for them to participate in the group arena, especially when the opposing side held the lead.

Xiao Jie sincerely instructed his team's Berserker, but his expression was still grave and stern. He clearly knew what a predicament they were in.

They knew. Qiao Yifan knew even better. It could be seen that from his previous performance, Qiao Yifan had made ample preparations beforehand. He had taken it very seriously and played very carefully. He had even taken note of the sunlight at the corner of the street and utilized it to his advantage. How could he not have been prepared for his current situation?

Zheng Shengchao didn't hurry and search for One Inch Ash. Qiao Yifan also didn't go on the defensive to protect his lead. The two cautiously and patiently looked for opportunities.

Xiao Jie couldn't help but feel somewhat fretful upon seeing this scene.　

He had figured that the other side would be more proactive and bold because of his lead. Certain decisions that might not be considered under normal circumstances might be made as a result. After all, he had a health lead as a backup! Thus, he had instructed Zheng Shengchao to take advantage of the other side's mentality.

But from the looks of it, the other side didn't have that sort of mentality. Xiao Jie couldn't help but feel doubtful. In the previous round, Qiao Yifan had taken the initiative and lured his opponent into a trap, but in this round, he had actually become more careful. Let alone boldy attempting it when there was a thirty percent chance, the current Qiao Yifan turned a blind eye to even a fifty sixty percent chance. He was looking for an even more certain opportunity.

Xiao Jie's prediction was completely wrong. He couldn't help but feel unhappy. On stage, Zheng Shengchao had long since noticed this point. After some more careful probing, he decided to abandon Xiao Jie's advice. The other side wasn't falling for it.

Unable to bait the opponent, Zheng Shengchao could only search for an opportunity to forcefully break through to the opponent, but Qiao Yifan refused to face him directly. Qiao Yifan weaved in and out of the alleys as if it was his own home.

Zheng Shengchao was puzzled. It was a new map for both sides. How come the other side was so familiar with it? How could he know this map like back of his hand?

Zheng Shengchao, who had been chasing him the entire time, was starting to become impatient. Every time he reached a corner, he lifted his head to see where the sun was. He had to think about whether that place might have traps set, a dead end, or if it could be completely sealed off by ghost boundaries. Because of all the thinking he needed to do, he often lost his target, making him feel even more annoyed.

"Are you planning on running around until you recover all of your mana?" Zheng Shengchao couldn't bear it anymore and spoke to the other side through the all chat. Glory characters had basic health and mana recovery, but it was very very slow in real combat. If not, wouldn't the matches go on forever? Zheng Shengchao knew the other side didn't have that goal in mind. These words were purely to provoke him.

At Happy's benches, Ye Xiu actually went over to ask Chen Guo: "Did Yifan bring recovery equipment into the game?"

"Do you think everyone thinks like you do?' Chen Guo felt hopeless.

Ye Xiu had done this before, but it had actually been a very bold move. Bringing two sets of equipment increased the character's weight significantly. Fighting would feel different. It was hard to say if bringing an extra set of equipment was actually helpful or harmful, so the switching-equipment playstyle only lasted a short while before becoming nonexistent. It was considered okay to bring one or two extra pieces of equipment, but the end result of carrying two full sets of equipment might just be dragging the character to their own death.

Even Ye Xiu only dared to do so against Team Everlasting. If he had to compete against similar-level experts, he would need to carefully ponder over it.

"I feel like with Yifan's skill level, bringing an extras set is still quite reasonable!" Wei Chen gave an enthusiastic thumbs up. His words meant that Qiao Yifan had the ability to toy around with Jade Dynasty's player.

"Do you really think Yifan's as shameless and unscrupulous as you guys?" Chen Guo was about to go crazy.

"I think it's just because Yifan's rather cautious." Ye Xiu said.

"Yeah yeah, he's probably overestimating these Jade Dynasty players." Wei Chen said.

"We also figured that Jade Dynasty was hiding their strength." Ye Xiu said.

"Yes, that's right. If it wasn't for that, he would definitely have brought another set of equipment." Wei Chen said.

"Yeah, he definitely would have." Ye Xiu nodded his head.　　

"Get out of here! You two, f*ck off!!" Chen Guo yelled.

Chapter 990: Remaining Mana

Ye Xiu and the others were all joking around off stage, while Qiao Yifan, on stage, was completely unaffected by his opponent's taunting. Jade Dynasty's Zheng Shengchao had no idea as to where One Inch Ash was or where he was heading, but the audience could clearly see how One Inch Ash was darting in and out of the alleyways with familiarity.

This sort of playstyle was usually very unpopular, but because of Qiao Yifan's brilliant performance last match, the audience's tolerance for Qiao Yifan's playstyle had obviously become very high. Even the commentator was praising Qiao Yifan's patience, saying that it was rare that someone kept such a cool head when they were in the lead by a full player in the group arena.

"Ok, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash has once again managed to sneak behind Severed Yearning once again. Will he manage to grasp an opportunity this time?" The commentator kept his eyes on the match.

"He's approached, but this position doesn't seem very appropriate for a Ghostblade's ambush. Let's see what Qiao Yifan will do!"

"Oh, he's laid down a Ghost Boundary."

"It's a Flame Boundary. Seems like Qiao Yifan also knows that this environment isn't too great for Ghost Boundaries, so he's aiming to deal damage."

"Jade Dynasty's player noticed, turned around, Collapsing Mountain!!! He has a very fast reaction speed. It looks like Zheng Shengchao was waiting for One Inch Ash to strike."

"Qiao Yifan has backed away. Seems like he felt that this opportunity wasn't a very good one. However, it's obvious that Zheng Shengchao isn't willing to let Qiao Yifan go so easily this time, and he's pursuing. Exchanges like this have happened several times already and Qiao Yifan has continuously managed to slip away, utilizing his familiarity with the map. However, this time… It seems like Zheng Shangchao has gained a better understanding of the map during the match. He refuses to be shaken off."

　

"Huh…? This place…" The commentator made a questioning sound before he started to become excited. The broadcast very cooperatively flashed to the area the commentator had noticed. The audience looked over, and immediately understood the commentator's excitement. This area had a very similar terrain to where Qiao Yifan killed his last opponent.

A brilliant performance was about to follow! The audience perked up, and some even began applauding. As for Team Happy's supporters, they had already begun to cheer and yell with excitement.

Jade Dynasty's members were extremely anxious at this moment. It didn't feel good to be spectating this at all. They could only watch as their teammate fell into the opponent's trap, but were helpless to do anything about it. Half of Jade Dynasty's players had even stood up, but their boss, Xiao Jie, was still sitting, unmoving, though his own anxiety was evident. His gaze even revealed a hint of rage, clearly unhappy at how his players were continuously falling for their opponent's tricks.

　　

Under the eyes of the people, Zheng Chaosheng didn't fail their expectations. His Severed Yearning took that final step.

A Ghost Boundary practically matched the timing for this step, coming down on Severed Yearning's head. Qiao Yifan had perfectly timed the skill, beginning to cast it beforehand, and just finishing the cast with this step.

Zheng Shengchao was shocked, but didn't panic. He wanted nothing more than for Qiao Yifan to stop and face him head on! With a Colliding Stab, Severed Yearning charged at One Inch Ash. One Inch Ash whirled around in a dodge, bounding to switch of positions with Severed Yearning.

After the Colliding Stab, Severed Yearning spun around and Zheng Shengchao only noticed the terrain of his environment then. His heart missed a beat, feeling dread rising. However, he was already trapped in a Ghost Boundary and One Inch Ash swung the Taichi in his hand, Ghost Boundaries came down one after another. The audience yelled and cheered, abandoning all pretense, while Jade Dynasty's players all felt like crying.

Zheng Shengchao struggled, wanting to break out of the encirclement of Ghost Boundaries, yet was met with failure after failure.

Compared to the Ghostblade of last round, Berserkers were a lot better at breaking through, but didn't have nearly as high of a resistance to the effects of Ghost Boundaries. Falling into a CC chain like this was much more troublesome for Zheng Shengchao than for the last match's Ghostblade player. Severed Yearning's life dropped constantly, the audience applauded thunderously, Jade Dynasty's players sat silently and boss Xiao Jie's expression made him look like he was ready to eat someone.

"Qiao Yifan has done it yet again, an amazing performance. However, this sort of playstyle consumes a lot of mana, so it seems that this time he won't be able to wipe out his opponent. That's perfectly fine though; being able to expend all your mana in the group arena means you've truly done everything you can. Qiao Yifan has reached this limit wonderfully. If Happy wins the group arena, then Qiao Yifan would've made the greatest contribution!" The commentator kept praising Qiao Yifan's performance, noticing, at the same time, that One Inch Ash's mana might not be enough and therefore wouldn't be able to keep up this playstyle of layering Ghost Boundaries in excess.

"Ah! So close…." A split second after the commentator finished analyzing the situation, he gave a cry from a sudden change on the field. Meanwhile, the audience suddenly gave a loud collective sigh at the same time.

"Severed Yearning almost charged out of One Inch Ash's encirclement. Though Jade Dynasty's player fell into a trap, it seems like he hasn't given up yet, seeking opportunities whenever he can." The commentator, having almost focused completely on One Inch Ash, finally decided to spare a few thoughts for Zheng Shengchao.

"Uh… Qiao Yifan's control seems to be too spread out this time!" Seeing the two's exchange on the field, the commentator suddenly came up with this comment.

Compared to the complete control of the match, Zheng Shengchao's Severed Yearning could still find some opportunity to try and break away from the control. Though he hadn't succeeded, he wasn't losing as badly as One Inch Ash's previous opponent.

"I feel like… Qiao Yifan might be thinking too much. Seems like he's controlling his rhythm on purpose to not completely deplete his mana so quickly. However, this leaves room for his opponent to struggle. Actually, in a situation where he has such an advantage, why doesn't Qiao Yifan just use up the rest of his mana to maximize his damage? I doubt anyone would be disappointed in him if he eventually lost the match," the commentator said with some confusion and disappointment.

Just as his words fell, the two on the field began their first ever head on exchange. Zheng Shengchao might not have been able to break through, but was able to deal a lot of damage to One Inch Ash.

"Qiao Yifan won't be wiped out before even depleting his mana, right? That would be such a shame… Qiao Yifan… he demands too much of himself…" Seeing how Zheng Shengchao gained the upper hand in this exchange, the commentator began to worry.

"Again! It seems like Zheng Shengchao is very confident in himself."

　

"Dark Boundary! This Dark Boundary was very timely, otherwise he might really be able to hold on against this barrage. I hope Qiao Yifan can take advantage of this opportunity and regain control over the situation…"

Yet Qiao Yifan didn't accomplish what the commentator was hoping for, continuing to stubbornly keep his slow rhythm and not depleting his mana to set Ghost Boundaries like in the previous match.

"If it's just like this… I feel like there would be no need for this trap. I think Zheng Shengchao would be more than willing to just fight Qiao Yifan head-on, right?" The more he spoke, the more the commentator felt disappointed in Qiao Yifan's actions this round.

"Zheng Shengchao is getting more and more confident as he fights, his status is at its peak." Slowly, the commentator's attention began to shift to Jade Dynasty's player.

"Blood Sword, Destruction Slash, brilliant! Soul-Devouring Crimson Grip, missed, what a shame. If that grab hit, it would have changed the situation completely. Zheng Shengchao's Severed Yearning might not have broken through, but he has gained the upperhand now, unleashing his own barrage of attacks. Qiao Yifan is struggling to endure. Under a situation where he originally held the upper hand, Qiao Yifan didn't utilize his Ghost Boundaries to their fullest, so One Inch Ash lost a lot of health as well, with only ten percent remaining. Now, what he is about to face is an even fiercer offense from his opponent because Blood Awakening has now been activated…"

"Wait, it's been activated…" The commentator suddenly realized something was wrong upon coming to this. He was dumbstruck for a long while and it wasn't until the two on the field engaged with one another that he noticed the health of each character falling and suddenly realized: Severed Yearning's Blood Awakening had already been activated because his health had already fallen by more than 50 percent, and this all happened without any fanfare. All he had noticed was Qiao Yifan's hardship in taking these attacks, but he hadn't noticed how Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had been quietly chipping away at his opponent's health all of this time.

That's right. This wave of damage wasn't nearly as elegant and consistent as the last match. However, if he was as liberal with his mana and consumed it like he did in the last match, how much damage would he be able to do with the little mana he had left?

Yet now, using the head-on exchanges, One Inch Ash might've lost a lot of health, but he had also drained Severed Yearning's health by quite a bit, but how much mana had One Inch Ash used during this fight?

Ten percent!

He had only used ten percent, ten percent of his mana to take over fifty percent of his opponent's health. This was a shocking result, and One Inch Ash had taken a lot of damage to achieve it. Though he still had almost twenty percent of his mana left now, he only had ten percent of his health. He might've been able to save some mana, but did he have enough health to use it?

Just as these doubts arose in the commentator, he suddenly understood.

　　

"It's coming!!!"

Thus, all the people watching the broadcast heard the commentator abruptly say these words.

What was coming? Just as the audience was lost in their confusion, One Inch Ash suddenly sped up the pace, Ghost Boundaries flashed continuously all over the field. This extravagant scene had One Inch Ash's mana plummeting, yet at the same time it quickly depleted Severed Yearning's health as well.

"It's enough! Qiao Yifan's remaining mana is enough to wipe out Severed Yearning. Severed Yearning is a Berserker, so he doesn't have the same resistance to Ghost Boundaries that the Ghostblade from last match had, so Ghost Boundaries deal significantly more damage to him. Qiao Yifan's remaining mana will be enough to take him out." The commentator quickly shared his findings then, but he had forgotten that the previous analysis was all in his head. Suddenly announcing this made the audience extremely confused.

However, the current situation on the field became the best annotation for the commentator's words. One Inch Ash completely took back control as he sped up without warning. Severed Yearning, who had seemingly taken control of the field for a while, was immediately drowned in Ghost Boundaries. He couldn't orientate himself or find a way out. His health depleted rapidly. His blood may have awakened, but there was no place to utilize it. He was securely locked in One Inch Ash's Ghost Boundaries.

　

Finally, One Inch Ash's mana was no more, and with the last powerful skill that consumed it, Severed Yearning's life was gone, too.

Qiao Yifan had successfully taken out his second opponent.

Chapter 991: The Older the Wiser

The system announced One Inch Ash's victory, but the stadium was completely silent.

The final turnaround had happened too quickly. Everyone had yet to comprehend what had transpired. The vast majority of the viewers as well as the commentator felt like Qiao Yifan had been playing way too cautiously. He had lured the opponent into a trap, but he failed to perfectly restrict the opponent. The viewers and the commentator had overlooked the fact that, while Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash lost a huge amount of health, he also successfully lowered his opponent's health.

The commentator explained how Qiao Yifan played this match, waking up the viewers watching the stream. However, the stadium didn't have a commentator speaking. Amidst the silence, everyone watched as Team Jade Dynasty's player Zhao Shengchao stood up and walked down from the stage.

In any case, Happy had won again. There was no need doubt about it. As a result, the first to react were Happy's supporters. Even if they didn't understand the contents of the match, just the result deserved applause.

Zheng Shengchao received the cold-shoulder like the previous player. The boss, Xiao Jie, ignored him. Zheng Shengchao sat down nervously. The fourth player went over to Xiao Jie for instructions, but he saw Xiao Jie wave his hands at him with a look of disgust. He didn't say anything and sent him away.

Xiao Jie used silence to express his displeasure with his players. The fourth player was Jade Dynasty's fourth swordsman. His opponent was still Qiao Yifan, except Qiao Yifan's character One Inch Ash only had 10% of his health left. He was nearly out of mana too. Even so, this Spellblade still felt fearful.

This time, Qiao Yifan didn't drag the fight on. One Inch Ash headed straight for his opponent. Without any mana, One Inch Ash couldn't use any skills. He could only use basic attacks. Not long afterwards, the opponent killed him.　

Qiao Yifan lost. He got up from his seat and got ready to leave the stage. This time, the stadium wasn't confused. They didn't hesitate and applauded wildly.

Even if many of them weren't able to understand the contents of the previous match, Qiao Yifan finishing a 1v2 in the group arena was clear as day. For a Phantom Demon, which did not excel even at 1v1s, being able to accomplish this was very impressive. The applause towards Qiao Yifan wasn't lacking.

As Qiao Yifan left the stage, he heard the thunderous applause and felt a bit dazed. Once he confirmed that the applause was for him, the formerly invisible Qiao Yifan felt moved. When he looked towards his team, his teammates also stood up and welcomed him with applause. Qiao Yifan felt moved once again. He also felt somewhat embarrassed. He rushed off the stage and walked over to his teammates.

"How does a 1v2 feel?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Pretty good." Qiao Yifan scratched his head. The smile on his face brimmed with happiness.

"Take a break. Watch us next." Ye Xiu smiled.　　

"Mm." Qiao Yifan nodded his head. He and everyone else returned to their bench. Team Happy's third player didn't immediately take his baton though.

"Old Wei?" Ye Xi looked around. He discovered that Wei Chen was at the very corner of their player bench. His head was buried in his arms, and he was scrunched up like a ball. Who knew what he was doing.

"Wait wait. Let me finish smoking." Wei Chen raised his head. He let out two puffs of smoke from his mouth. Chen Guo was furious when she saw this! The stadium was a public venue. Smoking was not allowed inside. However, this guy had hidden himself in a corner to grab a smoke. Chen Guo didn't know what to say. As the oldest in Team Happy, Wei Chen truly wasn't a role model for his peers.

After breathing in two puffs of smoke, Wei Chen clapped his hands and stood up. Who knew where his cigarette had gone off to. He walked over boldly and nodded his head fiercely at Qiao Yifan: "Little Fan, you played pretty well."

"Haha..." Qiao Yifan laughed foolishly.

"Watch me next." Wei Chen's arrogance pierced the heavens as he spoke.

Chen Guo didn't even say "Good luck!" to this guy.

Wei Chen didn't need this kind of encouragement. He walked onto the stage high and mightily. The stadium clapped out of politeness towards the next player. Then, they saw this guy wave his hands to send his greetings. He looked like he was enjoying it very much up until the applause died down. Only then did he finally climb onto the stage.

Soon afterwards, the next round of the group arena began. Team Jade Dynasty's Spellblade versus Wei Chen's Warlock, Windward Formation.

"Okay, I'll give you three minutes to come find me! If you can't find me, you should just forfeit!" As soon as the match started, the first thing Wei Chen did was type this into the all chat.

Jade Dynasty's player ignored him.

In that match, Mysterious Fantasy forfeited to Wei Chen because that point didn't even matter to them. In fact, that forfeit actually raised their team's morale. It was a trade off for better psychological stability. In this group arena, no matter how lacking a team's morale was, it didn't make sense to directly forfeit.

Everyone treated Wei Chen's words as psychological warfare. No one took it seriously, but in the next second, everyone actually saw Wei Chen's Windward Formation decisively run into a corner. This guy had actually started hiding.

The crowd went into an uproar. All sorts of rowdy jeering and whistling sounded. There was even some applause, but it sounded very weird. The applause was clearly a sarcastic one.

Chen Guo felt so ashamed that she wanted to crawl under the seats because Qiao Yifna's outstanding performance had helped Happy win a lot of fans. Chen Guo reckoned that all of that work had instantly been undone by Wei Chen's dirtiness.

Jade Dynasty's Spellblade wasn't affected by Wei Chen's words. He didn't directly head over though and instead took a more roundabout path. This was the first time Jade Dynasty's player went along a more strategic path. He walked around, but wasn't able to find the target. Wei Chen was still hiding in a corner near his spawn point, not moving.

The commentator suffered the most. No matter how experienced he was, it wouldn't be enough. One side wasn't moving. The other side was running around in circles. What was there for him to do? Calculate the distance between the two players?

Jade Dynasty's player ran around in a circle a few times but still didn't see his opponent, but continued to look around. This player had clearly underestimated Wei Chen's shamelessness. He didn't think Wei Chen would go so far as to do such a disgusting move. However, Wei Chen still did it. He sat in a corner near the spawn point like a cat.

In the blink of an eye, three minutes passed. Wei Chen typed out on the dot: "Three minutes is up. You still haven't found me. Go forfeit."

The stadium suddenly made all sorts of noise. However, the player booths were soundproof. The players wouldn't know what the stadium's reaction was. After all, Glory was different from other esports. Leaks could be game changing. As a result, players on stage were practically sealed in.

Even if he could hear the crowd's reaction, Wei Chen definitely wouldn't bat an eyelid towards it. He shouted for the opponent to forfeit, but there was no reply. Wei Chen continued to grumble: "Why aren't you forfeiting? Do you think this is fun for me?"

The crowd suddenly felt the urge to curse at him. That was exactly what they wanted to say to Wei Chen.

Jade Dynasty's player ignored him, but after running in circles for three minutes, he had to start seriously considering that his opinion of Wei Chen's shamelessness had been way off. The Spellblade turned around and started moving towards Windward Formation's spawn point.　　

During this time, Windward Formation kept on typing messages, using all sorts of unscrupulous words to provoke Team Jade Dynasty. He obviously used Qiao Yifan's 1v2 a lot. The viewers finally got something. The viewers confused about Qiao Yifan's second win had been explained through Wei Chen's trash talk. What an incredible player! The viewers, who now understood Qiao Yifan's play, admired him even more. At the same time, they also felt sympathy: How did such a player have such a filthy teammate?

Finally, Jade Dynasty's Spellblade reached Windward Formation's spawn point. He started moving slower, carefully observing his surroundings.

Wei Chen's trash talk continued as if he didn't know his opponent was nearby. Everyone had one thought right now. They hoped that Jade Dynasty's Spellblade would hurry up and uncover him so that guy could shut up already.

He's getting close! He's getting close!

The viewers had an omniscient view of the match started to become excited, but the moment the Spellblade was about to make the last step to find his opponent, Windward Formation suddenly ran out of his corner and started moving.

F*ck!

Many people in the crowd cursed inwardly. How did he know? No one understood. He probably cheated? Quite a few people had started doubting Wei Chen's morality.

In any case, the Spellblade missed his opportunity. He wasn't able to find Windward Formation at the spawn point and that guy's trash talk kept on pouring out. This time, the Spellblade was finally a bit confused because he had lost all sense of direction. He started wondering if Windward Formation was even there.

He is! He's about to come too!!

The viewers hated how they couldn't rush over and tell the Spellblade what was happening. From their god's view, they discovered that after Windward Formation went in a circle, he had circled around to the Spellblade's back. The commentator became excited too because, after Qiao Yifan's two matches, he started taking the habit of paying attention to the map's terrain. When he switched viewpoints, he suddenly realized that after Windward Formation circled around, the distance, angle, and terrain were all favorable towards Windward Formation.　　

The commentator immediately said this point and couldn't help but sigh: "It looks like Team Happy's veteran and Team Blue Rain's former captain isn't as boring as everyone imagined him to be. I only have one thing to say: the older the wiser."

Chapter 992: Victory Boos

The viewers watching the broadcast could hear the commentator's words, so they understood how impressive Wei Chen's play was. However, the lesser skilled members of the audience couldn't see anything special about it. They continued to boo at Wei Chen.

Amidst these boos, Windward Formation moved into an exceptionally good position. Perfect timing and advantageous terrain. Everything was in his favor. As soon as he attacked, he forced Jade Dynasty's Spellblade into a difficlult situation.　　

Warlocks excelled at controlling situations. Their attack range was higher than a Spellblade's. In addition, Windward Formation's Silver weapon, Death's Hand, gave +4 to spell casting distance. The Spellblade was being toyed around by Wei Chen like a wooden marionette.

The crowd was still booing wildly, hoping for Jade Dynasty's Spellblade to teach Wei Chen a lesson, but they soon discovered that it was the complete opposite from what they had hoped. Jade Dynasty's Spellblade was actually being destroyed by that dirty, shameless guy.

The boos stopped. The crowd had mixed feelings. For a moment, they were unable to give any applause to Wei Chen, even though he had beautifully grasped the distance and pace of the fight.　　

At the same time, the other match taking place at a different stage had officially ended.

1v5. What was thought to be impossible was established on the basis that the level of the two participating sides were close. Continuing their streak from the last match, Excellent Era's Sun Xiang once again swept through the group arena alone. In the follow team competition, after easily killing one of the other side's players, Excellent Era ended the match early with all six of their members intact.

There were many Excellent Era fans at the stadium. Although they couldn't help but focus more of their attention on the match between Happy and Jade Dynasty, Excellent Era sweeping through this match was still welcomed with applause.

This kind of achievement wasn't anything to be proud of for Excellent Era, but they wouldn't refuse the passionate support of their fans. Excellent Era's players stood together on stage, waving their hands towards the audience. The broadcast officially announced Team Excellent Era's advance to the Challenger League's finals.

However, it looked as if Team Excellent Era didn't care who their next opponent would be. After satisfying a few requests for signatures and pictures, Team Excellent Era exited the stadium. They didn't even bother waiting for the other match to end.

Xiao Jie noticed Excellent Era's arrogance and felt extremely unhappy. He couldn't bother bickering about it at this moment though. It was still a question whether or not Team Jade Dynasty could beat Team Happy.

Team Jade Dynasty hiding their strength was originally supposed to be a surprise for Team Excellent Era, but when they faced Team Happy, Xiao Jie was shaken.

After all, he had been a fan of Glory since the very beginning. He was no stranger to the names Ye Qiu, Wei Chen, or Sun Zheping, so after hesitating again and again, Xiao Jie reluctantly decided to reveal his surprise ahead of time.

With that, he thought beating Happy wouldn't be a problem, but even after switching to superior equipment, Xiao Jie was unable to see any sort of advantage. They were being dominated from start to finish. This match didn't even look like a competition between two equals. They were still being beaten even after switching equipment. If he had left the surprise until the end, how badly would they be losing?

Xiao Jie didn't dare think about it. Seeing Windward Formation force his team's Spellblade into all sorts of predicaments, disgust was written all over Xiao Jie's face. He hated losing and loathed this kind of performance. He had bought Team Jade Dynasty to have fun, not to endure suffering.

The Spellblade was finally defeated. Wei Chen won effortlessly. If the part where he had shamelessly went into hiding had been removed, the crowd would have been very willing to give him a round of applause. However, with that sort of opener, the crowd felt like the quality of the match had been dragged through the dirt.

To think he won like that... everyone thought to themselves.

Xiao Jie continued to sit there, not saying a word. The let the players swap on their own. They were already on their last player. As for Happy? Including Wei Chen, Happy still had three players. Ye Xiu and Sun Zheping had yet to even make an appearance. Xiao Jie didn't have any hope towards this Spitfire either. He only hoped that he would lose without making a fool of himself and not give a shameful performance.

The poor Spitfire player didn't have any confidence either. 1v3? For a small character like himself, such an achievement only appeared in his dreams. He didn't dare think about who the next player on Happy was. He was afraid that he might not even be able to beat the player on stage right now. What shameless method would this despicable guy use to deal with him?

The Spitfire player trembled with fear as he walked towards the stage. He swiped his account card. A short moment later, the match began. A string of letters popped up in the all chat: "Is there any point in trying to fight? Why don't you just forfeit!"

The boos from the crowd nearly shook the stadium. They had never seen someone so shameless before. Couldn't you try a different method for once? The viewers saw it clearly! While Windward Formation typed that out, he once again hid in a corner just like in the last match.

What about Team Dynasty's side? The Spitfire player carefully moved along a strategic route. The thought that Wei Chen would do the same thing as in the previous round didn't even cross his mind. Not just anyone could fathom such shamelessness.

But after going around and around, he was unable to find his target. Jade Dynasty's player was forced to lower himself and consider things from a shameless point of view.

No way, right?

He questioned his own guess as he controlled his character to move towards Windward Formation's spawn point.　　

The crowd was in an uproar. If this kept going, it wouldn't be a copy of the last round, would it? Boos and shouts erupted. Even Happy's most loyal supporters felt too embarrassed to say anything. The Happy fanclub formed by Seven Fields and the others had shrunk down into their seats. It looked as if they were ready to slide to underneath their seats at a moment's notice.

Fortunately, Jade Dynasty's player wasn't as stupid as everyone thought. After seeing his teammate get ambushed by Wei Chen's Windward Formation, how could he not be on guard against it? As he approached the spawn point, he changed his pathing, going along the route that Windward Formation had previously used to flank his teammate.

"Beautiful!!" The crowd couldn't help but cheer. Right now, they weren't concerned about the competition between the two teams. They just wanted to see that despicable Warlock get taught a lesson. They hoped that the Spitfire would surprise that guy from behind and make him piss his pants in fear.

This scene was about to happen. The Spitfire slowly approached, but Wei Chen's Windward Formation remained still. If this was before, he would have already started running, right?

Shouldering countless people's hopes, the Spitfire finally circled around to the spawn point. Wei Chen's Windward Formation didn't seem to be aware of him.

"Arrived?" He simply said in the chat.

What's arrived?

Everyone was puzzled. They hadn't thought that it was just a casual greeting. Weren't they playing a serious match, right now?

Unfortunately, the poor Jade Dynasty player was also puzzled. He had been startled by the sudden question. Then, Windward Formation's attack flew at him.

Jade Dynasty's player wasn't so confused that he had forgotten what he was doing. As soon as he saw the opponent attack, he instinctively dodged and counterattacked. The two characters immediately started fighting, exchanging blows.

The crowd started discussing amongst each other. They didn't think that this scene was as simple as it looked. Happy's Warlock must have some sort of disgusting trick up his sleeve.

What could it be? Everyone thought to themselves. As they thought about it, they saw Team Jade Dynasty's Spitfire fall.　　

Done?

Everyone was dumbstruck, when they saw the word Glory jump onto the screen.　

Where was his signature despicableness? Where was the shamelessness? Why was it over already?

The stadium didn't have a commentator helping them, so they were all scratching their heads in wonder. However, those watching the broadcast had already been told by the commentator, who didn't know whether to laugh or cry, that this was just an ordinary fight. Happy's Warlock was more or less too lazy to move, so he just waited for the Spitfire player to come. Then, the two sides fought, ending with the Spitfire falling.

The viewers watching the broadcast were cursing, while the crowd at the stadium were still puzzled. They felt like they had missed something. Everyone was staring at the screen, hoping to find something from the replays.

But they still weren't able to see anything. The crowd watched as Wei Chen walked out from the stage, also completing a 1v2 like his previous teammate. However, they had no idea what to do.

But after seeing that guy waving his hands towards them, a single thought formed in their minds.

Boo at him! Keep booing!

The crowd once again booed the winner. And then, they saw this guy continue waving his hands, welcoming their boos.

Did he not understand what these boos meant? The boos suddenly became louder. Wei Chen acted as though there was no one there and returned to his seat.

In the group arena section, Team Happy had won 3 points. It could be considered as an impressive result. In the next team competition, as long as they killed three of their opponent's players, they could not lose the match. If they killed another one, the match would end in their guaranteed victory.

The pressure had been piled onto Team Jade Dynasty. Xiao Jie no longer stayed silent. He got up and walked towards the players.

"What did you think about your performances in the group arena?" Xiao Jie asked.

No one in Team Jade Dynasty uttered a word.

"It looks like all of you know and feel ashamed. What about the following team competition? What do you plan to do to win? Will it be like the group arena? Stroll right into the opponent's trap? Get crushed by the opponents?" Xiao Jie said.

"Of course not." Someone suddenly lifted his head and gave a smile full of confidence.

Chapter 993: Deciding Match

The person who spoke up was Team Jade Dynasty's Cleric, Lu Shilin. Xiao Jie had personally scouted him. In his eyes, he was an outstanding Cleric. When Xiao Jie purchased Team Jade Dynasty, he naturally stuck him into the team. Lu Shilin could be considered as someone under his personal command. Xiao Jie had originally intended on directly handing Lu Shilin the team captain's position, but he wasn't stupid. He knew that he hadn't brought half of the team over. He had only brought one person. An individual's power was rather weak, even if he had the boss' backing. It might not be enough to convince the rest of the team.

As a result, the team captain was still Lin Yi. Apart from that, Xiao Jie even asked their former captain, Zhang Jian to help. Thus, when Team Jade Dynasty's ownership changed, no one was unhappy.

It was just that, at this moment, Xiao Jie was not happy at all. He had thought that they were in a superior position, but he didn't see any of their superiority in the group arena, which made him seriously question these players' ability to perform. If not, how could they have lost in such an ugly manner?

Right now, if they wanted to reach the finals, they needed to win the team competition with three or more players surviving. If this team continued to perform the same way that they did in the group arena, it would truly be hopeless. Fortunately, the true core of Team Jade Dynasty would finally be coming out.

This was Team Jade Dynasty's true power. Just wait and see, Happy. Xiao Jie shot a glance at Happy. An arrogant and proud smile once again appeared on his face.

The break time in between the group arena and team competition quickly passed. Jade Dynasty's players readied themselves. There was nothing new to their player list. It was the same five players from the group arena along with Lu Shilin.

"Do well! Take revenge!" Xiao Jie yelled to his teammates.

"Haha, revenge already? Then what will happen when you get eliminated?" The person who replied was Happy's Ye Xiu.

"You truly deserve to be called a God. You're quite confident!" Xiao Jie's voice carried a hint of sarcasm. His politeness at the start of the match was non-existent.

"And I should be." Ye Xiu nodded his head towards Xiao Jie's remark.

"You'll pay the price for your conceit." Xiao Jie sneered.

Ye Xiu didn't know whether to laugh or cry: "And I thought you were conceited! You didn't give any advice to them for the team competition, right?"

Xiao Jie's face darkened. He hadn't said too much in the team competition, but he still said a few words. He had purchased Team Jade Dynasty so he could enjoy planning strategies with the team.

"I hope you didn't. If not, the Alliance might have to work overtime and convene a meeting to discuss the new competitive format if this match ends too quickly." Ye Xiu said.

"Hahahaha." Chen Guo was unable to keep up her image and started laughing loudly. She had long since gotten a bad impression of Xiao Jie since long ago.　

Xiao Jie always acted as if his beliefs were infallible. If the team played spectacularly, it would be because of him. If the team played poorly, it was the fault of the players; he wouldn't blame himself at all. If Ye Xiu hadn't returned fire, Chen Guo would have rushed forward to say a few words herself. Fortunately, Ye Xiu did it first. His replies were much more brilliant. This type of reasonable and justifiable trash talk was truly Ye Xiu's strong point!

The Alliance wanted to test the new competitive format in the Challenger League, but they forgot that there was a huge skill disparity in the Challenger League. Didn't Excellent Era quickly and easily finish up and go home to eat? If Happy crushed Jade Dynasty and also finished early, what conclusions would the Alliance be able to come to with this Challenger League experiment? That truly was quite an incisive question!

"Hang in there! You have to hang in there!" Chen Guo added fuel to the fire and blurted out a few more words.

"Hmph. You won't be smiling in a bit." Xiao Jie replied.　　

"Of course." Chen Guo said proudly. She was usually the one who was the more worried, but in this critical moment, she was suddenly filled with confidence. She firmly believed that Happy wouldn't lose to this team. That wouldn't be professional!

Team Happy's participating players started going on stage too.

Because only three players had appeared on stage in the group arena for Happy, it was still unknown who would be going on stage in the team competition. The players who closely followed the Challenger League were quite familiar with an eye-catching team like Happy. They paid particular attention to this issue. Even the commentator was guessing who Happy would send out for the team competition. It was only until Happy's players started going on stage was the answer revealed.

The one in front was Ye Xiu. He wasn't just a God in Team Happy. He was someone who remained unsurpassed in the Glory scene. Behind him was Sun Zheping. With the name Blood and Blossoms, he was only one step away from the peak of Glory. From the boos from the crowd, it wasn't hard to guess who was next. Wei Chen. He would win by any means necessary. He embodied the concept of shamelessness. After the boos, the crowd suddenly started cheering and clapping because this was another player who had won through solid fundamentals in today's group arena, Qiao Yifan. He had come from a top team and had similar accomplishments in the group arena like Wei Chen, but the treatment towards him was the complete opposite. It was certainly a wondrous scene to look at.

After Qiao Yifan, the next player was clearly quite popular as this player received many cheers. This player had always received a lot of attention over the entire course of the offline tournament.

Tang Rou. Not only did she possess incredible mechanics, she also had outstanding looks. After appearing in the offline tournament, she received all-around attention. Chen Guo had received not just a few requests for Tang Rou. There were even many powerful people who directly looked for Tang Rou, trying to recruit her.

These people seemed to have a good understanding of Happy's situation. As a result, they felt like the reason Tang Rou was willing to play for Team Happy was definitely because she didn't fully understand her own value, and in order to recruit such an outstanding player in all regards, many teams were willing to pay a high price for her. This was why the clubs were quite confident.

Unfortunately, they didn't completely understand Tang Rou. They thought that they could move Tang Rou with very generous offers, but these had no effect on Tang Rou.

What exactly did she want?

This was what the various clubs wondered after getting in touch with Tang Rou. Unfortunately, no one could find the correct answer. They could only watch quietly as Tang Rou performed spectacularly again and again for Happy. It made them lament. Such a pearl was being thrown to the swines right in front of them, but they were unable to save it. It was truly too regretful.　　

After Tang Rou was Happy's Cleric, An Wenyi. Healers were a rather mild and not very eye-catching class that made people's blood boil. In addition, all of his other teammates shined too brightly. When An Wenyi appeared on stage, the atmosphere in the stadium clearly became a bit colder, but An Wenyi dind't mind because he never felt like he had done anything to deserve their cheers. If someone actually cheered for him, wouldn't that be more strange?　　

When he came onto the stage, he saw that Jade Dynasty's Cleric hadn't gone to his seat yet. Instead, he was waiting on the side for Happy's players. Ye Xiu, Sun Zheping, Wei Chen, Qiao Yifan, Tang Rou. All of them passed by him one by one. He kept a smile on his face and didn't pay much attention to them, but when An Wenyi walked by, he came over and welcomed him.　

"Hi." Lu Shilin extended out his right hand.　

"Hi." An Wenyi naturally shook his hand.

"In this team competition, the two of us will be the ones who decide who wins and loses." Lu Shilin said. Then, he drew back his hand and left with a smile.

An Wenyi was startled. His hand was hanging still in the air. The other side had only shook his hand casually. As for Lu Shilin's words, it wasn't hard to figure out what he implied from the way he shook hands. He was hinting that the huge disparity between the Clerics would decide the winner of this match.

"What an arrogant guy!" Wei Chen exclaimed. The rest of Happy had heard Lu Shilin's challenge to An Wenyi.

"Haha, psychological warfare? Boring." An Wenyi shook his head.

"Not entirely." Ye Xiu said, "Healers are frequently the deciding factor in the team competition. This isn't a bad tactic."

"I'll still do my best." An Wenyi said.

"Everyone will." Ye Xiu smiled.

"Then you guys work harder. It's best if you don't need this senior to rescue you guys." Wei Chen said lazily and then headed towards his seat. In this team competition, he was their sixth player.　

Happy's players took their seats and swiped their cards. After checking everything, the characters on both sides entered the waiting room. Once the countdown reached zero, the two sides loaded into the map. Happy versus Jade Dynasty. The deciding battle that decided who would advance to the finals officially began.　　

The players on both sides spawned at the corners of the map and started moving. Both sides had studied the map previously. As for their opening moves, none of them started discussing them when the match started. They had already made preparations beforehand. Afterwards, they would need to make the appropriate adjustments throughout the match.

Team Jade Dynasty's four swordsmen circled around Lu Shilin, maintaining a complete formation before advancing. Team Happy's five players separated and ran randomly around the map like they had no solid strategy planned.

Of course, no one believed that Happy didn't actually have a strategy going in. The commentator looked around the map through his god's view, observing the movements of Happy's characters to determine their intentions.

"One Inch Ash and Little Cold Hands are fairly close to each other. They aren't moving forward as fast as the other three. The attackers clearly aren't going to be these two. As for those other three, Ye Xiu, Sun Zheping. One is the Battle God, the other is the former number one Berserker. I think besides Han Wenqin, no one is more aggressive than those two? As for Tang Rou, even though she's a rookie, her aggressiveness isn't lacking compared to her seniors. In terms of style, I don't think there's a player combination that's more aggressive than these three….."

Chapter 994: Now He's Dead

What the commentator called the strongest offensive trio in all of Glory didn't stick together. The three characters each went down different paths. The broadcast switched to a bird's eye view of the entire map, with the players of each team outlined by different colored highlights. All the pathings of the players became much more obvious.

"Uh, from the bird's eye view we have, we can clearly see the movements of the players on each team. Jade Dynasty's players are more concentrated, maintaining a formation as they advance together. Team Happy, on the other hand, is completely scattered around, apart from One Inch Ash and Little Cold Hands, who are just barely in range of supporting each other. The other three characters have all pulled away, but from the directions they're each heading in, their intentions are rather clear. It's a little hard to believe, but these three… It seems like they plan to surround Team Jade Dynasty." The commentator's tone was very doubtful.

However, the developing situation gave them their answer.

Team Jade Dynasty, advancing forward in a straight line, met Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep first. With a greatsword in hand, he charged right towards the front of their team's formation. He was a single man, but he seemed to have the air of a general leading an army of thousands into battle.

Jade Dynasty's formation didn't change. The four swordsmen charging forward to meet their opponent while maintaining their positions around Lu Shilin's Cleric. However, none of them could resist looking around as their characters charged forward. Sun Zheping was just charging over on his own? There really wasn't anyone nearby to support him?

"Don't let him close in." That was when Lu Shilin gave that order. The Spellblade among the four swordsmen stepped forward, an Earthquake Sword sweeping out. Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep sidestepped it and continued to advance. Jade Dynasty's Berserker then jumped out, also wielding a greatsword, and charged furiously at Another Summer of Sleep.

However, his charge was just a feint. The real attack was the Ghostblade hiding beside him, sneakily summoning a Ghost Boundary. He swung his blade down, but then saw Another Summer of Sleep abruptly swing his Broadsword at him.

Clang!

The Ghostblade hastily raised his sword into a Guard, sliding back several units, but still managing to take the blow. Following that, the Blademaster and Berserker executed a pincer attack against Another Summer of Sleep, the Spellblade's Wave Formation had trapped Another Summer of Sleep within as well. They were really quite surprised, not expecting for Sun Zheping to charge right into their formation like that. This was underestimating them. Even though Jade Dynasty might not have been the best, they had once been pros. They didn't think that they had fallen to the level of being underestimated like this.

They decided to punish Sun Zheping for this. Yet that was when Tang Rou's Soft Mist arrived, spear raised, charging over at their flank with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Lu Shilin smirked. What was this? Support? These two were both recklessly charging into their formation, not supporting or working together. This was the level that Happy's tactics were at? One of the legendary four Master Tacticians?

Lu Shlin thought to himself and then turned his view, seeing a glimpse of Lord Grim from a different direction. So he had snuck around their back and was still on his way over!

Lu Shilin was really almost about to laugh out loud. So he wanted to use wave after wave of furious attacks to mess up their formation, huh? The problem was, they were absolutely terrible at controlling the pace. They were just coming out to get killed one by one!

　

"Take out the Berserker first," Lu Shiling ordered, not telling the four Swordsmen to deal with the two newcomers yet.

That was when he saw Soft Mist not even bothering to help Another Summer of Sleep and instead charged at Lu Shilin's Cleric.

"This isn't something unexpected." Lu Shilin kept up his smile, backing away a few steps and entered the Ghost Boundaries and Wave Formations of their Ghostblade and Spellblade. This was originally a defense against Another Summer of Sleep, but now it also acted as the perfect protection for Lu Shilin.

As expected Soft Mist didn't dare to follow him into such dangerous territory and could only change directions to go and assist Another Summer of Sleep. Never mind Lu Shilin, even the commentator felt like Happy's strategic arrangements were terrible this round.

"This round of attacks from Team Happy wasn't executed very well! First of all, Sun Zheping made the mistake by facing his opponent's head on; he completely underestimated Jade Dynasty's players and him being surrounded means that the second wave of attacks from Tang Rou didn't work very well. They've lost their goal for this wave of attacks. I trust that Happy didn't intend to throw Another Summer of Sleep into enemy territory and then pull him out a again."

"Now Ye Xiu's Lord Grim is approaching as well, but can he turn the tides alone? Oh… He's stopped. It seems like he doesn't intends to charge into the fray. It's true that the situation isn't the best, but he can't just give up like that, can he? Are they giving up on Another Summer of Sleep? It seems like it. Soft Mist is preparing to retreat."

"Hahahaha…" On the player stands for Jade Dynasty, their boss Xiao Jie finally witnessed a situation he could enjoy. It was unfortunate that he couldn't talk to Ye Xiu now. After all, that guy was currently trying to awkwardly clean up after the strategic disaster he had planned, no?

　

"Hey, I say, is this your strategy?" Xiao Jie called out to Chen Guo who was watching the match on Happy's side.

Yet, at the same time as his shout, the audience suddenly cried out in collective shock.

Xiao Jie turned his head back around to see Lord Grim, who hadn't jumped into the fray, suddenly break his weapon in two and stretch out his hands. Then, Lu Shilin's Cleric was grabbed, and Soft Mist's retreat seemed more like a pursuit.

"What?" Xiao Jie stood suddenly.

These words were heard by all the viewers watching this match. What they heard, naturally, wasn't Xiao Jie's yell, but the commentator, who had only just been commenting on how terribly Happy was doing, suddenly stop and cry out in surprise.

This scene was too unexpected. Because the stadium itself had many angles being played together, the audience there could see what was happening. However, the TV broadcast only had what the program director showed them. Most of the time, only one scene was being played on the TV and the scene just now hadn't been broadcasted on TV because the program director had not been expecting it at all. By the time he saw it and hastily switched to the correct angle, Lu Shilin's Cleric was already flying through the air, eventually landing in Lord Grim's hands.

"Cloud Grasping Fist?? Was that a Cloud Grasping Fist? How did Lord Grim manage to use Cloud Grasping Fist? We all know that unspecialized characters can learn all of the pre-advancement skills from every classes, but this doesn't include skills beyond level 20! All the skills learned beyond level 20 are only available after job advancement, unless… unless…"

　

"It's an equipment bonus!? The commentator yelled out in realization. "If it's an equipment bonus, then of course he'd be able to use it, god! What sort of weapon does Lord Grim have? We knew it could change forms, becoming weapons of all sorts of class types so that Lord Grim can fully utilize all of his skills, but now it seems that there are skills built into the weapon too! That means Lord Grim is no longer limited to those low leveled skills. Though these skills won't be at a very high rank, another skill means more options and more combinations. For example, what we're seeing now is a Cloud Grasping Fist. It might not have the same speed and range as a maxed rank Cloud Grasping Fist, but its usage here might be the deciding factor of this match. Jade Dynasty's Cleric has been abducted from their formation by Lord Grim just like that…"

"Okay, he was stolen a while ago, and now he's already dead…" The commentator had yelled excitedly, only focused on analyzing that Cloud-Grasping Fist and forgetting to talk about what had been occurring. When he got back to it, the Cleric of Jade Dynasty's had immediately received a beating. Soft Mist definitely hadn't been retreating just now, but running over to kill her target.

　

The four Swordsmen Jade Dynasty panicked, forgetting about dealing with Another Summer of Sleep. This wasn't a fair trade at all. How were they going to fight without a healer?

The four hurriedly ran over to help, but that was when two others arrived. One was One Inch Ash, who arrived with his Ghost Boundaries that immediately came down in a chain. This was the layering playstyle that he had used in the Group Arena. No, to be accurate, it was even more fierce, even more swift, because what he needed to do now was block them, stall for time, so he didn't need to consider how long this could last. As long as he stalled them for a little bit of time, allowing them deal with the Cleric, he would have done his job.

　

On One Inch Ash's other side, Little Cold Hands charged out, not to heal, but as support for their offense. A Holy Commandment was branded on Lu Shilin's Cleric, raising his damage taken by thirty percent, as if afraid he wouldn't die fast enough.

While one side was bleeding, the other side had just bled.　

"Question: What does a Berserker that has lost blood do to the people that made him lose blood?"

In the public chat, Another Summer of Sleep suddenly sent out this sentence. The four people freaking out at being blocked by One Inch Ash saw this and turned their cameras, only to find Another Summer of Sleep with Berserk and Whirlwind Slash activated, charging over.

The four hurriedly attempted to parry. As expected of a Berserker that had lost enough blood, the addition of Berserk transformed him into a hurricane and blew them everywhere. However, the four had no time to think about themselves. Cleric! This match depended on the Cleric's survival!

That was when they saw a sentence in the global chat, coming from Lord Grim. "Your Cleric said this would be a battle between two Clerics. Now he's dead. What about you guys? Are you going to continue?"

Chapter 995: Life Isn’t Fiction

Not a sound could be heard from the stadium.

Compared to the Jade Dynasty players on stage, the crowd had watched as Jade Dynasty's Cleric was grabbed from inside his team's formation and beaten to death.

Cloud Grasping a healer wasn't anything new. Even in the Arena, players in team competitions liked to use this move to create an opening. The prerequisite was naturally that the team had to have a Qi Master.

Yes, a Qi Master. This class was the prerequisite. Happy didn't have one though, so Jade Dynasty hadn't taken any sort of precautions against this move. However, a Cloud Grasping Fist actually appeared. Jade Dynasty's Cleric was kidnapped and wasn't able to resist. Then, Lord Grim and Soft Mist ganged up on him. On the side, Happy's Cleric also helped out. In a moment, there would be a Holy Commandment; the next, there would be a Sacred Fire. Jade Dynasty's Cleric wasn't even able to defend himself. He was being kneaded like a piece of dough. Even when he turned into a corpse, the corpse was sent flying with a blow-away attack. Ye Xiu threw out those words in the chat at the same time. Bang! Jade Dynasty's Cleric flew past One Inch Ash's Ghost Boundaries and landed in front of the rest of Jade Dynasty.

Nothing was worse than having the Cleric killed in a team competition. The only exception was if the team didn't bring a Cleric in the first place.

Team Jade Dynasty clearly wasn't the exception though. What's more, they regarded their healer as their core.

The healer was six feet under. The core had died. It was exactly like Ye Xiu had just asked. Was there even a need to continue?　　

The outcome of the match was soon decided. Happy easily won. Looking back at their run through the group arena, everyone realized in astonishment that this match wasn't as intense as they had anticipated it to be. Happy won the match without much trouble!

But Team Jade Dynasty's players didn't think the same. The instant the winner of the match was announced, the Cleric Lu Shilin rushed out from his seat in a frenzy. In this match, the viewers weren't even able to see his character name clearly or show his Cleric's ability before dying. Everything was because of that stupid Cloud Grasping Fist.

Yes, such a crude method that even normal players used had been the deciding move in this very important match. There weren't any deep or complex tactics involved. Sun Zheping and Tang Rou simply drew their attention, allowing Ye Xiu find the right opportunity to launch a sneak attack.

In reality, there was a single prerequisite that allowed for this to happen: Team Jade Dynasty didn't know Lord Grim could use Cloud Grasping Fist. If they had known, they would have protected their healer differently and paid particular attention to Lord Grim. They would have treated him more like a Qi Master. No matter what, Lord Grim wouldn't have been able to stand behind them so casually. He wouldn't have been able to lift his hand, whisk him away, and kill him so quickly.

Lu Shilin refused to accept the result. He refused a hundred, a thousand, ten thousand times. The outcome had nothing to do with strategy or skill. It was only because their Team Jade Dynasty didn't know one small detail...　

Happy had an unfair advantage. They should be feeling ashamed at such a victory!

Wei Chen was the first to get up from the player seats on Happy's side. As soon as he got up, he stretched his body: "So fast! I had only just fallen asleep!"

"You..... You....." Seeing Team Happy's players come out one after the other, Lu Shilin pointed his hand at them. He was so furious, he could only shake with anger, unable to say anything.

What could he say? Happy should have told them that they would use Cloud Grasping Fist, so Jade Dynasty could be on their guard? Lu Shilin obviously knew that was impossible. Thus, even though he refused to accept the results, he was unable to find any convincing arguments.

After saying "you" for awhile, just before Happy left the stage, he jumped out: "What type of f*cking class is an unspecialized? They're allowed in a competition????"

He was already grasping at straws. The Alliance never had any restrictions or requirements towards characters. There simply hadn't been a precedent for an unspecialized before. There was no rule stating that unspecialized characters were forbidden.

Lu Shilin's argument had no effect on Happy's players. They just kept talking and laughing, completely ignoring his existence. They left the stage and celebrated their victory with the others.　

Lu Shilin still wanted to rush over and argue, but someone grabbed him from behind. He turned to look. It was Team Jade Dynasty's team captain, Lin Yi.

"What are you doing?" Lu Shilin furiously threw Lin Yi's hand off of him. He clearly didn't have much respect for this captain of his.　

"A loss is a loss. Lose with dignity!" Lin Yi said.

"Dignity? Wow, you've really got some! You can accept such a stupid loss?" Lu Shilin shouted.　　

"That's the way competition is. At least, next time we won't make the same mistake." Lin Yi said.　　

"Next time? When's that? Next year?" Lu Shilin ridiculed, "You can hang around the Challenger League for three years because you can put up with such stupid losses, but not me!"

"I don't think it was a stupid loss. We just lost to something unexpected. In the end, it's because we didn't prepare enough. That goes for the team competition and the group arena too." Lin Yi said.　

Lu Shilin listened and then laughed: "So it's like that. You want to look for an excuse for your trash performance in the group arena? So you're actually very happy that we lost in this team competition! This way, it proves that you're not actually incompetent, right?"

"Calm down." Lin Yi felt helpless. He could understand Lu Shilin's feelings though. Losing in the Challenger League was a huge blow because this meant that another year had been wasted. It was even more painful than losing the championship title. If you lost the championships, it wasn't the end of the world, but losing in the Challenger League just might be the end of the world. Didn't Team Everlasting disband this season because of their consecutive losses in the Challenger League?

Team Jade Dynasty being unable to make it through the Challenger League year after year made the players live in fear everyday. Perhaps one morning they would wake up and suddenly be told that the team was disbanding. Everyone go home.

This was the life of those at the bottom of the competitive scene. It was similar to those at the bottom of society. They couldn't talk about their dreams or goals. Just surviving was already difficult.

Jade Dynasty had walked along this arduous path year after year. No one understood the fear and desperation of being at the bottom better than them. Xiao Jie's sudden appearance had been welcomed with heartfelt gratitude. They at least didn't have to worry about their team surviving for a short period of time.

But they soon realized that their new boss wasn't as pure as they imagined him to be. He eagerly wanted Team Jade Dynasty to return to the Alliance and return to the soil where the pro players truly resided.

Who didn't want that? Team Jade Dynasty had persisted year after year for this very goal, no? But in order to realize this goal, they had to face reality. Team Jade Dynasty had participated in the Challenger League for three years. How far their strength had fallen could easily be imagined.

Indeed, Xiao Jie had brought along a pretty good player. At the same time, he had found their former captain Zhang Jian as a helper. Using the experience accumulated from all these years, along with solid financial backing to massively upgrade their equipment, the entire Team Jade Dynasty had been reborn.

But even so, immediately returning to the Alliance this season was too early, no?

No one wanted to be in the spotlight more than Lin Yi and the other players, but a reborn team with new characters and equipment needed time to get used to. Their new Cleric became their core. With their core changed, the entire team's strategies and tactics also needed to be revised. Apart from that, this season's Challenger League had an unprecedented mountain to climb: Team Excellent Era.

It wouldn't be exaggerated to call Team Jade Dynasty's situation this season as a mess both internally and externally, but their new boss? Their new core player? They viewed this as a challenge and also saw it as an opportunity they could grasp. If they could beat Team Excellent Era and return to the Alliance, Team Jade Dynasty would instantly rise and return with their heads held high. After that, the two had actually started talking about becoming the champions.

　

Team Jade Dynasty's players couldn't adapt to such a sudden change. They didn't know how they had suddenly gone from worrying about the survival of their team to becoming the champions.　

It wasn't like Team Jade Dynasty's players didn't have such ambitions. However, their boss' and new teammate's attitude were too exaggerated.

As the team captain, Lin Yi had specifically looked for Xiao Jie to discuss this issue. The boss completely ignored his worries. He lost himself in his own methods. For example, not using good equipment and waiting until the final battle to catch their opponents off guard. In his opinion, Team Excellent Era losing their heads out of fear at such a scene was too much of a joke.

At that time, Lin Yi was also helpless, just like how he was when facing Lu Shilin now. This new boss and new teammate were too much in sync. It wasn't without reason. Both of them were extremely conceited. A lot of clearly difficult problems were solved by them with a laugh.

Team Jade Dynasty had taken off under these circumstances. Xiao Jie repeatedly reminded them to preserve with their strength, so they could surprise Team Excellent Era in the finals.　　

The famous author Xiao Jie treated his team like a work of fiction. He thought everything was under his control. If he wanted the team to suppress themselves and then reveal their true strength, then it would happen. If he wanted them to disguise as pigs and then eat the tiger, then it would happen. He treated reality like a work of fiction. Everything would unfold just like how he intended it to, but when what happened in reality completely went against the plot he had thought of, his faithful believer, Lu Shilin, who had lost himself to this imaginary plot, took the lead and collapsed.

Chapter 996: Deliberate Provocation

All of Lin Yi's persuasion couldn't calm Lu Shilin down. However, what else could he do? Even if he made a huge scene onstage, he couldn't alter the results of the match. That would probably only get them thrown out of the stadium by the security.

Lin Yi felt that he could no longer communicate with this guy. He could only take the rest of the players back to their seats. However, when he looked over, Boss Xiao Jie also had an angry look on his face.

"You guys go back to clean this stuff up. Leave me alone!" Xiao Jie pointed towards a group of players offstage. As soon as he said this, he turned and left without looking back.

Lin Yi and the others looked distressed. After staying in Jade Dynasty for this long, they had only thought about going their separate ways in the event that the team was unable to go on. Yet, they had never considered a result like what had happened today. None of them could be considered extremely strong players. Without this kind of team, they might never be able to become pro players again.

Lin Yi sighed. For them, this competition had only decided whether the team lived or died. However, Lu Shilin was actually acting like it was the end of the world. Indeed, this was also a type of mockery!

After Xiao Jie left, he disappeared in the blink of an eye, walking away without looking back once. Jade Dynasty's players had definitely seen their end as pro players, and their hearts ached. However, at this time no one went up to the boss to beg or give an explanation. After a year of getting to know each other, they knew what type of personality their boss had. His conceitedness made it so that he wouldn't go back on his word even when he knew he was wrong.

Lin Yi stood in place in a daze. He didn't chase after his boss, nor did he immediately leave. Instead, he turned around and walked towards Happy.

Seeing Happy celebrate made Jade Dynasty's players feel envious. When Happy saw Lin Yi head towards them, everyone in Happy restrained their emotions. They should show empathy towards the feelings of the losers!

"That was a good match." Lin Yi extended his hands towards Ye Xiu. Even if that loss spelled the end of his career, Lin Yi didn't lose the professionalism he should have. The respects paid to each other by the team captains before and after the match were too often just for show, but Lin Yi remembering to do this even with this kind of outcome showed his sincerity.

"Thanks." Ye Xiu shook his hand, "Don't give up. Keep working hard."

"I want to." Lin YI forced a smile, "I'm only afraid that there won't be any more opportunities for us."

Everyone in Happy was startled. Chen Guo pointed towards Xiao Jie disappearing into the passageway: "Could it be that... those words weren't just out of anger?"

They had seen Xiao Jie flare up at them. The match had just ended though. In the time it took to raise his hands, he disbanded the team under everyone's eyes. Who would easily accept such words? As a result, they just treated those words as a burst of anger from Xiao Jie. However, from what Lin Yi seemed to imply, those weren't empty words.

"I hope we'll have a chance to meet again in the future. I wish you all good luck." After Lin Yi finished speaking, he turned around and got ready to leave.

"Ah! Wait!" Chen Guo suddenly jumped out and shouted towards Lin Yi.

Lin Yi stopped his footsteps and turned his head.

"Those weren't just words of anger from your boss?" Chen Guo was still pondering over this issue. She couldn't believe someone would handle things so unreasonably.

"I'm afraid not." Lin Yi quietly said.

"Then what do you guys plan to do in the future?" Chen Guo asked.

"I don't know yet. For players at our skill level, we probably won't get any offers from teams!" Lin Yi laughed at himself, "Today's match is probably our final match."

"Uh...." Chen Guo hesitated. She appeared to be thinking over how to word her reply as she turned her head to look at Ye Xiu.

"Our boss is trying to say that if you guys don't have any way out, you guys can come over to Happy for now." Ye Xiu spoke for her.

"Ah?" Lin Yi was shocked.

"But….. I'm afraid you probably won't have the chance to be a team member. There are still a few suitable positions related to Glory work." Ye Xiu said.

Lin Yi listened and understood. They were all people from the same scene. How could he not understand Ye Xiu's implications? These positions were what many retired pro players hoped for. After all, Glory was what they were best at, but the problem was that Jade Dynasty's players weren't at the point where they wanted to retire yet. If the circumstances allowed it, they were more than willing to continue as a pro player and compete on stage. Even though they knew their skill levels were limited, they felt like it was still too early for them to be certain that they had no room for improvement.

If Lu Shilin was here, he would probably immediately jump out and question it: "What do you mean? Are you saying that I'm not good enough to be a pro and that I'm only good enough to do miscellaneous tasks?" However, Lin Yi knew that the other side had good intentions. Perhaps only a team of old players like Ye Xiu, Wei Chen, and Sun Zheping would truly understand and sympathize with such players, who were at the end of their road.

"Thanks." Lin Yi first expressed his gratitude, "But I think it's best if I discuss this with my brothers first before coming to a decision!"

"No problem." Chen Guo nodded her head, "Leave me your contact info!"

The two exchanged contact info. Lin Yi thanked them once more and then turned around to return to his teammates. As they left, they constantly turned to look towards Happy. Their expressions were filled with surprise. Lin Yi had clearly told them about Happy's intentions.

Lu Shilin was still petrified on stage like a statue. He stared blankly at this scene. Suddenly, he woke up and jumped down like a madman, pointing at the departing Jade Dynasty. Then, he pointed at Happy and shouted: "Good! I get it now! You guys were working in collusion with each other. You guys have already been bribed, which was why you guys intentionally performed poorly in this match! Too despicable. I'm going to complain. Referee! Where's the referee?"

This guy had gone absolutely mad. He actually thought that a normal conversation between the two sides was a shady business deal. Such a grand line of thinking made everyone surprised. Even the experienced Ye Xiu had never seen such an extreme person before.

"F*ck, what's with this guy? Steamed Bun, it's time for you to shine." Wei Chen responded and immediately cursed.

"Okay." Steamed Bun jumped out bravely, "How should I do it? Kill him?"

"Stop stop stop!!" Ye Xiu hastily stopped him.

"What? You dare to do it, but you don't dare to admit it?" Lu Shilin looked as if he had found a magic treasure that could reverse the situation and furiously retorted.

"Don't stop me! I'm about to cripple this shameless b*stard!" Wei Chen couldn't bear it anymore and was prepared to personally take action.

Lin Yi and the others were about to leave, when they heard Lu Shilin lose his mind. Xiao Jie had already disbanded the team, but in the end, Lu Shilin was still one of their teammates. They saw this guy causing trouble and even thought of himself as correct. He actually accused them of playing a fixed match. They couldn't help but get angry.

Jade Dynasty's players came back, ready to drag Lu Shilin away.

"Let go of me! You shameless b*stards. Don't you have any sense of professionalism?" Lu Shilin did everything he could to break free as he cursed at his teammates.

The expressions on the players of Jade Dynasty were ashen. If they really had no professionalism, they would have already beaten Lu Shilin to death. Just look at Team Happy's Wei Chen! Wasn't he already preparing to come over and beat him up!

The crowd went into an uproar, but because they were rather far away, they could only see it happening. They couldn't hear what the two sides were saying. It looked like Team Jade Dynasty had gotten into a dispute with Team Happy.

In the end, Ye Xiu was the most experienced. He didn't attack the unreasonable Lu Shilin, nor did he try and reason with him. He blocked Wei Chen, while shouting left and right: "Security! Security, help! There's someone here who refuses to acknowledge that he's lost the match."

As he shouted, someone laughed. When he looked at Lu Shilin, he felt like he wasn't that annoying anymore. He was just a brat who didn't get what he wanted.

The security guards noticed these movements and rushed over. Not even half a minute after Ye Xiu started yelling, they had reached the scene. Ye Xiu and the others hadn't even said anything to them yet, when Lu Shilin looked as if he was clutching onto his last hope as he grabbed the security guard's hand: "I'm going to report them. These guys colluded to play a fixed match."

Everyone slapped their hands to their foreheads. The Alliance obviously had a disciplinary committee to handle these matters and there were means to make a report, but the security was not responsible for it. These two systems were completely unrelated.

The security guard was experienced at dealing with these issues. After being grabbed onto by Lu Shilin, he didn't force him off. Instead, he warmly encouraged him: "Okay okay okay. Calm down first. Here here here, speak slowly."

"It's like this..." Sure enough, Lu Shilin started talking. Then, Happy and Jade Dynasty watched as this noisy kid was escorted out by the security guard.

"He got his life saved." Wei Chen said with certainty.

Ye Xiu didn't bother with this braggart. Lin Yi's group said farewell to Happy again. This time, Happy was ready to leave too. Chen Guo boldly walked towards Seven Fields and the others, who were staring foolishly at what they had just witnessed, and waved: "Let's go celebrate our victory!!"

Tonight, Team Happy had a reason to relax. It had been a long and arduous journey, but they had finally reached the final step. Next up was Team Happy's goal for this entire year: Team Excellent Era.

Excellent Era had arrogantly left, not waiting to see the results. After they left the stadium, before they could even sit together at the hotel, they already got the news. Team Happy had won and would be their opponents at the finals.

"That fast?" Everyone in Excellent Era was shocked, seeing the time. Even though Jade Dynasty was a weak team in their eyes, wouldn't Happy also count as a weak team on the same level as them? Yet Happy beat them in such an overwhelming manner? On the way back to the hotel, no one in the team talked about the upcoming finals. This was a rare scene.

Chapter 997: Excellent Era’s Exclusive Interview

The Challenger League had finally reached its last stages.

Two days after the match against Team Jade Dynasty, the media began to harass Team Happy, all wanting to interview Ye Xiu. The finals of the Challenger League. The showdown between Team Excellent Era's ex-captain and Team Excellent Era for the right to return to the Pro League. For such a spectacular topic, even the Pro League matches could be pushed to the side.

.

And within this topic, the most exciting aspect was Team Happy's exceptional performance. This built up anticipation for the possibility of a task once thought impossible. Happy's strength wasn't nearly as bad as people had thought. If you took a look at the victories they had scored in the Challenger League all the way until now; almost all of them were one-sided victories. Among these defeated opponents, there was Everlasting, Mysterious Fantasy and Jade Dynasty, these three pro-level teams.

Even though these three were all very weak pro teams, they hadn't been a threat to Team Happy at all. In other words, Happy's strength was far above theirs. Them challenging Excellent Era wasn't arrogant or absurd.

The winds were changing.

At the beginning, everyone thought that Happy was just looking for death, wanting attention, shameless, but now more and more people began to become interested in Happy, eager and expectant for what they would do next.

This sort of enthusiasm was real and not just people who wanted to see Excellent Era fall and therefore supported Happy, like it was in the beginning.

Back then, their support of Happy was just to embarrass Excellent Era. Truthfully, they didn't believe Happy could threaten Excellent Era. However, now their support was more and more real because they began to acknowledge Happy's strength. This would, without doubt, make them even more anticipatory, because now there was an even bigger chance of seeing Excellent Era get humiliated.

Some reporters went ingame and randomly interviewed random Glory players, asking them about their thoughts on this match. After asking several hundred people, they compiled their results and surprisingly found that the number of players supporting Happy exceeded the number of players supporting Excellent Era, a whole 68% percent...

And when the reporters asked for their reason in supporting Happy, the gist of it was a single sentence: it's fun to watch the drama unfold.

From this point of view, a newly brought up army, a team that came from an Internet cafe, defeating the Glory powerhouse Excellent Era was evidently more unexpected and more interesting than Excellent Era winning.

An upset was very attractive to many people.

However, this was only a hope. Another media outlet also went around interviewing random players and didn't ask for hopes, but estimations. In this round of questioning, Excellent Era was far in the lead. 91% of players estimated that Excellent Era would win the match, even though many of them had said they hoped Happy would win.

On the Monday issue of Esports Home's weekly, these two interesting results were discussed together. At the same time, Esports Home also had what each thought of the upcoming match. This was something other media outlets didn't have. On the weekend, both teams were harassed by many different reporters from different media outlets, but both teams rejected interviews. After that, they went to the reporter they were familiar with to have a chat.

Excellent Era had Cao Guangcheng, while Happy hadChang Xian. The two reporters that had practically been silenced because of Excellent Era being relegated, now had monopoly of all the best resources.

　

Edports Home had resolutely expressed that the final match of the Challenger League had to be fully and comprehensively reported on, even if that meant giving it a portion of the sections reserved for the Pro League, which was just finishing up and in its most crucial moments. As for the Alliance, they also placed great importance on this Challenger League match that was the most popular one yet. On the weekend, they had been extremely busy. After talking things over among themselves and contacting the necessary outside parties, they made a last-minute change to the location of this final battle. To better present this match that had captured so much attention, the Alliance decided to move the finals to the Liulisong Sports Arena in the north sector of the city.

The largest difference between this stadium and the last was that it was fully equipped with holographic projectors. The Alliance had decided that the finals of the Challenger League would receive the same treatment as Pro League matches and that meant displaying it through the holographic projection technology to the audience.

This aspect was added mostly for the audience. There wasn't any difference for the two competing teams. The holographic projectors just changed the way the match was shown. For the participants, they were still in the player booths, sitting and competing in front of their computer screens. They couldn't see the holographic projections; that was an omniscient view.

However, the media to the Alliance to the passion of the normal players clearly showed that the amount of attention this Challenger League match was receiving was unprecedented. It wasn't just because there was a powerhouse superstar team like Excellent Era present. To be honest, the reason it could attract so much attention was mostly because of the drama Happy had created.

As the match approached, how did each side see things? This was what the media was looking for and what the players were curious about.

So, on the Monday issue of Esports Home, they found their answer. In the interview with Excellent Era, Happy hadn't been mentioned even once. What Excellent Era was so fixated on discussing was just one name, Ye Qiu.

"Ye Qiu is a good captain." When Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan, spoke of this, his expression was tinged with complicated emotions. He asked the journalist for a cigarette and from what the journalist knows, Boss Tao had already quit for a while now.

That's what the reporter, Cao Guangcheng, had written in the interview with Excellent Era.

"Ye Qiu is a good captain, very impressive. He's brought an honor onto Excellent Era that no one has managed to surpass. This is something that we can't deny. If possible, I really hope that Ye Qiu and Excellent Era could be frozen in that perfect moment in time and continue that way forever. Unfortunately, nothing in this world stays the same. The Alliance develops, Glory moves forwards, we also have to keep moving forward. If we stand still and isolate ourselves, then I feel that we would have trouble keeping our competitiveness. Excellent Era is actually a very good example of this. After getting our three consecutive championships, we couldn't keep surpassing our limits, only hoping to keep our current pace. Yet that led to us watching as the other teams caught up one by one, snatching the championship from our hands."

"So in these years, Excellent Era has always been pursuing change. I hope we can find a way to survive that better suits the current situation of the Alliance; that's the only way to allow Excellent Era's continued and stable development. This sort of change, naturally, requires a cost. I had mentally prepared myself for this, but to be honest, I hadn't thought Excellent Era would be relegated. Being relegated was an accident, but what I say is that everything has its pros and cons. The year of rest we got after being relegated might just be the relaxed atmosphere we need to turn things back around for ourselves."

"Excellent Era might not be in the Alliance anymore, but if you ask me, I think Excellent Era is always looking forwards, positive, never giving up, no matter where we are, we only have one goal: the championship. We will never give up on working towards the championship. However, the road to this goal is longer than usual this time. We have to start from the Challenger League, and here, we met the greatest player we at Excellent Era have ever had, Ye Qiu. Yet now he's our opponent. To be honest, this is more surprising to me than Excellent Era being relegated."

"Recently I've heard people from other teams say, and of course, our reporter friends ask me, saying everyone is very curious, wondering if Ye Qiu had a spat with Excellent Era. Otherwise, why would he suddenly come back after retiring and go against Excellent Era in the Challenger League?"

　

"Heh, why Ye Qiu suddenly retired and suddenly came back, I think you should ask Ye Qiu this question! Though I'm close with him, I'm not a part of his mind. Of course, I understand everyone's troubles. Ye Qiu never accepts interviews from the media, so getting an answer from him is practically impossible."

"How he thinks about this exactly, I can't really guess, but I believe that I can tell everyone for certain that Excellent Era and Ye Qiu have no bad blood between them."

"Whenever there's a fluctuation in performance or rumors of transfering in the teams today, it'll always come with guesses like that. But in reality? It's baseless rumors. Excellent Era and Ye Qiu have no bad blood between them, but if you want to say we have some differences in opinion, that's true. Like if I say snails are delicious and you say pork is delicious. Can these differences in opinion be called bad blood?"

　

"These differences in opinion exist wherever people exist, so I won't go on about it. Now Ye Qiu is our opponent, and to be truthful I'm still not very used to this situation. How did Ye Qiu become our opponent? But this is alright, I respect his decisions. This time, let's battle it out as opponents. Of course, if he okay with it, I wouldn't mind going out for a drink together after the match."

Excellent Era's interview was attended personally by their boss. This was extremely rare. And in the interview, Excellent Era's boss seemed to have completely opened himself up, confidently, eagerly, and directly answering many of the questions everyone had about Excellent Era and Ye Qiu.

The only question he avoided was why Ye Qiu came to the Challenger League to face off against Excellent Era. He kicked that question to Ye Qiu for him to answer.

Those who were kept in the dark naturally would come after Ye Qiu for questions, but those who knew wanted to flip the table in rage. For example, Chen Guo.

"Shameless!!" Chen Guo slapped the newspaper onto the desk harshly, as if she was hitting Tao Xuan with this slap.

Tao Xuan had answered all the nice things and thrown the one trapped question right to Ye Xiu. That was such a sly move.

Chapter 998: A Storm is Coming

Excellent Era's boss Tao Xuan personally accepted an interview, this was definitely giving them enough face. However, after compiling the draft, Cao Guangcheng had experienced the cunning and intelligence of a boss level figure. In the interview, Tao Xuan fully expressed his and Excellent Era's tolerance and understanding of Ye Qiu's actions, but it was this move that was a needle hidden in silk.

Excellent Era was so understanding and generous to Ye Qiu, but Ye Qiu had led a team against them into the Challenger League, ready to fight to the death with them. With this, their images in the eyes of the public were clear. The only words, apart from traitorous, that could be used to describe Ye Qiu's actions was biting the hand that fed him.

Spectacular!

Cao Guangcheng couldn't help but exclaim to himself as he compiled the draft. So, how would Happy deal with this?

Though Excellent Era and Happy weren't sitting face to face together, one couldn't forget that the reporters interviewing the teams were all from Esports Home.They could easily guide the interview in any way they wanted to, and they could make the two interviews match each other. Cao Guangcheng was responsible for Excellent Era's side. He was only disappointed at not being able to interview Happy himself, getting Chang Xian to go for him.

Yet when Chang Xan came back and compiled his draft for Cao Guangcheng to see, Cao Guangcheng was furious.

In Chang Xian's draft, he saw that the other had written: when the past was brought up, Captain Ye Xiu smiled and then lit a cigarette, before eagerly beginning to chat with the journalist.

As expected, a famous teacher trains a fine student! This saying was extremely similar to the situation where he wrote about Tao Xuan "asking the journalist for a cigarette". However, under the same situation, Tao Xuan had made a needle in the cotton move, while Ye Xiu kicked his legs up and said: no comment.

Cao Guangcheng wanted to slam the desk and scold Chang Xian for this, then he'd be able to finally get everything he was holding in regarding Chang Xian off his chest. However, Cao Guangcheng knew very clearly, this wasn't that Chang Xian didn't put effort in, but that his interviewee wouldn't cooperate, avoiding the topic. If it was so simple to get what you wanted to know, then a journalist career would be far to easy. This draft gave Cao Guangcheng sufficient reason to doubt Chang Xian's ability for a while.

　

Despite being doubtful, he still had to use the draft. Even though it hadn't captured the point, this was still an exclusive interview. Currently, only Chang Xian could successfully interview Team Happy. The two reporters that were sent specifically to report on the Challenger League had become especially awkward once the tournament had reached the finals. That was because the two finalist teams didn't accept interviews from just anyone, forcing them to join the other reporters and media, lying in wait to ambush the teams' players for just a few questions here and there like paparazzi.

Compared to the amalgamation of what scraps they could pick up, god knows how much better Chang Xian's draft was. However, Cao Guangcheng was already prepared for the harsh scolding he was bound to get when turning these drafts in to the editor in chief.

As expected, not even an hour after the drafts were given in, the editor-in-chief called Cao Guangcheng's mobile, and unleashed a torrent of curses at him. Although the draft that wasn't up to standard was Chang Xian's, the editor-in-chief's first sentence was, "Little Chang is a newbie so it's natural that he might not be able to do well, but are you a newbie, too?"

Like how Cao Guangcheng ignored how hard it would be for Chang Xian to talk Ye Xiu into giving up information, the editor-in-chief also ignored how Cao Guangcheng didn't have any control whatsoever over the interview Chang Xian did with Happy, and slammed the big black pan onto his head*.

　

However, the end result was the same as Cao Guangcheng scolding Chang Xian. Though he had gotten shit for it, the draft still had to be used. They had hoped that they could get some tension and drama between the two sides, but in the end, one talked about the weather while the other focused on the food.

In the end, Chang Xian's interview of Team Happy deepened everyone's understanding of Team Happy as a team, while Tao Xuan's personal interview once again stirred up a wave of hatred for Ye Qiu among Excellent Era fans.

The continuous implications, resulted many uncertain Excellent Era fans, who thought that there might be more to the story, resolutely standing to the side of their team.

In the next few days, Chen Guo didn't dare look at the discussions going on online regarding this topic. Se was afraid that if she did, she'd die of anger. It was a good thing that the atmosphere in the team was stable, and Ye Xiu was as calm as always. This time, Chen Guo didn't get mad at Ye Xiu for being so calm. The finals were approaching and she was grateful for Ye Xiu's attitude, otherwise if he was easy to anger as she was, he'd have his mind in chaos and wouldn't be able to compete properly.

　

Yes, compete.

　

The current Ye Xiu was completely focused on the finals. These days, he was often discussing things with Wei Chen, with Sun Zheping, with all the members of the team.

This wasn't a last minute effort.

They had started preparing to defeat Excellent Era from summer last year, when Excellent Era was relegated.

　

Glory had an online game as its foundations, and this made it so that it wasn't just the tens of minutes on stage of one's performance that would influence the final result.

A minute on stage hid ten years of work. This saying was more or less appropriate for Glory as well. In this year, after putting everything they had into these behind-the-scenes work, the tens of minutes on stage was about arrive.

When it came down to it, everything depended on these tens of minutes. No matter how well you prepared, how much effort you put, if you didn't perform to your best in these few minutes, everything would be for nothing.

How would Team Happy face this final battle? Chen Guo didn't even know. All she knew was that this was what Ye Xiu had been talking to the others about recently. Some, she heard, some she didn't, but she never went and asked. She hoped that Ye Xiu could focus his time and effort completely on the competition. There was no need for him to explain anything to her.

At this time, Chen Guo seemed like the person in Team Happy with the least to do. Though she was usually passionate and energetic, she didn't seem to have any intentions on joining in any time soon. What she could do now, was make sure to not bother anyone. With this, she felt content and not at all left out or lonely. Seeing everyone so busy, she only felt security and warmth.

　

At times like these, Chen Guo was reminded of another person, a person who was currently in enemy territory.

Su Mucheng.

　

What was she feeling now? Was she like the members of Happy, doing her best in preparation for the match? Though Chen Guo hated Excellent Era now, she wouldn't find any wrong in it. This was the professionalism a pro player should show. They should put their best efforts into any match. Though a lot of uninvolved people tried to place many unneeded expectations and implications onto this match, Chen Guo could clearly see from Ye Xiu, everyday, that Ye Xiu didn't care at all about anything outside of the match itself.

Taking revenge because he had been forced to retire? He wasn't doing that. Having conflicted emotions because he couldn't bring himself to fully cut ties with Excellent Era? He didn't have that either.

　　

Yes, that's how it was. There was no good or bad, it seemed cold and cruel, but he faced Glory, and competition with this honest attitude. This was the oldest God of Glory in her eyes and with just this, Chen Guo felt that her years of being his fan hadn't gone to waste. This was someone worth respecting with all your heart because he could do what no one else could. For example, Chen Guo understood this logic and approved of this attitude, but she just wasn't able to to accomplish it herself.

She was unable to face Excellent Era with a calm heart. Thinking of what Excellent Era had done to Ye Qiu, she would just love to see Happy rip them apart a hundred times, and them tearfully kneeling in regret beside them.

Time went on, day by day, and the match day was getting closer and closer. Chen Guo made sure to take over anything that could disturb the others, while doing a good job on staring into space. Even if Chang Xian came over during this time, he would only be able to interact with Chen Guo, and when he saw Chen Guo's seriousness, Chang Xian didn't dare to bother the other members of Happy.

Friday. Match day. Esports Home released an issue. Team Happy and Team Excellent Era's face off in the Challenger League finally made the headlines on Esports Home's weekly issue, the topic bigger than any of the pro matches that were due to happen the following day.

On those headlines, the two words "Ye Qiu" were even larger than Happy. This was originally a fight between two teams, but for the media, who liked this sort of drama, focused on Ye Qiu versus Excellent Era. If Happy didn't have Ye Qiu, then no matter how talented they were, the fact that they were in the Challenger League meant that even at a time like this, they probably wouldn't be seen anywhere near the headlines.

In this issue, the reporters at the frontlines hadn't managed to get any firsthand information. Chang Xian didn't want to disturb them and Excellent Era had also closed themselves off to train, so Cao Guangcheng couldn't approach them either. However, in this situation, it gave them room to express their own opinions, describing what they had seen and thought. Thus, that tension of a storm about to come was fanned and fueled to its highest by the two. The two reporters took note on what they had seen and heard, describing the two teams they had interacted with in the past few days and placed that on the section left for the Challenger League. A costly section like the headlines obviously wouldn't have anything with actual, realistic content. It was usually just for the title to attract readers.

Esports Home's Friday weekly issue was sent to the newstands all across the city in the early morning and it was at that time that Happy boarded the Alliance-arranged coach to the stadium.

Although the match was in the evening, they had switched stadiums, so the teams had to warm up and familiarize themselves with the environment. After contacting Happy for their opinion, they sent someone over in the early morning to get Happy to the stadium for warm up. Excellent Era also got the same call for their opinion and were currently also on their way over to the place where the final match was taking place: Liulisong Sports Arena.

And then that's when the two teams met at the entrance to the stadium.

Chapter 999: Warm Up

"Hey, Old Ye!"

The one to greet Happy wasn't a random person, but Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan. As he called out, he walked over briskly. His tone of voice and conduct didn't lack cordiality. For a moment, Chen Guo felt dazed. Had she confused him with someone else?

Ye Xiu smiled and waved. It could be considered a greeting.

"You guys came quite early." Tao Xuan smiled.

"You guys did too." Ye Xiu said.

Tao Xuan's gaze shifted towards the members of Team Happy, sizing them up. He was a senior member in the scene. Wei Chen. Sun Zheping. If he tried a bit, he could recognize them. However, as the boss of a powerhouse, he didn't need to waste his time trying to make friends with players past their prime, so he treated them the same as ordinary players. He nodded his head as a greeting to the rest of Happy.

"Who would have thought? Your team is quite interesting. Happy, right? I never noticed that our neighbor was a crouching tiger hidden dragon!" Tao Xuan said and gave a smile towards his team. If their boss was smiling, how could they not do the same? All of the players in Team Excellent Era started smiling.

After Tao Xuan was done talking, he didn't wait for anyone in Happy to give a reply. His eyes turned towards someone in Team Happy.

Tang Rou.

The only person in Team Happy who truly interested Tao Xuan was Tang Rou. However, Excellent Era's Battle Mage position was taken by their ace player, Sun Xiang. Tao Xuan didn't have any intentions on replacing him. It was just that when he saw Tang Rou in Happy, he felt even more regretful than the other teams interested in Tang Rou　

"Miss Tang, it's nice to meet you." Tao Xuan ignored everyone else and specifically singled out Tang Rou.

With Tang Rou's background, she was someone who had experienced many things. She could handle any situation. She gave a polite reply towards Tao Xuan's greeting. Then, she heard Tao Xuan say: "Miss Tang, someone as talented as you definitely shouldn't stay buried. After this match, if you're interested, you can contact me at any time. This is my business card."　　

"Hey, what are you saying?" Chen Guo was listening on the side and flared up. Tao Xuan's words implied that he considered everyone else beneath him. Not only was he trying to recruit her in front of everyone, he was also hinting that Happy losing the finals was set in stone.

"I'm not saying anything." Tao Xuan smiled. His tone of voice was confident and at ease because Tang Rou had already accepted his business card and nodded her head, saying thanks.

"That's enough chit chat. I'll see you guys tonight." Tao Xuan called out to Excellent Era's players and started walking away. Excellent Era's players followed their boss. Not a single one glanced at Happy. Only Su Mucheng remained behind. She acted as if she didn't know and started talking to Ye Xiu and the others. Tao Xuan obviously knew about it, but when he turned his head and saw this scene, he didn't say anything and left the along with the others in Excellent Era.

"That guy is too infuriating. Why didn't you have any reaction?" Chen Guo looked around. Ye Xiu and Wei Chen were usually experts at making people angry. Why were they so calm?

"I just felt like it! Such a powerful boss personally ran over to talk some trash in front of us. It's not a trivial matter. I felt like I should give him some room to express himself." Wei Chen said in deadly earnest.

"Oh? Who was that?" An Wenyi and Luo Ji asked curiously. Tao Xuan thought he was some top dog, but he forgot that he was too high up. Ordinary people wouldn't recognize him. His trash talk had been prepared quite meticulously, but unfortunately, he didn't think that there were people in Happy who didn't even recognize him. They just saw him give Tang Rou his business card.

"Is he a scout?" If An Wenyi and Luo Ji had to make a guess, they would most likely give this answer.

Chen Guo wasn't able to get angry. She pulled Su Mucheng over and chatted about all sorts of things, but despite this being before a big match, she didn't mention Glory even a single time. Chen Guo was clearly avoiding this sensitive subject. After all, no matter how clear Su Mucheng's position stood, she was their opponent this match. Even if she faced them as a professional, what type of feelings did she have in her heart? As a result, Chen Guo felt like it wasn't good to talk about Glory.

After entering the venue, both teams had people specifically to receive them, and Su Mucheng had to go back to Excellent Era. The two teams were led to their lounges. The appropriate arrangements had already been set up in the venue. The two sides each had two hours to get used to the set up.

"Team Excellent Era said that you guys can enter the stage first to familiarize yourselves with the set up." The employee passed on the message.

"Okay. Thank them for us." Ye Xiu nodded his head.

"Okay. I'll relay it to them." The employee immediately left. The people in Happy wandered around their huge lounge. Even Wei Chen was deeply moved. In his generation, even pro teams didn't have such luxurious conditions. Stadium? What a joke. At that time, who had such nice accomodations? Finding some sort of building that could house a few hundred or a few thousand people was enough for a match. It hadn't even been ten years since then and teams now had their own arenas. Glory's growth could only be described as rapid.

"Not bad! Not bad! Really not bad!" Wei Chen touched and looked around. His spirit was trembling with excitement as he waved: "Come on! Let me see what the set up is like on stage."

Everyone in Happy left the lounge and walked through the player passageway to arrive at the stage.

From the audience's seats, there wasn't much of a difference compared to the previous venue. The accomodations were about the same. However, the decorations were completely different.The player preparation areas were all on the south side. The stage was split on the east and west. The center of the stage was a vast empty area, where the holographic projections could be shown. After nearly a season's baptism, the holographic projection technology was quite mature. Those in the crowd would absolutely have a different experience than those watching at home. It wasn't just as simple as the atmosphere.

After this change, the number of seats filled up in a stadium soared. The Alliance and the various teams had benefited greatly. This method would continue to be improved.

After Happy walked around their preparation area, they went towards the stage. For the players, the empty area in the middle for the holographic projections wasn't important because they wouldn't be able to see it in the middle of a match. The stage was their true battlefield.

Each side had six booths for the maximum number of players inside a team competition. The computers in front of the seats were all set up uniformly. It was an Alliance standard. Players could bring their own mice and keyboards. It was easy for them to plug those in. However, before the match, they would undergo an inspection to see if they complied with the Alliance's regulations. If a player forgot to bring their own equipment out of carelessness, there was no need to worry. The Alliance wouldn't cancel the player's qualification to compete. The player could borrow a teammate's or the use standard equipment provided by the hosts.

The players could start warming up on stage. The necessary inspections had already been done. The regulations for this year's Challenger League finals was quite strict. It was completely in line with the Pro League.

Everyone in Happy went to their side. They turned on the equipment and tried them out. Even Chen Guo got to experience the feeling of a pro player playing on stage. After checking out their equipment, they left and saw Wei Chen standing alone on stage staring blankly at the rest of the stadium.

Chen Guo didn't go up and bother him. She learned from Wei Chen and looked around. A retired old soldier like him had never thought he would return to such a familiar scene, but such a scene was happening today. What was he feeling right now?

Chen Guo turned his head to look towards Wei Chen. Then, she saw Ye Xiu also standing next to him. The two seemed to be having a good time smoking. The smoke swirled into the air for everyone to see.

Chen Guo was speechless at these two. Can't you leave some room for others to get emotional?

Although Wie Chen had never been on such a large stage, as a veteran of the scene, he had frightening adaptability. He wasn't like the young ones who checked out each seat curiously. Two hours soon passed. Team Excellent Era's players could be seen.　　

In reality, the warm up for the two teams didn't conflict with each other. The two hour time limit wasn't really a time limit. If a team wanted to spend another hour, it wouldn't violate any rules. It was just that right before the match started, all of the equipment would be inspected one last time. At that time, players were required to leave.

As a result, Excellent Era saying Happy could go on stage first was an unnecessary courtesy. Their arrogance as a powerhouse showed.

Only the players from Excellent Era came to warm up. Tao Xuan didn't follow along. When they saw that Happy was still there, they didn't say anything. After taking a look at their preparation area, they went to their area on stage. Just when Happy was about to leave, someone in Excellent Era suddenly said: "Hey!"

Everyone in Happy stopped. It was Sun Xiang, who refused to give up even after being ridiculed numerous times.

"Ever since the offline tournament started, I won every match 1v5." Sun Xiang held out his hand and waved it: "Tonight will not be an exception."

"This kid is hopeless." Chen Guo was helpless. Even she remained aloof at Sun Xiang's taunt. Sun Xiang's cried "The wolf is here!" yet the wolf never came. Who knew how many times this joke had happened.

Everyone in Happy ignored him and left the stage.

At 8:00PM, the Challenger League Finals officially started.

Chapter 1000: A 3v1 Arrangement

As expected, the finals didn't disappoint. There was still an hour left before the match officially went underway, yet the Liulisong Sports Arena was already completely packed.

This wasn't Excellent Era's home stadium, but the influence of a powerhouse was not something those at the level of Jade Dynasty or Mysterious Fantasy could compare to. In the finals, Excellent Era's fans gathered together. There were plenty of local fans and City H's most loyal fans, who would always follow the team into battle as Excellent Era's iron fan army; they too graced their presence for this match. Banners in support of Excellent Era could be seen all throughout the stadium. However, those hoping for tonight's victory were in the minority. More of them were pointing towards next year, pointing towards Excellent Era's sweep through the Alliance.

Just like the survey had found before the match, even though many were hoping for Happy to win, more people's predictions favored Excellent Era. As Excellent Era's most loyal fans, how could they doubt the superior team? In comparison, those who hoped for Happy to win just wanted drama. Cheer for them? They were afraid that others would think of them as idiots.

Despite the trend, there just happened to be a bunch of idiots. Among the sea of Excellent Era banners, that bunch held up Happy's logo high and shouted that Happy would topple Excellent Era. They became the joke of the surrounding people, but they didn't care. They were staunch supporters of Happy. The players and the characters from Team Happy had a connection that stemmed from the game.

"Happy! Happy!!" Seven Fields led everyone to shout with all they had. It was a reminder to everyone: don't ignore Happy.

Excellent Era's fans quickly discovered this small group of reckless people and flung all sorts of insults and biting remarks at them. Seven Fields and the others remained unmoved as they continued to express their support for Happy.　　

At 7:30 PM, the lighting in the stadium gradually began to darken. Everyone immediately became excited because this indicated that the match was one step closer to starting.

Whether it was the broadcast or the holographic projections, all of them required light. Watching a Glory match was similar to watching a movie. As soon as the match started, apart from the stage, everything else would be pitch black. If not for these conditions, it would have been very difficult for Ye Xiu's face to not have been revealed after so many years of playing.

When the lights went completely dark, the host began calling for the players to come onto the stage. First up was Team Excellent Era. The person at the front was Xiao Shiqin, who had transferred to the relegated Excellent Era because he was confident about Excellent Era's future. The spotlight shone on the player passageway. Xiao Shiqin walked out and waved to the crowd. He was no stranger to this scene, but it had been a year since then. When he saw the projection of Life Extinguisher appear next to him as he walked out, even Xiao Shiqin felt fascinated.

The brought to life character made a heroic battle pose. The crowd applauded. Afterwards, the spotlight shifted to Excellent Era's second player. The holographic projection on stage also changed.

This was the new way players came onto the stage. The crowd's spirits were thoroughly ignited. Excellent Era's fans cheered. The last player to come out was Sun Xiang. He and the pose struck by his character One Autumn Leaf made the crowd's cheers reach its highest point.

After Excellent Era was Happy. When the host announced their name, the stadium erupted with boos. When the host introduced Happy's first player, Ye Xiu, the boos reached its highest point. There were even curses and insults thrown in as well. When Ye Xiu's character, Lord Grim, appeared on stage, the crowd roared in laughter.　　

It was just a model, so the proportions didn't need to be rescaled. The character was larger than a real person. As a result, the character's equipment was even more clear, and the joke that was Lord Grim's mix and match equipment was magnified.

Lord Grim's equipment was all Level 75 Orange equipment, but it included cloth, leather, light, heavy, plate armour. How could the crowd not laugh? Such a dress style was too much of a novelty.

The crowd became even more hectic with their laughter. As Excellent Era's fans laughed at this set of equipment, they continued to curse at the ungrateful traitor. Some fans even tried to rush on stage, but were quickly stopped by security and kicked out. Towards such a controversial match, the organizers had made plenty of preparations towards possible behavior like that.

After Ye Xiu, the boos towards Happy clearly lessened. At the end, when Luo Ji and An Wenyi came onto the stage, there was practically no noise at all. Seven Field's group continued to cheer, but in this packed stadium, what noise they could make was rather small.

After introducing the players, about half an hour had passed. The two sides sat at their respective benches. At the player preparation area, Excellent Era's boss, Tao Xuan, personally came to watch over the match. Before the match started, he once again came over to give a polite greeting to Ye Xiu. Under the gazes of so many Excellent Era fans, he had to put in enough effort.

Soon afterwards, it was time for the final preparations before the match. The list of who would be playing in which match had been set. It could not be changed anymore. However, there had been a leak. With the new change in format, the Alliance might change this fixed player roster to teams picking their players at the match continued, but these were all after matters. The usual format would be used in this match. When it was almost 8 PM, the host called for the first players on each side to go on stage and get ready. Happy's first player stood up.

Tang Rou!

The first player sent out by Happy was Tang Rou.

This was Ye Xiu's arrangement. She herself liked it too because the first player sent out by Excellent Era should be Sun Xiang. Tang Rou liked to fight against skilled players. From Ye Xiu's analysis, the combo of Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf wasn't something any one in Happy could beat face to face. Ye Xiu had formulated many plans. In the end, he decided on Tang Rou first, meeting force with force. If the fire inside Tang Rou was ignited and she went beyond her limits to win, then that would be great. If not, with Tang Rou's Battle Mage style, Sun Xiang would also have to go all out. As a result, the second player sent out would be Mo Fan.

Mo Fan's quiet and extremely patient style would make it so that Sun Xiang would have nowhere to vent all the pent up energy he had from the previous match. That pent up energy would turn into annoyance. With that mentality, it would be easy for openings to leak. Mo Fan slowly contending with him was the most suitable. Even if he didn't win, Wei Chen would be up third. His shrewd and dirty style would be enough to deal with the extremely gloomy Sun Xiang.

Tang Rou, Mo Fan, Wei Chen.

These three were the first three players in the group arena lineup. This arrangement was to deal with Sun Xiang alone. Even though Sun Xiang had yet to beat them in a verbal battle, that wouldn't make Ye Xiu underestimate his skill in Glory so much so that he even arranged a 3v1 specifically to target him.

Tang Rou headed towards Happy's booths on the right side. At the same time, the matchup for the first round in the group arena was announced.

Team Happy - Tang Rou - Battle Mage - Soft Mist.

Team Excellent Era - Xiao Shiqin - Mechanic - Life Extinguisher.

Xiao Shiqin!?

Hearing this name come out, Tang Rou stopped in astonishment. She turned her head to look.　　

She hadn't walked far yet. She could clearly see from Excellent Era's bench, the person who was about to go up was that one wearing glasses, the player who looked like an intellectual.

It's not Sun Xiang? Tang Rou wasn't the only one surprised in Team Happy. Everyone looked towards Excellent Era's bench. Their expressions of surprise made Sun Xiang delighted. Sun Xiang was clapping and laughing out loud. He was pointing at Happy as if they were monkeys at a zoo.

"You thought the first player to be sent out would be me? You've been fooled! Hahahaha!" Sun Xiang wasn't going to let this opportunity pass and immediately called them out.

Xiao Shiqin turned his head to look at Happy and smiled. Then, he turned his head back and headed towards Excellent Era's booths on stage.

Happy didn't underestimate Sun Xiang, but from the looks of it, Excellent Era didn't underestimate Happy either. Was Sun Xiang provoking them with a 1v5 intentional? Or did the team make adjustments because of his brainlessness. Trying to figure that out was pointless at this time. Sun Xiang not going first made Happy's battle arrangements pointless. What's worse, Excellent Era very likely read Happy's likely plan and made their own counterplan.

Xiao Shiqin versus Tang Rou?

Just from the this matchup, Ye Xiu could smell hints of a counterplan. Having a highly intelligent tactician deal with a battle fanatic like Tang Rou was most definitely the correct choice, but then again, an intelligent player like Xiao Shiqin wouldn't be on the losing side towards any type of playstyle. Him leading might just be a safe arrangement.　

The unexpected arrangement disrupted Ye Xiu's plans. He had to analyze the situation. Even though the lineup had been set, he could give different instructions to the players depending on the circumstances.

Ye Xiu looked towards Tang Rou. He saw that when she found out that she would be facing Xiao Shiqin, she let out a rather regretful expression.

Ye Xiu understood Tang Rou's expression too well. It was just that she was giving out this expression towards a player like Xiao Shiqin. If the other side knew, who knew what they would think.

Xiao Shiqin was an All Star player too. Even if his title as a Master Tactician stood out more, even Sun Xiang wouldn't be certain he could beat him in a 1v1. For a player of this caliber, let alone Xiao Shiqin, even if Zhang Xinjie came over with his Cleric, it would be hard to say what the result would be!

Chapter 1001: Don’t Underestimate Your Opponent

Seeing Tang Rou's expression, Ye Xiu made sure to give her a reminder. He had to say something that stunned everyone who heard him.

"Hey, don't underestimate your opponent!" Ye Xiu ran out of his seat and called out to Tang Rou.

Underestimate your opponent?

Xiao Shiqin was heading to the player booths and almost tripped when he heard these words. What was that? It sounded very unfamiliar? How long had it been since he heard someone utter those words?

Xiao Shiqin steadied himself. He couldn't help but turn around and look. After all, he didn't really have a good understanding of Tang Rou's personality. From her performance on stage, Xiao Shiqin couldn't see any reason for Tang Rou to underestimate him. Could it be that after a year away from the Alliance, he had already been ignored to such an extent?

Don't underestimate your enemy. Xiao Shiqin stared blankly for a long while until he saw Tang Rou reach her player booth. Only then did he continue walking.　

When he got into his player booth, he had adjusted his mentality. He was an All Star player, who had seen all sorts of storms and waves after all. Something like that wouldn't drive him to his wit's end. However, he didn't lose his vigilance. He had a good grasp of Tang Rou's skill level from her match recordings, but perhaps she was hiding her strength? Or perhaps she had a mysterious trick up her sleeve that she had prepared specifically for him?

Xiao Shiqin carefully pondered over every possibility. It was this mentality that allowed him to become a Master Tactician, who cared deeply about the small things.

Ye Xiu warned Tang Rou not to be careless, but it resulted in Xiao Shiqin putting up his guard.

The match began. The map was Dockside Town. When the offline tournament kicked off, the maps chosen for the finals had been announced beforehand. A team like Excellent Era would certainly researched these maps thoroughly. They had no doubts that they'd reach the finals. As for Happy, just in the match against Jade Dynasty, Qiao Yifan had fully utilized the map to his advantage. Just from this alone, it could be seen that Happy didn't dare to be negligent in studying the maps for every match. Thus, their focus naturally wasn't as concentrated as Excellent Era's. Even though the map was new, Excellent Era's understanding of it was most likely deeper than Happy's The Esports Home issue released on this day had mentioned this point in the pre-match analysis. In addition to this, throughout the broadcast, the commentator hastily did some analysis during the map loading screen.

The Challenger League finals was a very important match. Even the broadcasting side wouldn't slack off. The previous broadcasts were all commentated solo, but for this match, the golden casting duo of the Glory League, Pan Lin and Lin Yibo, were both assigned.

After Pan Lin quickly introduced the advantages and disadvantages each side had for this map, Li Yibo lost no time and commented on how the map could be utilized.

"This Dockside Town carries the tradition of maps chosen by the Alliance. The style is all-around. Fighting in the water, streets, indoors, and so on could can all be taken advantage of on this map. But then again, I feel like calling this map Alley Town would be more appropriate?" Li Yibo commented.

"Haha, Coach Li, you're right. This map really should be called Alley Town. Okay, everyone can see that the two characters have loaded in. The one on the upper left corner of the map is Team Happy's Tang Rou. Her character is Soft Mist. The one in the lower right corner is Team Excellent Era's Xiao Shiqin. His character is Life Extinguisher, a character we are all very familiar with. He's left our sight for almost a year now! Now that he's appeared again, I'm sure many of our viewer friends are feeling reminiscent." The commentator Pan Lin said.

"The difference between him and the other players on Excellent Era is that Xiao Shiqin transferred into Excellent Era after Excellent Era was relegated last season. From this point, we can see his determination and foresight." Li Yibo said.

"Yeah, he obviously didn't join Excellent Era to play in the Challenger League. What he's looking at is Excellent Era's future next year." The commentator Pan Lin said.

"At this point, it should be the next half of this year." Li Yibo said.

"But he still has to help Excellent Era win this match first. Right now, the two characters have started moving. Tang Rou's Soft Mist is going straight towards the center, while Xiao Shiqin is moving more strategically." Pan Lin said.

"That's his usual style." Li Yibo said with understanding.

"Yes, I don't think there's a need to say too much about Xiao Shiqin. Then, let's talk about Team Happy's Tang Rou. What are your thoughts, Coach Li?" Pan Lin said.

"Hm, I've been paying attention to this player recently. Her skill is quite good. From what I've heard, there are numerous teams that are interested in her. Her future prospects are boundless!" Li Yibo said.

"Okay, Tang Rou's Soft Mist has already reached the center of the map, but there are no signs of her opponent."　　

"It seems like she's already realized that her opponent is moving more strategically. She's now having her Soft Mist move around." Pan Lin continued to speak as he watched the match.

"As a Master Tactician, Xiao Shiqin's playstyle is not limited to only one style. His style is dynamic. For a rookie like Tang Rou, who hasn't played Glory for very long, this could be quite fatal." Li Yibo added in a comment. From his omniscient view, he could see that Xiao Shiqin had already located Soft Mist and was currently circling around her.

"It looks like our previous analysis was correct. Excellent Era has a deeper understanding of this map. It seems like they've focused their research towards the finals early on." After seeing the path that Xiao Shiqin took, Li Yibo sighed with sorrow, "On the other hand, Happy's player appears to be a bit lost! A rookie's ability to grasp an unfamiliar map can't compare to a veteran's."

"Good! Right now, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher has already successfully circled around to Soft Mist's side. Tang Rou still hasn't noticed and is still moving forward. Ah, the terrain up ahead is very wide. Is she trying to letting the opponent find her?" Pan Lin said.

"If this terrain is used properly, she might be harassed to death by the Mechanic!" Li Yibo predicted how things would develop.

"Then what will Xiao Shiqin do? Life Extinguisher is quietly following behind her. Is he going to play dirty? Life Extinguisher hid a Bouncing Mine. It looks like he will be playing dirty! Mechanical Seeker has been sent out. And then….. Air Drop! Life Extinguisher summoned an Air Drop. He's going on the offensive!" Pan Lin said.

The two things nicknamed "Rising Winter Melons" flew above Soft Mist's head. Their stomachs opened and bombs rained down. Soft Mist rolled on the ground. After getting up, she dashed forward. The two "Rising Winter Melons" chased after her. The bombardment of bombs practically landed at her feet. A huge scene exploded behind her. Fire and earth flew everywhere.

The Air Drop was thrown behind her and kept on dropping bombs until the skill's duration ended. The instant the place quieted down, Tang Rou heard a kaka sound. She looked down. A little Mechanical Seeker had run up to her feet. Soft Mist hastily jumped up and her spear leapt at the small robot, creating a huge explosion.

"Tang Rou's reaction speed is very fast, but it's not over yet….."

Pan Lin wasn't able to finish his words, when he saw the airborne Soft Mist suddenly move towards the side.

"Ah, she dodged it??" Pan Lin cried out in astonishment.

From his omniscient view, he obviously saw it very clearly. After the Air Drop and Mechanical Seeker, Xiao Shiqin had thrown out an Air Compressor. This gadget used air pressure to attack the target. When it was initiated, it didn't release any light effects. The only clear warning was a bang, similar to when a champagne bottle was opened. The Mechanical Seeker's explosion covered up that sound, yet even in this situation, Soft Mist was able to evade it.

"How did she find out? How did she move in midair?" Pan Lin continued to be surprised. Usually, Coach Li Yibo would explain. Inviting him over as the guest was for him to interpret these complex interactions!

This time, when Pan Lin cried out, the person to his side was also quiet. He turned to look and saw that Li Yibo was also furrowing his brow in astonishment. It seemed like he didn't know either. The commentator didn't have to see through it and talk because these complicated situations were for the specialist to interpret. Li Yibo was their specialist in this case. If he couldn't see through it, it would be a bit embarrassing!

Pan Lin had already thrown the question out though. Even if Li Yibo couldn't answer it, he still had to give some sort of answer. He had the broadcast replay that scene for him. He carefully studied it, while the battle continued. Soft Mist landed on the ground and headed towards the Air Compressor.

Life Extinguisher's whereabouts had been exposed. He turned around and ran. Soft Mist chased after him; her foot landed on the Bouncing Mine that Xiao Shiqin had buried earlier.

The Bouncing Mine exploded. Soft Mist rolled, negating the knockback from the explosion. Soft Mist got up and continued to chase after Life Extinguisher, ignoring the scraps from the Bouncing Mine flying at her.

The broadcast seized the moment to play a quick cut of when Soft Mist leaped to avoid the Mechanical Seeker and her dodged the Air Compressor. The camera focused, zooming in on the instant Soft Mist's spear hit the Mechanical Seeker. Then, the replay went into slo-mo. Everyone saw it clearly. After the Mechanical Seeker blew up, the spear that should have been retracted suddenly moved sideways and stabbed into the ground. Soft Mist used this as leverage to quickly move through the air, allowing her to avoid that Air Compressor.

"In this instant, it wasn't possible for Tang Rou to have seen that Air Compressor, so there's only one possibility. When the Mechanical Seeker exploded, she heard the sound of the Air Compressor starting up." Li Yibo explained.　　

"This….. Is that possible?" Pan Lin asked.

"Uh, very experienced players might be able to differentiate between the sounds." Li Yibo said.

"But Tang Rou is only a rookie!" Pan Lin exclaimed.　　

"It looks like this rookie has extraordinary talent!" Li Yibo could only explain, but this explanation was actually correct. Tang Rou really did have incredible hearing.

Chapter 1002: Night-Blooming Cereus

The battle was still ongoing. After taking the chance to broadcast a slow motion replay, the camera quickly returned to the match. Pan Lin and Li Yibo hastily turned their attention to the match after analysing that quick exchange.

Against the damage from the Bouncing Mine's fragments, Soft Mist chased after Life Extinguisher's disappearing figure as the latter turned the corner. For Tang Rou, what was around that corner was unknown, but the audience had an omniscient viewpoint and could clearly see what was lying in wait. When Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher turned the corner, he immediately threw down an Electromagnetic Coil.

Electromagnetic Coil wasn't a trap which only triggered when stepped on. The effects of this skill was similar to a Ghostblade's Ghost Boundary, having an area of effect. It was just that compared to the flashy effects that a Ghost Boundary unleashed, the Electromagnetic Coil's power was much more discrete.

The clueless Tang Rou only cared about catching up as soon as possible with Soft Mist, eliciting a round of discussion from the spectating Pan Lin and Li Yibo.

"Tang Rou seems a little too hasty. If she pursues him like this, then won't she just fall straight into Xiao Shiqin's trap?" Pan Lin said.

"Yeah, any experienced player probably wouldn't engage a Mechanic with this sort of complex terrain. Mechanics have all sorts of strange gadgets, which are easily concealed in this sort of environment. Xiao Shiqin has very successfully led Tang Rou into an area where he can utilize his advantages to the maximum," Li Yibo said.

"Tang Rou has already reached the corner." As the match developed, Pan Lin's speech quickened as well. "Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher is actually waiting right around the corner, definitely waiting for Tang Rou to step into Electromagnetic Coil's range to attack. However, with his current point of view, it's not possible for him to track Tang Rou's movements, so how will Xiao Shiqin know when to attack?"

　

"She's in!" Pan Lin yelled. And in the data shown on the broadcast, one of the numbers immediately skyrocketed: Tang Rou's weight.

"Ah! Xiao Shqin's Life Extinguisher struck at practically the same time. How did he do it?" Pan Lin yelled.

"Probably by the sound of her footsteps…" This question wasn't hard for Li Yibo to answer. Many pro players were able to use the sound of another's footsteps to judge the distance between them.

"Rocket Punch! A Rocket Punch flew out. Under the effects of the increased weight, Soft Mist's movements are slower, making it harder for her to dodge."

"Ah! She's…"

"Dragon Breaks the Ranks!"

"Tang Rou resolutely activated Dragon Breaks the Ranks as soon as Soft Mist stepped into the Electromagnetic Coil's range. She didn't even bother to dodge the Rocket Punch sent out by Life Extinguisher!"

Soft Mist charged at Life Extinguisher with her spear raised to cast Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Because of the effects of the Electromagnetic Coil, Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn't have the usual amount of overwhelming speed, but they were at such close range already; how many steps did it take to turn a corner, after all? Dragon Breaks the Ranks might be slower than normal, but it still arrived at Life Extinguisher's side in the blink of an eye. The Rocket Punch did hit Soft Mist, but Dragon Breaks the Ranks had a higher priority than many grabs. Rocket Punch's impact couldn't do anything to stop its momentum.

Xiao Shiqin couldn't continue his offense, hurriedly making Life Extinguisher dodge, avoiding the Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

As for Soft Mist, she had used the charge to force herself out of the range of the Electromagnetic Coil through pure brute force. Without hesitation, she followed up by stabbing a Dragon Tooth at Life Extinguisher.

Life Extinguisher rolled to avoid it, and quickly opened up his Rotor Wings upon getting back to his feet. With a single rise and fall, he flew over the wall. During his descent, he even turned around to toss a grenade back. Who would've expected that, with just this glance, Xiao Shiqin got a glimpse of Soft Mist's right elbow twisting back, her spear dragging along, as a magical pulse began to swirl over the spear and shoot towards the tip.

The grenade landed and the spear stabbed forth, the magical pulse turning into a massive dragon. All that was blocking its way was a wall, so it smashed right through!

With an immense boom, the fierce Rising Dragon Soars the Sky tore through the wall. The skill ended there, but Soft Mist had already charged through the hole in the wall, the spear in her hand pointed at Life Extinguisher.

Wasting a powerful move just to break a wall? And before, preferring to use a Dragon Breaks the Ranks to push through the electromagnetic field instead of just stepping back a bit?

Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher had activated an Accelerator to hurry the hell out of there because the situation had spiralled out of his control a little. Tang Rou's extremely straightforward way of dealing with things had destroyed his rhythm completely.

As for Pan Lin and Li Yibo, they weren't able to say a single word about Tang Rou's choice of action. It was only until this cat and mouse situation that didn't have much to it that they realized that they had to continue commentating.

"This Tang Rou… er…" Pan Lin tried to formulate a response.

"It's crude," Li Yibo then said with confidence, "But she managed to succeed."

　

"Now Xiao Shiqin needs to adjust his rhythm. I trust that what happened just now will make him rethink his judgement of his current opponent. The way to deal with this participant, Tang Rou, how would you put this… it's not something on a technical level. Xiao Shiqin needs to get a better understanding of his opponent." Pan Lin said.

"Yes." Li Yibo nodded continuously from beside him. "Taking such a choice of action in this situation requires extreme courage, and Xiao Shiqin wasn't completely prepared for that. However, the match has only just begun; let's wait and see what happens next!"

"Life Extinguisher's Accelerator has ended, but Life Extinguisher managed to gain a safe distance, using the speed advantage given by the skill. Soft Mist hasn't had much of a chance to use any of her Chasers, so she has no buffs at the moment. I believe that Xiao Shqin won't give her the opportunity in the future either," Pan Lin said.

"Yes, after seeing the headstrong attitude of participant Tang Rou, I feel that Xiao Shiqin will avoid facing Tang Rou head-on, continuing to use a more strategic playstyle," Li Yibo said.

"Yes, now he's beginning to move strategically again. Let's see what sorts of arrangements Xiao Shiqin has in mind this time?" Pan Lin said.

Offstage, at Happy's bench, Chen Guo had thought that Tang Rou had this match in the bag. If it were any of their previous opponents, they probably would've been hunted down and crushed in shock by that relentless offense. Yet this match, Tang Rou's opponent was truly worthy of his identity as a top pro player. He didn't panic at all when Tang Rou destroyed his tactical rhythm, decisively retreating and bringing the match back to how it had been in the beginning with ease. He was still running and Tang Rou was still chasing, but in this game of cat and mouse, the initiative had switched hands twice already. At first, Xiao Shiqin was guiding the match, the initiative in his hands, then when Tang Rou mucked up his rhythm with pure brute force, she had snatched the initiative from him. Now, somehow, the initiative was back in Xiao Shiqin's hands.

The two characters darted about the Dockside Town, Xiao Shiqin using his gadgets in a continuous offense that Tang Rou found impossible to guard against. In comparison, she didn't seem to be able to do much of anything. She didn't manage to snatch a single chance to close in on her opponent like before. Who had the advantage was obvious; you could even say that Tang Rou was in the palm of Xiao Shiqin's hand.

"What… what should we do?" Chan Guo, watching offstage, was getting extremely anxious. However, from her point of view, it seemed to be futile. Xiao Shqin's playstyle seemed impossible to beat and she couldn't think of anyway that Tang Rou could turn this around.

Beside her, Happy's members were all very solemn, obviously not able to see a way out of this situation either. However, Tang Rou was someone who liked to create miracles. Accomplishing the impossible was her hobby. That's why everyone still held a thread of hope in their hearts, hoping that she would create another miracle to surprise everyone.

Yet, it never came...

The pace never experienced another change throughout the battle and, bit by bit, Soft Mist's health was chipped away until she fell.

Chen Guo couldn't believe her eyes.

It wasn't like she had thought it was impossible for Tang Rou to lose. She just didn't think it was possible for a match with Tang Rou in it to be like this. If you used a single word to describe it, then there was no more suitable word than depressing. The pleasant surprise that had erupted at the beginning didn't change the mood of the match at all.

Chen Guo watched as Tang Rou walked out from the player booth and off stage towards Happy's bench. Boos accompanied her all the way over and Excellent Era's fans didn't show any sort of mercy for a beautiful lady like Tang Rou. When Happy first appeared, Soft Mist was the core reason for the defeat of the face-slapping challengers. For these people, their hatred of Tang Rou was only second to Ye Xiu. Seeing Tang Rou lose in such a helpless way, the stadium was filled with cheer and Excellent Era's fans were revelling in her misfortune.

"This is only the beginning!"

"Who's next?"

"Now that's what disparity means!"

Excellent Era fans yelled aggressively, putting all their effort into making a ruckus, especially those in the section of the audience closest to Happy, doing their utmost to boo Happy. Excellent Era's win in the first round had lit a flame in these repressed fans' hearts. All this time, they had been waiting for Happy to be humiliated, yet that had come back to slap them in the face repeatedly. Now, their team had personally come to punish Happy, how could they not be excited?

An Wenyi and Luo Ji both looked around in surprise, obviously not prepared for this sort of situation. Never mind those two, even Wei Chen looked a little pale. Back when he was in the pro league, it wasn't nearly as impressive. The Challenger League didn't have any away or home game differences, but with the influence they had as a powerhouse, Excellent Era managed to turn Liulisong Sports Arena into something like their home turf.

"It's so bloody loud. How come it feels like we're in Excellent Dynasty Convention Center?" In the audience, a person seemed to be very annoyed by the cheering of the Excellent Era fans beside him, complaining as he pulled his hat lower. The so called Excellent Dynasty Convention Center was the stadium that Excellent Era played in for their home games. This person didn't seem to be a stranger to this sort of cheer.

　

"There's nothing we can do about it, Happy is losing rather terrifically, after all!" Another person said before tilting his head to the side. "What are you thinking, Little Gao?"

"Ah… Probably…" The one who was referred to as Little Gao also had his hat on very low, just like the rest of his companions, gazing at the familiar figure on Happy's bench.

Don't give in! Yifan.

Chapter 1003: Glory Really is Hard

The three hiding in the audience carefully spectating the match were three members of Team Tiny Herb, Xu Bin, Liu Xiaobie, and Gao Yingjie.

Although Liulisong Sports Arena wasn't Tiny Herb's home stadium, City B was Team Tiny Herb's turf. Hearing so many people cheering with such excitement for another team on their own turf made Liu Xiaobie, who was born and raised in City B feel extremely uncomfortable.

"Happy didn't take out too much of their opponent's health. The next few rounds will be rather hard on them." Xu Bin was the one whose focus was constantly on the match. After all, he had only transferred to Team Tiny Herb for a year now and he wasn't a local either, so in regards to emotions, he wasn't as involved as Liu Xiaobie.

"Yeah, I would never have expected…" Liu Xiaobie turned his attention back to the match, also expressing his surprise. Who in the pro circle had gotten to know Soft Mist earlier than them? Back then, it was still when the tenth server had just opened and everyone had been playing on level twenty something smurfs when they had first met this young lady.

The Soft Mist was a complete newbie back then, and now? In under a year… It was because of this sort of history that Tiny Herb's players didn't dare to underestimate her. In reality, if Tang Rou wasn't an irregularity among Glory players, she would probably be Liu Xiaobie and co's teammate by now - which Glory player would reject an invitation from a champion team like Tiny Herb?

"Who do you think will go next for Happy?" Xu Bin wondered. They weren't unfamiliar with Happy's players at all. In the previous battle for the newer bosses, the pro players had rotated in teams to fight off Happy's players, and gotten to understand them. One should remember, if two teams didn't enter the playoffs, they only crossed swords twice a year. Against Happy, they probably fought once a week during the battle for bosses.

"Yifan probably won't appear in the group arena, right?" Liu Xiaobie said after glancing at Gao Yingjie. He knew that these two young men were special to each other, and knew that the reason Gao Yingjie had decided to come today was to support Qiao Yifan.

"With the current situation in Happy, they just might have him play," Xu Bin said. When he joined, Qiao Yifan had already left the team, so they didn't have much interaction. However, after Happy rose to infamy, this name was often mentioned in Team Tiny Herb and Xu Bin knew who he was now.

"It's not Qiao Yifan…" It was then that Gao Yingjie shook his head, because he had already seen that the member of Happy that stood up to go onstage wasn't Qiao Yifan.

Mo Fan After his match against Mysterious Fantasy, this was the second official match of his since coming to Happy.

"How is it? How do you feel in this sort of competitive atmosphere?" Ye Xiu looked at Mo Fan, who stood up in preparation to go onstage.

Mo Fan originally planned to ignore everyone and head off to the player booth. Upon hearing Ye Xiu's words, he hesitated, but still stopped. He didn't even turn his head, just standing there and thinking for a good while before replying, "Noisy." After that, he walked towards the booth.

By then, Tang Rou had returned from the booth and when they brushed past each other, they didn't interact much. Tang Rou said, "Good luck" and Mo Fan simply nodded in response.

Tang Rou, having returned to the bench, wore an expression of disappointment. Chen Guo hesitated and didn't manage to say any words of comfort in the end. This match's situation really was rather ugly. Considering Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher's remaining life, Tang Rou had been crushed. It didn't even count as a morale victory, which made things very hard for Chen Guo.

"How do you feel?" She heard Ye Xiu ask directly and simply as she hesitated.

"Disappointed," Tang Rou replied.

"Heh, don't worry about it. No one in the entire pro circle would dare say for certain that they can win against a player of Xiao Shqin's caliber. You win some, you lose some," Ye Xiu said.

"I know that." Tang Rou nodded. She wasn't naive enough to believe that there really was such a thing as being invincible. Walking next to the river, whose shoes wouldn't get wet? That was the way competition was.

"But I was helpless against him," Tang Rou said. This was the point she was truly disappointed about. Throughout the entire match, she couldn't grasp any sort of advantage, being led around by the nose. This sort of helplessness was a terrible feeling.

"If this was something that could be solved with just a few words, then I would've told you them before you even went up. The person you were up against is one of the best in Glory. If he had any fatal flaws that just anyone could exploit, then he wouldn't be where he is now. Work on improving yourself, in all aspects. There'll be no more shortcuts from here," Ye Xiu said.

Tang Rou gazed at the replay shown by the projector of the match just now. However, there really wasn't anything to see in the last match. The opportunity Tang Rou had created for herself at the beginning of the match might count as interesting, but considering the results of the match, it was much less impactful.

"Glory… Really is hard…" Tang Rou sighed, gazing at the powerful yet helpless figure of Soft Mist.

"That's precisely why it's fun, no?" Ye Xiu asked.

"Yeah." Tang Rou nodded, her gaze already turning to watch the second match that was about to start. Her defeat had been devastating, but it would also provoke her determination to pursue this. She was already focused on the next match, ready to learn what she could from it.

As the hologram was projected, the second match officially began. The map wouldn't change in the group arena, but the spawn point would change randomly, but would usually stay in opposing corners.

"Deception, huh…" Xiao Shiqin gazed at the second player on Happy's side. Since this was only his second official match, the amount of info they had on Mo Fan was pitiful. However, just that one match had fully displayed Mo Fan's style.

Xiao Shqin had studied that match in depth, but he still didn't dare to let his guard down.

The last match was against Tang Rou, an opponent that appeared so often that there was a surplus of data for him to research. From Xiao Shiqin's view, Tang Rou's playstyle didn't have any strategic element to it. It used a simple and crude method to destroy an opponent's rhythm and build up a new one herself. In this, if she ever managed to succeed, her opponent would lose the initiative. Speaking mechanically, her ability didn't lose to any pro player.

Xiao Shiqin had thought he managed to fully understand Tang Rou's style, but who would've thought that in the match against Tang Rou, his rhythm had still been destroyed by her. That unreasonable and extremely offensive play style displayed a persistence that Xiao Shiqin had not expected at all. It was a good thing that he wasn't some random player, but a veteran. After having his rhythm destroyed by Tang Rou, the one who built a new one up wasn't Tang Rou, but himself.

　

With this prior experience, Xiao Shiqin had to revise his prior judgement. Did he hold back too much on his estimation of Happy's strength?

If this was true for Tang Rou, who they had a lot of data on and had done a lot of research into, then could Mo Fan, who they only had one match worth of data on, be hiding some huge potential?

"Okay, now the match has started. Xiao Shiqin is still choosing to move strategically. As for his opponent, Team Happy's Mo Fan, has only played one match in the offline matches, or rather, the entire Challenger League. Coach Li, did you watch that match?" Pan Lin began the discussion as the match began.

"Of course, that match left quite a lasting impression on me. It can be seen that this participant, Mo Fan, has extreme patience, and has an accurate understanding of when to attack and when to retreat," Li Yibo said.

"Heh, actually, this character's name, Deception, I believe many know, belongs to the infamous scrap-picker of the Heavenly Domain. Coach Li, do you think his playstyle and habits were developed through his scrap-picking?" Pan Li asked.

　

"I think that it's very likely," Li Yibo said confidently. "Patience, timing, being able to execute a full retreat, these are all very important skills a scrap-picker should have.

　　

"However, I think we shouldn't spend too much time on this topic," Pan Lin said.

"Yes, let's watch the match." Li Yibo didn't continue to speak about it either. After all, scrap-picking wasn't an honorable activity. Talking about the art in scrap-picking here wasn't a good idea.

Both sides had decided to move strategically, moving in a roundabout method towards the center of the map.

The place where the two characters should meet was currently devoid of life. As for Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher? He had stopped a little ways away from this area. His character didn't reveal himself, but instead sent out an Electron Eye, that drifted along the wall and over.

　

The range view of the Electron Eye wasn't as wide as the characters. In the limited shot, Xiao Shiqin looked around carefully. Then suddenly, snowflakes appeared in the shot and his view turned back to normal. Electron Eye's view had disappeared.

"As expected of an observant scrap-picker!!" Pan Lin cried out in astonishment.

　

"Yeah, he spotted even such a tiny Electron Eye. What terrifying observation skills," Li Yibo agreed.

　

"And from such a distance, such a small target, his shuriken was extremely precise!" Pan Lin added.

"This match seems to be a game of cat and mouse, but who the cat is and who the mouse is hasn't been decided just yet!" Li Yibo exclaimed.

Chapter 1004: Ninja and Mechanic

"Oh? Life Extinguisher has started to move." He had originally thought that the two players would need more time to figure out their opponent's location, but it looked like Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher made the first clear move. Life Extinguisher turned around, went into a secluded alleyway off to the side, and began advancing forward resolutely.

Pan Lin saw the alley. The direction that Life Extinguisher was heading towards was very obvious. Pan Lin started getting excited: "This direction... Life Extinguisher is trying to circle around Deception. Xiao Shiqin is already aware of Deception's location. He found out after that Electron Eye. Just what did he see?"

The broadcast immediately replayed the scene from the Electron Eye. Everyone's eyes went wide, but up until it was destroyed, no one saw anything eye catching.

"How did Xiao Shiqin do it? Coach Li?" Pan Lin asked.

When Li Yibo watched the replay, he had watched even more seriously than anyone else, because he knew that if Pan Lin couldn't figure it out, the problem would be thrown his way. That was his responsibility as a consultant, but this time, Li Yibo really didn't find anything from this replay. When Pan Lin asked this question, Li Yibo grunted as if he were about to reply, but then he suddenly said: "Wait, let's take a look at Mo Fan's Deception first."

Mo Fan's Deception suddenly started moving. He had been crouching down on the corner of a rooftop. At this moment, he drew back from the corner, but he didn't get up. He simply climbed in this way onto another rooftop.

"Does Mo Fan know Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher is moving towards him?" Pan Lin cried out in a surprise. Deception's movements were like a praying mantis hunting its prey.

From the omniscient view, the viewers watching could see the movements of the two characters and didn't dare to breathe. It was as if saying something would reveal the hidden movements of the two sides, but in the stadium, Excellent Era's fans were jumping and cheering madly because if this scene continued to develop like this, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher would be the ambusher.　

This was also why the competitors were sound-isolated from the outside crowd during a match. If not, a warning from a third party could affect the outcome of the match.

"Life Extinguisher is closing in. It looks like his target is obvious. Xiao Shiqin knows that the other side is hiding on this rooftop! But the problem is, that was before. Deception is no longer at that position."

"Life Extinguisher is still moving forward. Oh..."

When XIao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher was about to reach his destination, he looked like he was about to send attacks towards that rooftop. Because of his class's features, Life Extinguisher didn't need to approach. Right when Life Extinguisher was fiddling around with who knew what mechanical tools, Deception activated the Disappearing Body Technique and slowly climbed down noiselessly from the rooftop behind Life Extinguisher.

Cut Throat!

Deception initiated with an Assassin skill. His knife slid across Life Extinguisher's neck, and blood spurted out as a ray of cold light flew out. Xiao Shiqin only just noticed. Life Extinguisher didn't turn his head back and immediately rolled. However, Mo Fan wasn't slow. With a Broken Flash, he kicked the fleeing Life Extinguisher up into the air.

Storm Shuriken!

Deception swung his hands and a storm of shurikens shot towards the airborne Life Extinguisher. The shurikens wove a net. Let alone in the air, it would have been difficult to dodge even while standing on flat ground.

Life Extinguisher was hit by multiple shurikens. During this time, Deception had closed in. He swung his ninjato and struck Life Extinguisher with Flame Cut. Bang!

At the same time Deception cut Life Extinguisher, Xiao Shiqin had already counterattacked. Even though he was unable to dodge the cut, he was able to turn his body and fire a merciless gunshot at Deception.

It was only a normal attack, so the damage could be tolerated. Mo Fan seemed to ignore it. After getting shot, he leaped up and Bird Fell onto Life Extinguisher.

Boom!

When Bird Fall hit Life Extinguisher, a flame burst forth. That obviously didn't originate from Bird Fall. Life Extinguisher had stealthily thrown a grenade, which exploded when Bird Fall hit.　　

Life Extinguisher crashed into the ground because of Bird Fall, but Deception could not follow up. The shockwave from the grenade's explosion flung Deception to the side too.

"Beautiful!" Li Yibo shouted, "The timing of that grenade was too perfect. Everyone, look. If this grenade had exploded earlier, Deceptions Bird Fall wouldn't have landed. The shockwave of the explosion has lower priority than Bird Fall. Deception's attack would have hit Life Extinguisher, and Deception would have dropped to the ground along with Life Extinguisher. However, by having the explosion come immediately after Bird Fall hit, Deception was sent flying away, unable to continue his combo."

"Shadow Clone Technique!" Pan Lin suddenly roared.

Deception suddenly used Shadow Clone Technique, instantly teleporting to Life Extinguisher's side, but before he could attack, Life Extinguisher raised his arm. His punch seemed to instantly expand as it flew towards Deception.　

Mo Fan reacted extremely quickly. Deception stepped to the side and the Rocket Punch flew past him. By the time he turned back, Life Extinguisher had already rolled to the side. In his original location was a small gadget instead.

Bang!

Air Compressor's unique sound effect was extremely distinct. A high pressure air blast was released. With the distance between them, Deception had no way of avoiding it and was instantly sent flying into a wall.

Life Extinguisher half squatted on the ground. His hands never stopped to rest. Mechanical Seeker, Air Drop, Predator, Cruiser... All sorts of offensive Mechanic gadgets barraged Deception. At the same time, under the effects of an Amplifier, all damage from his skills was instantly doubled.

Boom boom boom boom boom…...

All sorts of noise erupted. Deception had only just crashed into the wall, and in the next second, he was covered by fire and light. Apart from gasping at Xiao Shiqin's combo, nothing else could be said. He had clearly been the one ambushed, but a short moment later, he was the one dealing more damage to the ambusher.

What could be done? This was a game after all. If this was real life, Deception slitting his throat would have been enough to instantly kill him, but in the game, life was a calculable statistic. A sneak attack would only let you seize the initiative. It wouldn't let you win with a single strike.

Excellent Era's fans had been worried for Xiao Shiqin the previous minute. Now, they were cheering again. The ones closest to Happy continued to shout.

"Did you see that? That's true skill! Skill!!!"

"Fucking scrap picker, go pick up trash!"

Just when the crowd was riled up, Life Extinguisher stopped attacking. The numerous bright lights receded. In the hole blasted apart by this fierce wave of attacks, there was no Deception to be seen. The only thing that lay in the hole was a charred scarecrow.

Ninjutsu - Body Replacement Technique!　

Body Replacement Technique and Shadow Clone Technique were similar, but because the substitute was a scarecrow, it was easy to distinguish it from the real body. It was mostly used as an escape tool. However, in the pro scene, there was no such thing as an absolute escape. A winner had to be decided in a match. Body Replacement Technique was often used like Shadow Clone Technique in this case. It was the sign of a sneak attack or a counterattack.

As soon as Xiao Shiqin realized something wasn't right, he immediately stopped attacking.

Where did Deception's real body go? Life Extinguisher spun around in a circle, but he didn't see any signs of Deception.

The teleportation range of Body Replacement Technique wasn't very large. Deception should be within his line of sight, but he wasn't. That could only mean one possibility!

The earth beneath Life Extinguisher suddenly started rumbling. A blade leapt up out of the ground. However, Xiao Shiqin already knew what was coming. When the effect of Underground Tunneling Technique was cancelled, Life Extinguisher had used Rotor Wings to fly up into the air.

Underground Tunneling Technique missed. Life Extinguisher immediately threw a grenade as a congratulatory gift. Deception hastily dodged and threw several shurikens at Life Extinguisher, but as the number one Mechanic, how could Xiao Shiqin's control over Rotor Wings be questioned? Life Extinguisher weaved around in the air, dodging all of Deception's shurikens.

Mo Fan saw that he couldn't get anything more and began retreating, but with the other side looking down from above, it wouldn't be easy to run. He could only use a skill: Ninjutsu - Smoke Bomb.

Thick purple smoke pervaded the area. The user of the skill would not be affected by the effects. Mo Fan had his Deception turn around and run. However, Xiao Shiqin immediately had his Life Extinguisher fly lower to the ground. The air flow induced by the rotating Rotor Wings dispersed the thick smoke. Not long afterwards, Deception was uncovered.

Mo Fan saw that quietly slipping away was impossible. He quickly formed a hand seal. While the cover from the smoke bomb had yet to be completely blown away, he activated Shadow Dance.

Upon seeing this, Xiao Shiqin had Life Extinguisher throw down an Electromagnetic Coil and then used a Rocket Propellor. Despite having the absolute speed advantage, he didn't retreat. Instead, he continued to throw down all sorts of tools in preparation to face Shadow Dance directly.

Mo Fan didn't mind. His goal was still to retreat. Shadow Dance was merely a distraction. Seeing that Life Extinguisher's attention had been attracted, his real body immediately ran outside of the range of Shadow Dance's heart, causing the numerous shadow clones to disappear, but then several Rising Winter Melons hovered over his head and exploded. The skills wantonly used to contest Shadow Dance weren't wasted. They actually headed straight for Deception.

Chapter 1005: Missing the Crucial Opportunity

"No wonder Xiao Shiqin is one of the Master Tacticians of Glory. His ability to switch targets is very quick and fluid. All sorts of gadgets are rushing towards Deception again, while Life Extinguisher is not in a hurry to head over. He's just like a general devising a plan. Being such an excellent Master Tactician, wouldn't he be even more outstanding if he were a Summoner, Coach Li?" Pan Lin said.

"Haha, I know what you mean, but I believe a pro player with qualities like Xiao Shiqin would be able to produce great results no matter what class he picked."

Li Yibo's answer was fairly evasive, so Pan Lin promptly gave a laugh as he caught on. "Haha, that's very true."

"Deception is now trapped by Life Extinguisher's attacks. Does he have any method to escape? The Body Replacement Technique is currently on cooldown. Oh, there's the Shadow Clone Technique! Deception used Shadow Clone Technique. Ah, it's unfortunate... The Shadow Clone Technique didn't allow to let him escape from Life Extinguisher's attacks." Pan Lin said.

"It seems like Xiao Shiqin was ready for all these methods and enlarged the effective area of his attacks. He should be starting to shrink it now." Li Yibo said.

"As expected, the attacks are focusing in on the true Deception. Ay, if Deception's current body is the substitute, while the substitute is the real him, wouldn't this be an opportunity?"

"Ah!" Pan Lin cried out after finishing his sentence because the Deception that was surrounded by attacks was instantly destroyed. It was impossible for any character to be so weak. Evidently, his theory had been correct. Deception actually used a clone to pretend to escape. This was done so he could lure Xiao Shiqin away. His real body would only start to take action when he got into attack range.

"Haha, Mo Fan actually did it, but the results don't seem to be too good!" Li Yibo said.

"True... Xiao Shiqin's target switching is truly too fluid and too beautiful!" Pan Lin gasped in admiration. In reality, this was because Xiao Shiqin's reactions were a lot quicker than the commentators. When Pan Lin was still talking about his theory, Life Extinguisher had already started to adjust his attacks. When Pan Lin cried out "Ah!", the attacks were already heading towards Deception's real body. The clone was simply taken down in passing as it was still within range.

Deception continued to suffer under Life Extinguisher's continuous attacks. All kinds of gadgets emerged nonstop: ones flying from the sky, ones scurrying along the ground, and even ones coming out from underground. Deception was dodging and running, but he couldn't even find any opportunities to escape, let alone retaliating.

The broadcast gave a close-up shot of Deception's Body Replacement Technique cooldown. Under the current circumstances, apart from waiting for the rescue skill to come off cooldown, there seemed to be no way out.

Everyone looked at the stopwatch and counted quietly in their heads.

Three, two, one…...

The clock flashed, and the Body Replacement Technique went off cooldown. Deception's hands started to form the hand signs. The action was so quick that it seemed like a blur for everyone else. His silhouette shook. After the fog scattered, all that was left behind was a straw dummy. At the same time, Life Extinguisher's focused attacks started to expand and increased in range.

Deception's straw dummy didn't attract any fire power. On the contrary, his real body started to receive attacks the moment it reappeared. . Although the attacks were weaker than before, there were only one or two seconds of peace before the attacks focused on him again. The lonely straw dummy was left in its original spot all by itself, and none of the attacks bothered to strike it.

"Xiao Shiqin was vigilant about this and calculated the opponent's cooldown time. This is one of the biggest differences between a pro player and a normal player." Li Yibo sighed at once.

Even though he had waited for the life-saving skill for so long, it didn't manage to save him in the end. Even though there was only one opponent, Mo Fan felt as if he were surrounded by tens of thousands of troops. No, it was even more serious than that. When he was scrap picking, although he was actually surrounded by many, they might not necessarily attack him. The scrap picking areas tended to be areas of conflict, so the players were too busy clawing at each other's necks. As a result, they didn't tend to scrap pickers as much.

However, there was only one opponent, so the focus of Xiao Shiqin's attacks was extremely obvious. Mo Fan tried to control Deception to break out using whatever methods he could think of, but none of them worked. It only took a single person to create such a impenetrable net. It has been a long time since Mo Fan had felt so nervous.

No one was born an expert. Mo Fan had been a noob before too. At the time, he was constantly put in dangerous situations where he was isolated and surrounded by enemies. Slips happened quite a few times. However, as he continued to improve, he could do as he liked in chaotic battlefields. Even if there were occasional slip ups, there were a lot of reasons for it. At least, he had never felt so nervous or felt a sense of crisis again.

Despite having only one opponent attacking him, Mo Fan felt as if the pressure of being surrounded by danger during his days as a noob had returned: He wanted to leave, but there was no way out.

Was this the end?

Amidst all kinds of explosions, Life Extinguisher's silhouette was faintly discernible, and his whereabouts were still rather ambiguous.

If he couldn't escape, what about attacking him?

When the thought popped up in his head, the silhouette appeared among the lights once again. Mo Fan subconsciously controlled Deception to throw a Shuriken from his hand.

Xiao Shiqin was cautiously controlling his skills. He had witnessed Mo Fan's excellent escaping techniques. Mo Fan could find opportunities at the slightest opening. However... he obviously lacked experience in high-level matches. If he didn't use the Body Replacement Technique right away, and left it available to use, it would have made things much harder for Xiao Shiqin. If a skill was used and it failed, it would be useless, but if it stayed unused, it would always stay a threat. The opponent would have one more option to be wary of. Unfortunately, he used it immediately. Next, the cooldown for Shadow Clone Technique was almost up. What would he do?

While Xiao Shiqin was thinking about this matter, something flashed on his screen. As a veteran, he didn't attempt to work out what it was, and controlled Life Extinguisher to dodge aside. When he spun his view to see what it had been, he saw that it was a Shuriken.

Not good!

Xiao Shiqin's heart tightened, this dodge resulted in a small pause in his attacks. If this was a normal opponent, they might not be able to grab this chance, but this guy was an escape artist. Would he let go of such an opportunity that he had created?

Xiao Shiqin hastily attempted to correct it, but as he expected, dodging the unexpected attack caused a tiny mishap in his rhythm. Mo Fan was able to grab onto this moment, and Deception's silhouette rushed out of the fires of battle in the blink of an eye.

"Sigh! It looks like I'll have to put in a lot of effort again..." Xiao Shiqin thought, but he didn't expect that Deception didn't leave after rushing out of his barrage. Deception flicked his hands and several more Shurikens flew out. Deception himself also followed closely behind.

He wants to attack!

Xiao Shiqin realized that Mo Fan wasn't planning to escape. After looking at the skills he had available, he realized that majority of them had been thrown out already. Deception had left them in the dust.

A skill that was used was equal to nothing! Xiao Shiqin was thinking about it just moments before, but he was now put in a similar situation.

Flame Cut!

Deception slashed down with a Flame Cut from behind the Shurikens. Life Extinguisher jumped aside, and activated the Rotor Wings to start to move. However, before he could move another step, Deception instantly dashed in front of him.

Shadow Clone Technique!

Mo Fan used it to block Xiao Shiqin's path. When he appeared, an attack was launched by a series of quick hand signs. He didn't give Xiao Shiqin any opportunity to guess which was the real character.

Ninja Technique: Hundred Streams!

Several streams of water shot towards Life Extinguisher like arrows. Life Extinguisher dodged, but this was exactly what Deception had anticipated. Deception jumped and stomped on Life Extinguisher's shoulders with a Bird Fall. The moment he pushed down, he swung out the rope's end on his ninjato. He was able to accurately loop it around Life Extinguisher's neck with a Body Bind Technique and threw him into the ground ruthlessly.

"He caught him! Deception caught Life Extinguisher! Xiao Shiqin is unable to get away this time." The commentator, Pan Lin, cried out. The stadium bubbled with excitement, Deception was completely suppressed just moments before, and he was able to suddenly strike back. Audiences loved these quick changes in pace the most. Of course, this wouldn't include Excellent Era's fans as the current situation had shut their mouths. They nervously watched Xiao Shiqin's performance, while they accumulated repelling energy.

"Mo Fan's wave of attacks is splendid, and the way he grabbed that opportunity was quite exciting. With such a counterattack, the situation should... eh? What?" Li Yibo was just commenting on Mo Fan's performance, and was about to give new anticipation towards this match. However, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher was able to break out within the time it took him to speak.

"Oh no, Mo Fan made a mistake. How could he let Xiao Shiqin break out so easily after spending all the effort to retaliate!" Pan Lin sighed.

"Flying Cicada Double Sting!" Pan Lin suddenly raised his voice.. His shout clearly contained anticipation. Unfortunately, all hope was lost in his continuing sentence. "The Flying Cicada Double Sting missed, it's too late... If it had been activated just a little bit earlier, it would have been better!"

"Indeed, there seems to be some minor problems in Mo Fan's linking of his attacks. When fighting against opponents like Xiao Shiqin, even the slightest mistake will be punished..." Li Yibo sighed.

"Mo Fan is still controlling Deception to keep attacking, but the chances are slim..."

"Mm, Xiao Shiqin has already readjusted, he's just waiting for his skills to come off cooldown!"

"It's begun!"

"He sent a Predator out, followed by an Air Drop... Mechanical Seeker is blocking the way. Deception has no way of breaking out, he's facing an encirclement once again."

"Sigh, what a pity." Li Yibo shook his head continuously.

Chapter 1006: Reverse Psychology

If Tang Rou's performance could be likened to a night cereus in bloom, then Mo Fan's performance was just the same flower blooming a few more times.

In the beginning, he had used a shuriken to destroy the Mechanic's Electron Eye, giving everyone a small surprise. Then, he managed to successfully ambush Life Extinguisher, giving everyone a small climax. Then, in a dire moment, he managed to struggle and create an opening, making a beautiful counterattack, and giving everyone an even larger climax.

　

However, no matter if it was a surprise or not, small climax or large climax, they were all extinguished in the blink of an eye. Mo Fan had caused some trouble for Xiao Shiqin, but it didn't manage to have any influence on the overall match. In the end, Deception fell in his struggle. Xiao Shiqin had managed to successfully one vs two. Even worse was that he hadn't taken much damage in either round. This round was a little better, after all, Mo Fan had managed to obtain a few chances to attack. However, overall, Life Extinguisher's health had only gone down by a third. Still having so much health after taking out two people in the Group Arena gave him a terrifyingly huge advantage.

"Mo Fan has thoroughly shown us his ability, but I think he still doesn't last long enough in those crucial moments. What do you think, Adviser Li?" Taking the pause in Happy's switching of players, the broadcast began replaying some scenes from the match, and the shots were mostly Mo Fan's shining moments. Pan Lin then began to commentate.

"It's true. Two times he managed to grasp the upper hand, but his opponent quickly turned the tables. This participant has many problems regarding how he deals with different situations. It's obvious that he is rather inexperienced. Let's hope that this match helps him grow a little!"

The two people commentating seemed to both look at Mo Fan in a favorable light. However, the audience present couldn't hear this. Even if they did, the Excellent Era fans wouldn't care. As Mo Fan walked back to the seats from the booth, he was sent off with boos from all sides. As a scrap-picker, most players hated him, so the jeering directed at him was confident and self-righteous. They could even jeer a little about Happy. They even accepted this kind of person into their ranks? Where was their integrity?

Mo Fan was emotionless, completely ignoring the noise around him and walking back to Happy's bench. Everyone looked at Ye Xiu, watching how he would communicate with Mo Fan.

Yet Ye Xiu didn't approach the other or even turn his head. He simply said, "Sometimes, it's better to save your skills for later."

Mo Fan didn't respond, returning to his seat without a word. It was only after a pause that he suddenly made a noise of confirmation.

As for the others, they were all solemn. Before, Chen Guo had even been imagining how Happy might be able to crush Excellent Era in an overwhelming victory, but reality was a cruel mistress. After two rounds, Happy had already lost two heads and only managed to take out a third of their opponent's health. Wei Chen, the third to go up, was uncharacteristically serious, not even saying anything shameless, just nodding his head at everyone before heading off to the booth.

The previous two matches had been complete defeats, unable to even show the difference between the strength of their accounts. Wei Chen with his Windward Formation, heading up now, was the one with the strongest equipment in all of Happy. However, his opponent, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher, was an All-Star level character. Disregarding the quality of the equipment, Windward Formation's eight pieces of silver equipment was nothing compared to Life Extinguisher in terms of quantity. Life Extinguisher had a whole eleven on him.

Chen Guo's optimism died completely. Watching Wei Chen walk step by step to the competition booth, anxiety rose in her heart.

　

They couldn't lose this round; good luck, Old Wei! Chen Guo silently encouraged. She saw him walk towards the competition booth, not even responding to the boos from the Excellent Era fans. Today's Wei Chen was completely focused because of the dire situation they were in. He didn't even have the energy to spare for shamelessness.

The third round quickly started and, as always, the characters spawned and the commentators introduced the players.

This was the third time Xiao Shiqin had entered the Group Arena already, so there was no need to introduce him again in such a short span of time. Pan Lin and Li Yibo's discussion naturally focused on Wei Chen.

"Those who haven't been fans of Glory for long would probably be unfamiliar with this player, Wei Chen. However, if there are any Blue Rain fans around you, you might want to go up and ask them about it. Wei Chen was the first captain of Team Blue Rain, and in the first years of Glory, he was one of the figures at the very top. I doubt anyone expected him to return after all these years. Wei Chen has often gone on the field in these past matches. Adviser Li, what do you think of Wei Chen's current status?" Pan Lin said.

"So many years have passed, but Wei Chen's playstyle really hasn't changed a bit!" Li Yibo exclaimed, casually making a boast about his experience, before beginning to comment. "From these few matches, he hasn't lost any of his experience or awareness despite not having fought in a pro match for so long, and he also has the advantage being of a veteran: his mental fortitude. However, in regards to performance, I feel that none of the past matches have really pushed him enough to show his limits. Maybe this match can show us what level he's truly at? How will Wei Chen respond to this player who is currently at the top of the Alliance?"

"Ok, let's turn our attention to the match. Xiao Shiqin has, again, let Life Extinguisher take a more strategic route, and Wei Chen's Windward Formation… Uh, he… wandered around a little and didn't leave, staying at his spawn point. Heh, this… seems to be exactly the same as how he started the past few matches! We can hear very loud booing from the audience present. Seems like the audience really doesn't like this strategy. I trust that after using it several times, Wei Chen is clear on what the audience thinks, but he doesn't seem hesitant at all!" Pan Lin explained the current situation.

"Heh, that's always been Wei Chen's style. For victory, he's willing to do anything," Li Yibo said in a tone that suggested he understood Wei Chen very well, once again lowkey boasting.

　

This time, Pan Lin decided to cooperate. "Actually, Adviser Li, you've fought Wei Chen back when you were a pro player, so if it's possible, could you analyze Wei Chen's intentions for us from an opponent's perspective?"

　

"This, it's probably a psychological tactic! When a player doesn't meet their opponent, very rarely will they guess that their opponent hasn't even moved. Not being able to find their target after so long, they'd begin to worry and become impatient. Meanwhile, Wei Chen can wait off to one side, building his advantage on a psychological level," Li Yibo said.

　

"But… Won't everyone know after they watch the match recordings?" Pan Lin said.

"Yes. It's precisely because it's so simple, that no one would expect him to use it over and over again." Li Yibo said.

　　

"Reverse psychology!"

"That's right." Li Yibo nodded.

"But… after the participant knows that there's this chance that he'll use it, they'll probably go over when they don't find him. That way, he can't build a psychological advantage!" Pan Lin said.

　

"Then what if they can't him find when they come over?" Li Yibo said.

　

"Oh…" Pan Lin came to a sudden understanding, "So this is to confuse his opponent and make sure they can't guess his intentions!"

"Actually, the intention of this playstyle is precisely to make sure his opponent can't guess his intentions," Li Yibo riddled out.

"Okay… Now we can see that Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher is approaching the center of the map. Naturally, he didn't find Windward Formation. Life Extinguisher seems a little hesitant; it seems like Xiao Shiqin isn't sure how to proceed!" Pan Lin said.

"It's because Xiao Shiqin must've seem Wei Chen's match recordings, so he knows of the possibility. And it's because he knows of the possibility, that he has to be wary of it. What he's afraid of isn't Windward Formation staying at his spawn point, but Wei Chen countermining him, making him believe that Windward Formation hasn't moved when he has is actually making his way over strategically." Li Yibo said.

"However, it seems that Windward Formation hasn't planned to do that now." Pan Lin said.

"But Xiao Shiqin needs to make sure." Li Yibo said.

As expected, Xiao Shiqin had Life Extinguishers wander around the area. After still not discovering his opponent, he began to make his way towards Windward Formation's spawn point.

"Life Extinguisher is coming; what will Wei Chen do? Will he have Windward Formation move and continue to trick Xiao Shiqin?" Pan Lin cried out.

　

In reality, the stadium was filled with booing, and even the audience watching the live broadcast on TV were getting impatient. No one was interested in a single man act like Xiao Shiqin running around trying to find his opponent; everyone was waiting for the two sides to clash. This made things hard for the commentator, who discussed this sort of boring situation as if it was extremely interesting.

　

"Life Extinguisher is quickly approaching, but Wei Chen doesn't seem too intent on having Windward Formation leave!" Pan Lin said, glancing at Li Yibo. The situation wasn't as Li Yibo had predicted.

　

"This is probably a reverse psychology of last time's reverse psychology*. Wei Chen predicted that his opponent might guess that he would move his character to try and confuse him, so he instead just left his character there, to achieve an unexpected goal," Li Yibo said.

"Uh… This… it's possible…" Pan Lin agreed uncertainty, looking at Li Yibo helplessly.

Reverse psychology of a reverse psychology, that was a tangled riddle that only Li Yibo could come up with. Pan Lin didn't know how skilled Li Yibo used to be as a pro player, but he dared to assert that Li Yibo must have great mental fortitude as well and wouldn't be defeated by any sort of trash talk. He was just way too thick-skinned.

　

Li Yibo carefully analyzed Wei Chen's actions and Wei Chen didn't disappoint him, staying there with his proud "reverse psychology of reverse psychology."

In the stadium filled of booing sounds, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher had finally arrived and the two characters faced each other. Wei Chen's Windward Formation attacked immediately, waving his hand and casting Chaotic Rain.

Chapter 1007: Details

"Life Extinguisher has entered Windward Formation's line of sight. Wei Chen immediately had Windward Formation launch an attack. Chaotic Rain has already been cast. Xiao Shiqin.... Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher dodged it..." Pan Lin instantly became excited as soon as the attack came out, but it ended up having a strong start but a weak finish. He obviously didn't want that to happen. He had hoped to talk about how Xiao Shiqin was caught off guard and panicked because of Wei Chen's sudden attack.

Unfortunately, Life Extinguisher dashed diagonally, nimbly circling around Chaotic Rain's effective range. Xiao Shiqin reacted without delay, not at all rushed. Evidently, Wei Chen's Windward Formation standing there and attacking didn't have any of Li Yibo's "reverse reverse psychology" to it. Xiao Shiqin had been prepared!　　

After dodging Chaotic Rain, Xiao Shiqin waited to counter attack. Another curse from Windward Formation flew over. A Hexagram Prison suddenly emerged, attempting to seal him in, but Xiao Shiqin reacted promptly and had Life Extinguisher dodge it too. At the same time, he also threw out a Mechanical Seeker. The little robot strode cheerfully, marching towards its target.

At this distance, Xiao Shiqin obviously wasn't hoping for this skill to damage Windward Formation. It was mainly to distract him, so Wei Chen would have to split his attention elsewhere and have a harder time locking him down.　　

Wei Chen seemed to not have noticed the robot though. Windward Formation waved his Death's Hand and continued to point it at Life Extinguisher. Curse after curse was cast, up until the little robot was about to reach him. Only then did Death's Hand move. A Curse Arrow shot out. Bang! The little robot was shattered into dust. Windward Formation didn't seem to be affected at all and continued throwing out attacks.

"Xiao Shiqin attempted to use a Mechanical Seeker to distract Wei Chen, but it failed. Wei Chen deserves to be called an experienced player. This type of method isn't able to faze him." The commentator Pan Lin saw this scene and quickly commented on it.

"After beating two clearly inexperienced players, Xiao Shiqin will need to make adjustments in this match. He can't keep playing like he did before!" Li Yibo sighed.

Xiao Shiqin didn't need anyone to remind him.

Seeing how his little distraction produced no effect, Xiao Shiqin was deeply moved by his opponent's efficiency. As a player who had joined in season four, Xiao Shiqin had never fought against Wei Chen before. In order to prepare for this match, he had looked up recordings from the past. From a tactics perspective, watching those past recordings didn't help much because of Glory's foundation in the game. As the level cap increased, new strategies and tactics would be created. Back then was still the Level 50 era. Those past tactics wouldn't work in this day and age. Xiao Shiqin simply wanted to get a feel for his opponent's style from these old matches. He felt like he wasn't getting enough information from the Challenger League. Most of the time, the gap between the opponents was too wide. There was nothing valuable to learn from those matchups.

From the match recordings of Team Blue Rain's old captain, Xiao Shiqin's deepest thought was that Huang Shaotian had truly inherited Team Blue Rain's glorious tradition of trash talking!

At the same time, Xiao Shiqin once again felt gratified at Yu Wenzhou, whose hand speed was no good. If Team Blue Rain's two ace players had both inherited that non-stop trash talking tradition, it would have brought disaster upon the entire Alliance.

How lucky, how lucky…...

After rejoicing inwardly for a bit, he obviously had some understanding of Wei Chen's style. Wei Chen was an aggressive player. His tricks or his disrespect for his opponents were simply a way to disrupt the opponent's mentality. Because after every little trick came a sharp wave of attacks. 　　

Warlocks were proficient at controlling their opponents. His style seemed to be made for this class. As for whether Wei Chen picked this class because of his style or the class made him play in such a way, Xiao Shiqin didn't know. From those past matches, Xiao Shiqin deeply felt that facing this player required staying calm and maintaining steadiness. This wasn't easy. You could restrain your actions, but how could you restrain what you felt? As a result, it could be seen from those past matches that many clearly strong players lost miserably against Wei Chen. The performance that those players displayed wasn't at all what it should be.

There were exceptions though. The one that stood out the most was his current teammate, Ye Xiu. In that year's match, Wei Chen wanted to distance himself from Ye Xiu to assail him with trash talk, but Ye Xiu rushed towards him and slapped him relentlessly until there was no future left in Wei Chen because he was already dead.

It was like that…...

Xiao Shiqin had thought up a way to deal with Wei Chen, and the person who gave him the greatest lesson just happened to be Wei Chen's teammate , Ye Xiu.

Life Extinguisher, who had been dodging Windward Formation's attacks the entire time, suddenly stopped and was hit by a Voodoo Curse.

It was only a DoT skill. Xiao Shiqin smiled. Life Extinguisher didn't dodge the attack and instead launched his own attack.

Hunter!

This wasn't the same as that Mechanical Seeker. Hunter was far faster than a Mechanical Seeker. As soon as the mechanical dog landed, it immediately pounced on Windward Formation.

Blood Siphon Curse, Soul Entanglement.

Life Extinguisher was hit by two more curses. Xiao Shiqin didn't have any intention of dodging those two, although he did dodge the Binding Curse. While he ate those two curses, Life Extinguisher launched two more of his own attacks.

Air Drop, Self-propelled Artillery.

After releasing Hunter, he started an attack from the skies and the ground. Even though Life Extinguisher was suffering from several debuffs, that wouldn't kill him so quickly. He used forceful attacks to destroy the other's control.　

Warlocks had cast times, so they had no way of casting curses under such concentrated attacks. Windward Formation withdrew and retreated.

"Windward Formation is falling back! Xiao Shiqin paid the price of three debuffs to win this opportunity to launch a dense wave of attacks. Wei Chen has no choice but to retreat. Windward Formation is starting to move. Hm... he's only going to here….. here….."

The commentator Pan Lin hesitated for an instant. Air Drop's surprise attack had arrived. Bombs dropped down from the stomachs of those Rising Winter Melons. Boom boom boom boom. Explosions erupted one after the other. However, these bombs exploded above Windward Formation's head, so the only things that fell were a few effect scraps. Windward Formation had found some cover for his head with just a few steps back. In the end, Air Drop was only able to get him to move to a different platform.　

"Wei Chen found some a good cover. Air Drop is unable to reach Windward Formation, but there's still that Self-propelling Artillery. Ah.... the Self-propelling Artillery can't reach here either. Windward Formation has a cover in front of him. Self-propelling Artillery isn't able to get to this height."

The machines summoned by Mechanics weren't huge fierce metal beasts. The majority of them were small precise gadgets. The Rising Winter Melons from Air Drop were about the size of a watermelon. The Self-propelling Artillery was even smaller. A washbasin was big enough to hold it.

Stopping these attacks wasn't impossible. If not, if Air Drop actually dropped bombs like a real bomber, wouldn't the map just get completely decimated?

As a result, Wei Chen found two covers, easily blocking both of these attacks. Behind those high walls, Windward Formation didn't delay and started casting. After reaching this position, he continued his attacks on Life Extinguisher. As for that Hunter, he had trapped it with a Hexagram Prison long ago. That stupid dog was fearless and tried to escape. It was a challenge of skill priority which ended with the dog being turned itself into a pile of scrap metal.　

Xiao Shiqin had eaten three debuffs to launch those attacks, but all of them were stopped just like that. What stood in his way had just been a platform and a tall wall.

"Wei Chen utilized the terrain beautifully, blocking Xiao Shiqin's attacks. We talked about this when the match first started. Team Excellent Era should have a greater understanding of the maps than Team Happy. Xiao Shiqin's performance has confirmed this conjecture. His familiarity with this map is as if this is one of his home maps, but it looks like the two details that Wei Chen used to block his attacks were details that he hadn't studied!" Pan Lin said.

"This... Xiao Shiqin might have known about them, but he probably didn't think that Wei Chen would be able to react so quickly!" Li Yibo said.

"It looks like Xiao Shiqin underestimated Wei Chen's familiarity with the map. Disregarding everything else, Wei Chen has never left this part of the map ever since he started. Even if he wasn't familiar with it at the start, he's got to be familiar with it by now! Haha...." Pan Lin said half-jokingly, but Li Yibo was surprised.

He thought of when this round first started. Wei Chen's Windward Formation didn't leave and instead strolled around the spawn point. Could it be that this guy really had been studying the map? He planned on fighting Xiao Shiqin here, so he utilized the time it took for Xiao Shiqin to reach there to study the area around his spawn point?

Yes, it must be like that!

Li Yibo was certain about his guess because at this moment, Wei Chen once again utilized the terrain to beautifully to negate Xiao Shiqin's attack. Pan Lin was currently in awe!

However, this discovery couldn't be talked about! Because previously, he had been certain that Wei Chen's movements at the start was a part of his "reverse reverse psychology". If he said that Wei Chen was actually utilizing this time to study the terrain, wouldn't that be the same as slapping his own face?

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

Chapters 264, 303, 326, 515, 525, 532, 539, 540, 544, 546, 548, 551, 553, 554, 556, 564 had missing sections on QI, which have now been fixed. 406 and 408 have missing sections too, but I can't edit those two chapters for some reason so those will have to be fixed at a later date. If you know if there are any other past chapters missing anything, please leave a comment below.

Chapter 1008: Focused Playstyle

This wasn't the first time Li Yibo had dug himself into a hole like this. With the experience he gained in all these years, his mastery of digging out was top notch.

"Wei Chen leaving Windward Formation there wasn't just a psychological battle. He even took that time to familiarize himself with the environment. Now he's able to utilize the environment to his advantage and grasp the upper hand firmly." Li Yibo was composed as he continued talking, still not denying the idea of a psychological battle as he explained his new discovery.

"So that's how it is!" Pan Lin was enlightened. He hadn't manage to notice that. As for Li Yibo's thick skinned eisegesis, he was long since used to it and couldn't be bothered to say anything about it.

"In fact, from the beginning of their exchange, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher has been continuously suppressed. The few times that he attempted to take the initiative back, he was easily thwarted by Wei Chen. These few counterattacks have fully utilized the environment."

"Ah! Life Extinguisher has taken yet another blow! Once again, the terrain was fully used to his advantage. The Curse Arrows struck from a dead angle and a Soul Slice from the right. Xiao Shiqin made the decision to let Life Extinguisher take the better of two evils, the Curse Arrows, but he never noticed that there was a Binding Curse in the shadows of those Curse Arrows!"

"Xiao Shiqin is in a very passive situation right now, but he's already understood where the problem lies. Look at his actions. He isn't trying to counterattack anymore, but turn and retreat to regroup," Li Yibo said.

"However, he's taken a Binding Curse, so taking another wave of damage is certain."

"Death's Door, Wei Chen has directly activated the powerful move Death's Door. He wants to trap Life Extinguisher in this corner! It seems like he's noticed the change in Xiao Shiqin's intentions and is willing to bet all his chips on this powerful skill, Death's Door. The duration of the Binding Curse is just enough for Death's Door's chant. Just this skill might not be enough! However, if this Death's Door hits Life Extinguisher, then he can use a round of attacks to deal massive damage to Life Extinguisher!" Li Yibo, who was usually composed and talking like a master presiding over the rivers and mountains, had now become excited as well as the match crescendoed. Everyone stared intently at the progress of Windward Formation's cast time. What would happen once this skill was unleashed?

"Ah! Life Extinguisher moved first!!!" Pan Lin suddenly yelled. "He's managed to struggle out of the Binding Curse early. Windward Formation's chant seems a step too slow."

"This is simply a character advantage! This is an All Star level character's advantage. Usually, the duration of a Binding Curse is more than enough time to cast a Death's Door, but Life Extinguisher's spirit resistance has allowed him to escape the Binding Curse earlier. Windward Formation's Death's Door.... Huh, this Death's Door…." Li Yibo suddenly came to a halt in the middle of his sentence. Windward Formation's chant ended a little too late, and this lateness was meant to be the crucial opening for Life Extinguisher's successful escape, but in reality, that wasn't what had happened, because this Death's Door had a larger range. Life Extinguisher might've been able to get the chance to run earlier, but he was still under the control of this Death's Door.

"Life Extinguisher didn't manage to escape! He's still within Death's Door's range. How come this Death's Door seems larger than the usual Death's Door we're familiar with? Coach Li?" Pan Lin said.

"Yes, this Death's Door does have a larger range indeed... at least two levels higher than the usual Death's Door," Li Yibo said.

"Two levels higher, how excessive!" Pan Lin was shocked. For a powerful skill like Death's Door, one level would cost an immense number of skill points, and for this skill, it's crowd control was more important for Warlocks who specialized in control, not damage. So, for this powerful skill, usual skill builds wouldn't max it out, only upgrading the skill to meet their needs. Especially for pro characters, they would be built according to their team's style, strategies, so they went for an efficient build. After all, skill points were limited, if it really was possible to max out all skills, then this problem wouldn't exist. For Warlocks, a maxed out Death's Door? That was common amongst most normal players, but in the pro scene, you couldn't even describe it as being like phoenix feathers and qilin horns, because it didn't even exist.

"This… is probably a habit from Wei Chen's years in the online game after retirement! Having gotten used to it, he probably finds it hard to change his habits," Li Yibo explained weakly. How would he know that the main reason for the grandiose Death's Door was that Windward Formation had more skill points than most pro characters. For many characters, investing in this skill would have been a burden, but for Windward Formation, two levels up was nothing, and his Silver weapon Death's Hand added a level, too. For other Warlocks it maybe excessive, but for Windward Formation, this was an economic build for him.

"Ok, though Life Extinguisher used his higher spirit to get out of the Binding Curse earlier, Windward Formation used his higher level Death's Door to keep him within the area of control… Windward Formation is now on the offense again, and Life Extinguisher… Life Extinguisher is continuously using gadgets, but within the range of Death's Door, this is simply a waste! Life Extinguisher hasn't just gotten on the field, this is already his third battle. Why would Xiao Shiqin waste so much mana?" Pan Lin was dumbstruck, staring at the match.

Originally, there was only one target in Death's Door, but Xiao Shiqin's continuous release of mechanical tools caused more and more miasma to coil out from the Death's Door, dancing across the field. However, these mechanical tools were fragile and and couldn't be controlled to dodge like the character itself could, mostly being swiftly caught and destroyed by the miasma. Even so, Xiao Shiqin continued to make Life Extinguisher throw them out relentlessly and black streams flew all over the area Death's Door covered, explosions everywhere, coming from the gadgets that Life Extinguisher was throwing out. Soon enough, the reason for his actions became crystal clear. Using this chaos, Life Extinguisher somehow managed to escape from Death's Door's range.

"Ah… Life Extinguisher escaped! The attacks Windward Formation sent in combination with the Death's Door didn't manage to hinder him at all. The field was too chaotic and this was all caused by Xiao Shiqin's willingness to sacrifice his mana to create this opening."

"Sacrificing mana to keep his health. This is probably the only thing Xiao Shiqin could do. Actually, this isn't the first time he's used this method to escape a Warlock's control," Li Yibo said.

"Oh?"

"He's done this in a match against Blue Rain before," Li Yibo clarified.

"Oh? Against Yu Wenzhou's Swoksaar?"

　

"Of course. Since Yu Wenzhou isn't as up to task regarding hand speed, he didn't manage to keep pace in such a chaotic situation like this and Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher managed to escape. For Wei Chen, he is no longer in his prime, so his reaction speed and mechanics can't keep up with a situation like this either. Blue Rain's ex and current Warlock players were both thwarted by this method of Xiao Shiqin's, this coincidence…" Li Yibo sighed.

"However, Xiao Shiqin still isn't a good position!" Pan Lin pointed out.

"That's true. He used a great amount of mana and doesn't have much left. If he can't consume it efficiently, his mana probably wouldn't last for the duration of this match," Li Yibo agreed.

"However, this is already his third round. What he's done so far is already enough of a victory!"

"Of course, it's almost a one versus three. Xiao Shiqin has already done his best."

The two were analyzing the match, talking one after the other. From their words, it was clear that they didn't think Xiao Shiqin had a chance to win this match anymore. Though he had successfully thwarted Wei Chen's plan to trap him, he had used up too much mana, and next, unless...

"Ah, Xiao Shiqin hasn't left. After a strategic repositioning, he turned around and went on the offensive!!" Pan Lin yelled in surprise. He and Li Yibo had both thought that after escaping, Xiao Shiqin would have Life Extinguisher leave the area that had been the target of Wei Chen's thorough research. They never expected him to turn after escaping and mount an offense.

"Uh, it seems like Xiao Shiqin feels that there's no point in stalling any further, hoping to use this wave of attacks to deal as much damage as possible to Windward Formation and pave the way for the next player on his team!" Li Yibo guessed.

"Air Drop! However, this time Windward Formation has no cover within reach… Just escaping from Death's Door, Xiao Shiqin has already used up a lot of skills, so most are still on cooldown. However, he's using what he can to initiate attacks. He added a lot of normal shots, making up for the lack of skills to combo! Wei Chen doesn't seem to be dealing with this round of attacks very well! That first Air Drop forced him to move and stop his attacks."

"Self-propelling Artillery! This cooldown ended just at the perfect time to be used there."

"Huh? There seems to be a Cruiser over there. When did he summon that? Windward Formation is retreating, trying to find cover against the Self-Propelling Artillery. Aiya, he's been trapped. Windward Formation's path was blocked by that Cruiser so he can't get to the cover he needs and can only face the Self-Propelling Artillery head on. Aiyou, he's not dealing with those blasts well!"

"The Hunter is in pursuit, too. Life Extinguisher's offense is very consistent. He's seen through Wei Chen's use of the environment. Windward Formation retreats, ah! A Mechanical Seeker darted out from around the corner and he didn't see it either. He didn't see it and was hit… Windward Formation was hit by the Mechanical Seeker's explosion and the Hunter has lunged for him… Coach Li… This…"

Li Yibo, who had been making a calculated guess about Xiao Shiqin paving the way for the next player on his team, was stunned by Xiao Shiqin's relentless offense and immediately opened his mouth to express a new opinion. "Is Xiao Shiqin planning to wipe Windward Formation out in one wave? Let's see if he can do it."

Chapter 1009: A True Mechanic

Eh, does Life Extinguisher have enough mana to wipe him out in one go?" At this time Pan Lin raised a question, one that almost everyone was concerned about. Life Extinguisher's mana was indeed very low, especially after it had been squandered in order to escape from the clutches of Death's Door. It looked as if it could run out at any moment.

Li Yibo didn't immediately reply. After carefully examining the situation for a moment, he finally responded. "Xiao Shiqin is currently using many normal attacks to connect his offense and suppress his opponent. He is being extremely careful."

"From their mana..." As Pan Lin looked at Life Extinguisher's mana consumption and Windward Formation's health decrease, he was momentarily stumped.

Li Yibo once again didn't reply. However, when he carefully examined the situation again, he too couldn't figure out the problem. From his observations, there was definitely insufficient mana. However, Life Extinguisher's attack rhythm was very steady. At this moment, when his mana had been completely exhausted, he had suddenly started holding his fire. Li Yibo thought that this kind of thing shouldn't happen when fighting against a peak pro player.

Digging himself into a hole was something that Li Yibo hadn't done infrequently. However, when he could avoid it, he always did. Now, he didn't dare to recklessly come to a conclusion, because he was very aware of the fact that players at Xiao Shiqin's level couldn't be completely understood by him in this day and age.

Life Extinguisher's assault continued, yet many of the spectators had already forgotten to watch the battle, instead focusing on Life Extinguisher's mana bar. They wanted to see when the light blue bar, which showed the character's fighting strength, would reach its limit.

Still not there, never there!

Life Extinguisher miraculously continued his attacks, fighting very conservatively. It wasn't at all like the previous two matches, especially not like the one with Deception, large-scaled and ostentatious. If the match with Deception could be called indiscriminate bombing, then Life Extinguisher's current offensive could be likened to driving a train, car after car cleanly crossing in front of you. Every car accomplished its mission, never failing once.

"A very efficient offensive . . ." After a long period of silence, Pan Lin finally jumped out with this line.

"Indeed," Li Yibo nodded. So far, Life Extinguisher had landed every hit without fail. Each blow had managed to achieve its purpose, something that was almost unbelievable on a professional stage. It wasn't as if his opponent was a corpse.

Except, at this moment Windward Formation seemed to be a corpse, being rigidly suppressed.

"Wei Chen ... has fallen into a trap." Li Yibo suddenly came to this conclusion.

"What?"

"Xiao Shiqin just reversed the situation, utilizing the terrain. Everything Wei Chen relied on before has suddenly become a trap. See ..." Just as Li Yibo said this, the screen showed Windward Formation backed into a corner from trying to evade the attacks. However, just as he turned, a land mine suddenly exploded. Wei Chen had nowhere to hide, because he was being attacked from all sides.

"When was that landmine placed?" Pan Lin suddenly yelled out. "Since Xiao Shiqin began his offensive, Life Extinguisher hasn't had a chance to visit this position."

"What about before?" Li Yibo asked.

"Before ..." Pan Lin suddenly had a vague impression, "It appears that he had come over, but at that time ..."

"At that time he was still being suppressed by Windward Formation's use of the terrain," Li Yibo continued.

Pan Lin was shocked. Absolutely and thoroughly shocked. He even forgot that he was currently providing live commentary. He had no words to describe the amazement he was currently feeling in his heart. Xiao Shiqin had actually placed a land mine at this spot at that time. This meant that he had already planned his attack at that moment.

Xiao Shiqin wasn't at all unaware of Wei Chen's strategy of utilizing the map. He had simply beat Wei Chen at his own game, using himself as an experiment to reveal Wei Chen's plans. In fact, he had already made plans to counterattack at that time. Every move he made now had been precisely calculated. This was how his highly efficient offense had come about.

Master Tactician Xiao Shiqin. His fundamental grasp of Glory had only truly been revealed at this moment. He had this sly old fox in the palm of his hand, completely reversing everything that Wei Chen depended on. The following offensive had pretty much followed a defined sequence of events. Every move pressured Wei Chen, giving him no choice but to respond as expected. And each of these responses unfortunately gave Xiao Shiqin more opportunities to make things difficult for him, to the extent that basic attacks became the main method of reducing Windward Formation's health. This could be easily seen in the statistics outputted by the system.

In terms of effectively injuring Windward Formation, the percentage of damage done by basic attacks was an astonishing 41.12%. This was indeed an extremely unusual circumstance, and as a result the broadcast specially cut to an image of the statistics to display to the viewers.

There wasn't another explosion nor another mistake.

Xiao Shiqin's movements truly seemed like those of a Mechanic, highly efficient and accurate.

Excellent Era was victorious. Xiao Shiqin had completed a 1v3, bringing Excellent Era a beautiful opening in the group arena, one that couldn't possibly be more perfect. The Excellent Era fans in the stadium couldn't control their excitement. The cheers they made drowned everything else out. Even words said face-to-face needed to be shouted to be heard.

In this situation, Wei Chen could only imagine the treatment he would receive. Yet, he was already past the point of caring about these things. As he returned to his seat on Happy's side, his face was grave, to the point that Chen Guo almost couldn't recognize him. His face was full of disappointment and concern, disappointment about this match, and concern for how the following matches would play out. This ... where was the shameless Wei Chen that they were all so familiar with?

"With Xiao Shiqin's successful 1v3, we can pretty much guarantee Excellent Era's victory in the group arena. The real question is how many points can they obtain."

"Under the new system of calculating points based on the number of players, even with this big of a lead, the team in the lead can't relax. Of course, Happy is even less likely to let their guards down. So, who will Happy send onstage next?"

The camera pointed towards Team Happy's preparation area. The person who stood up was completely unfamiliar to the camera, because prior to this, he had never allowed himself to appear on screen, refusing any coverage. Except this time, after coming out of retirement, he didn't seem to resist at all.

"It's Ye Qiu!!" Even though Pan Lin didn't recognize him, he could see who it was from the competition's lineup. "Now he ought to be called Ye Xiu, but simply changing a name doesn't erase much. Happy's fourth player is indeed Excellent Era's former captain, the founder of Glory's first dynasty, God Ye Qiu. After announcing his retirement, he suddenly established the grassroots Team Happy to return to the Glory scene. Throughout the Challenger League, he has brought us many surprises. And now, he and his team have reached the Challenger League finals, but blocking their path now is his old mother team, the team with which he won endless glory and countless cheers with. Now, Ye Xiu is representing Team Happy onstage. Team Happy has had a very unfavorable beginning in the group arena, while Excellent Era resolutely sent out their God Xiao Shiqin, showcasing his might in the group arena. Even though his character's mana is mostly depleted, I can't imagine that he'll back off easily. In the previous round, Xiao Shiqin also had this miniscule amount of mana, using basic attacks to dish out 50% of his damage and achieving an ultimate victory. How will he perform this round, facing against Ye Xiu?" As soon as he saw Ye Xiu onstage, Pan Lin was also excited. Why had this year's Challenger League received so much attention? Wasn't it just for this very moment?

"Ye Xiu is walking towards the competition area. Communicating in the stadium is very difficult now. If I took off my headphones right now, all I would hear is booing. That's right, sounds of booing. The audience is currently booing Ye Xiu very loudly. The following match is, in reality, one that many are unwilling to watch. Especially the Excellent Era fans; this booing is their protest. Their former hero has now become their enemy. For a long time now, this has been a type of cruelty in the pro scene. Ye Xiu had once borne the weight of far too much of Excellent Era's troubles. Now, his animosity is something that many fans are unable to accept. This type of attitude is something we can all understand. However, a competition is still a competition. No matter what, we're still hoping to see an exciting round."

"At present, Ye Xiu has already entered the competition booth, and both characters have already been loaded. The match is about to begin. From the data on-screen, we can see that Life Extinguisher truly has very little mana left. If he still wants to kill his opponent like this, then I think his normal attacks would have to make up for more than 95% of his damage output, right?"

From the moment Ye Xiu appeared, Pan Lin had remained excited. Even as Ye Xiu walked over to the player booth, he had talked incessantly, not pausing until this moment when he had finally given Li Yibo a chance to get a word in.

"He he, there's really no point in calculating this. Life Extinguisher's remaining mana really isn't enough to launch any kind of offense. Even during the last round, although normal attacks did a significant amount of the damage, the things that truly suppressed and controlled Windward Formation were still his gadgets. With Life Extinguisher's current mana supply, there's really no suspense to this match. Let's instead watch in anticipation for the dialogue these two will exchange!" Li Yibo said.

Dialogue?

There was no dialogue.

As the fourth round of the group arena began, Xiao Shiqin finally stopped relying on tactics to open the match. Instead, he directly controlled Life Extinguisher to move towards the center of the map, directly meeting Lord Grim in the middle. The two sides clashed without hesitation. Life Extinguisher's mana level was indeed too low to back up his attacks. After a few exchanges, Life Extinguisher's mana ran out completely, and afterwards, the match concluded in the most straightforward way possible: after typing out a GG in the public channel, he directly withdrew from the match. (Author Note: GG is a polite phrase used in esports meaning Good Game. If you don't know this, let me spread the word).

Withdrawing meant admitting defeat. In the esports scene, this had always been allowed, and Glory was no exception. Although Life Extinguisher still had some health left after his mana ran out, Xiao Shiqin decisively used this method to withdraw. No one in the audience felt much regret about this. Rather, they exploded in enthusiastic cheers and applause.

At this, even Excellent Era's boss Tao Xuan smiled in satisfaction, standing up to applaud. In this manner, he showed his support for Xiao Shiqin's decision to directly withdraw.

Continuing to skirmish and tiring out the opponent a bit would also have been okay. However, with this kind of dominating lead, continuing to fuss over small amounts really wouldn't be proper for a former dynasty team. Tao Xuan felt very gratified that Xiao Shiqin had not brought his habits from his previous team over to Excellent Era. This kind of relentless fighting really didn't suit Excellent Era, especially against this kind of opponent. As for Xiao Shiqin's performance, Tao Xuan was truly pleased. He had integrated into this team well, possessing the style that the team should have.

At this moment, Excellent Era's second player had already stood up, a youth that was unfamiliar to many people. Under the cover of the stadium's cheers for Xiao Shiqin, he silently walked towards Excellent Era's player booth.

Chapter 1010: Excellent Era’s Rookie

"Team Excellent Era's second player for this match is now heading for the stage. I believe many of you are unfamiliar with this pro player. His name is Qiu Fei, and was promoted from Team Excellent Era's training camp just this season. The team underwent large adjustments during the time of its elimination this summer. Three core players left the team with Xiao Shiqin joining. In addition to that, Qiu Fei was selected to join the front lines from the training camp." Pan Lin introduced the Excellent Era player upon his debut.

"Yes, if we add on the fact that Ye Qiu retired last winter, and the addition of Sun Xiang, Excellent Era changed almost all of their core members within the last year and a half." Li Yibo said.

"Yeah, especially their captain Ye Qiu, and vice captain Liu Hao. These two core player left. Then there's also He Ming, the member who appeared mostly as the sixth player in the matches. He and Liu Hao were traded for Xiao Shiqin, and joined Team Thunderclap. There was also Guo Yang, who joined Team Wind Howl last summer." Pan Lin introduced Excellent Era's trades.

"Mm, all the players that left Excellent Era are doing well this year." Li Yibo spoke.

"Indeed, they are now part of the main rosters of their respective teams. Team Wind Howl, which Guo Yang joined, also went through some large adjustments throughout the year. There's the addition of Tang Hao, the new ace, and Zhao Yuzhe, last season's Best Rookie, as the main roster's pillars. With the addition of a capable player like Guo Yang, Team Wind Howl's performance this season has been outstanding. We can say that the team has risen to the top of the the league, no?" Pan Lin said.

"Yes, for Team Wind Howl, they no longer have to think about whether they can make it to playoffs. They should be considering how they can make it to the finals." Li Yibo said.

"Liu Hao and He Ming have also been very good after joining Team Thunderclap. Team Thunderclap was very close to squeezing into the finals in the first half of the season. However, after the Glory's update in the winter season, Team Thunderclap took a hit to their placings and are currently slipping behind."

"That's unavoidable for updates like these." Li Yibo said.

"True, as for Qiu Fei, he's a rookie found by Excellent Era after all those outstanding players left the team." Pan Lin rounded back to what was currently happening.

"There's a lot of strong rookies this season!" Li Yibo sighed.

"Yes, like Lu Hanwen of Blue Rain and Gao Yingjie of Tiny Herb. Both of their performances this season have been outstanding, so much so that they even played at All Stars."

"I've noticed something interesting. The classes of Lu Hanwen, Gao Yingjie, and Qiu Fei coincidentally all match the class of their team's ace players."

"Yes... They will all become the future of their team as well as the league's."

"However, compared to Lu Hanwen and Gao Yingjie, who have experienced the matches from the league, Qiu Fei can only fight in the Challenger League this season!"

"Although he's played a few matches... uh, this might seem disrespectful towards Excellent Era's opponents, but I've got to say: the level of the opponents in the Challenger League aren't really a good judge of Excellent Era's level."

"That's true." Li Yibo agreed.

"That's why for Qiu Fei, this is the first challenge he's ever truly faced!" Pan Lin said.

"This is a pretty big one too. His first opponent is Ye Qiu."

"Yes, is there anyone else on this planet who knows Battle Mages better than Ye Qiu?" Pan Lin said.

"Keep it low, there are also a lot of outstanding pro players internationally." Li Yibo laughed.

"Alright…..." His words from before were only a form of hype, so he didn't try to argue back. He continued to talk about the highlight player, Qiu Fei: "If Excellent Era nurtured this player with the intention of making him the successor, then the first player he would have succeed would be Ye Qiu!"

"Obviously."

"Then when Ye Qiu was still part of Excellent Era, he would have taught Qiu Fei through words and example. The both of them might be familiar with each other." Pan Lin said.

"But Ye Xiu has changed classes since, and no one has ever seen this type of character before in the pro scene. No one would dare to say they are familiar with his class." Li Yibo said.

"But with Ye Qiu's familiarity with the Battle Mage, he wouldn't simply forget about it after changing classes! If it were like that, this match will be even harder for Qiu Fei." Pan Lin said.

"That's not entirely true," Li Yibo laughed, "Ye Qiu knows about the Battle Mage, but that doesn't mean he knows the player. The Qiu Fei that he knew was the Qiu Fei from one and a half years ago. Young players like Qiu Fei won't be in a set shape in all areas, so no one can predict his growth. If Ye Qiu is trying to understand him by sticking up with the past, then I believe Qiu Fei will definitely give him a surprise this match. There must be a reason for Team Excellent Era to arrange such a young player to fight this round. I think it might be based on this mindset."

Pan Lin was truly convinced by Li Yibo's thinking: "You are right."

"Alright, Qiu Fei has already entered the competition area, the match is about to start!"

When Ye Xiu started to appear on stage, the topics of the commentator increased. After the appearance of Qiu Fei, the two echoed each other and talked nonstop. Now that the match official started, Pan Lin's spirit also rose. He personally looked forward to such a showdown.

"The current screen is now showing information about Qiu Fei's character, Combat Form. Team Excellent Era is worthy of possessing the Battle God, One Autumn Leaf. Qiu Fei's Combat Form also has good equipment. His character has ten pieces of Silver equipment. This is comparable with many of the top God characters! The character's stats are also outstanding. 1314 Strength and 1310 Intelligence. Qiu Fei's Combat Form inherited One Autumn Leaf's style, where the Strength and Intelligence are relatively balanced."

"Haha, when I saw that data, I was also shocked! Those stats are even higher than One Autumn Leaf's!"

"Hahaha, it seems like you must have forgotten for a moment, that it's the Level 75 generation. You were probably comparing this data with One Autumn Leaf's data from the Level 70 generation."

"I was. It's a habit gained from commentating for a few years, so I wasn't able to adjust my mind at the time." Li Yibo said.

"I hope that, after this match, whether it's Combat Form or One Autumn Leaf, both will eave a new impression in your mind. Alright, the match has officially started. The map is still Dockside Town, and both characters have appeared at the spawn point, what will they do?"

"Oh! None of them are moving strategically! Neither of them are moving strategically, whether it's Ye Qiu's….. Sorry, he now goes by Ye Xiu, whether it's Ye Xiu's Lord Grim or Qiu Fei's Combat Form, neither of them are moving strategically. Both of them are heading straight for the center of the map." Pan Lin shouted.

"Mm, what Qiu Fei did was correct. Even if he could give Ye Qiu, uh... Ye Xiu a lot of unknown moves, in terms of tactics, I think it would be best if he didn't try to surprise Ye Xiu." Li Yibo said.

"You're right."

"As for Ye Xiu, if this were the first round of the group arena, he would have carried out some form of tactics, but after Xiao Shiqin continuously fought three people from Happy, the morale is in dire need of an increase. They would need a person to stand out and fight resolutely, then defeat them directly. This would be a way to boost morale. After all, the group arena isn't everything, there's still the team competition afterwards. If Happy is in fear of Excellent Era's grandeur, then they will definitely lose. The most urgent matter for Ye Xiu is to save Team Happy's morale."

"That's right. Okay, both of them have now gotten closer to the center of the map. They should be opponents that are familiar with each other, and they might still have the bond of teacher and student. However, they didn't exchange any words and headed straight towards the center to fight. There are still around 40 units of space between them, so they will meet soon."

"30 units! Oh! He attacks! Ye Xiu launched the first attack. Lord Grim is running while firing his gun." Pan Lin shouted.

"Lord Grim's Silver weapon is very interesting and can change into various kinds of forms. As far as we know, it already includes the weapons of the six main classes. This is why Ye Xiu can control Lord Grim to easily use all the skills an unspecialized can use among the six main classes. A lot of newer players might not know too much about the unspecialized class. This playstyle was popular for a certain amount of time in the early days of Glory. However, the main problem was changing weapons to use skills. As everyone knows, many of the skills in Glory can only be used with the corresponding weapon of that class, so an unspecialized would have to change his weapon constantly in order to continue using skills of all the classes. Putting the matter of how complicated and often he would have to change his weapon aside, the cooldown between changing weapons also needed to be taken into consideration. This would confine the options the unspecialized could take. However, the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim's hand perfectly solves all of those problems. The various forms of transformation his umbrella undertakes doesn't seem to have any cooldown. It could be said that this weapon is specifically designed for an unspecialized character. Okay…...we can save this topic for later, so let's watch the match for now." Li Yibo saw that the two had already clashed in the match, so he stopped with his introduction on the information.

"Qiu Fei controlled Combat Form to dodge Lord Grim's previous fire. Lord Grim didn't use a kiting method despite having the advantage of a greater attacking distance. He still continued to rush straight at Combat Form."

"Combat Form attacks and starts with Falling Flower Palm!"

"Lord Grim moves and successfully dodges!"

"Oh! There's a small detail here..."

"Tyrant's Destruction!!!" Pan Lin's yell cut off Li Yibo's attempt to explain. Li Yibo was helpless because the fight was intense from the very start. He didn't have the chance to take advantage of what happened to give some high-level explanations.

"Lord Grim blocked it! This is the Blade Master's Guard! Combat Form's Falling Flower Palm was connected very suddenly with Tyrant's Destruction. Lord Grim had no way to dodge, so he could only use Guard to catch it." Pan Lin cried.

Chapter 1011: A Confrontation Separated by a Year

"Sky Strike! After Combat Form's Tyrant's Destruction was blocked, he immediately followed up with a Sky Strike! How fluid! This is a very basic combo though. I'm sure many players in the game can do it, but being able to link them together so fluidly isn't easy." Pan Lin shouted.

"But Lord Grim was still able to evade it with a leap backwards." Li Yibo said.　　

"Mm... This type of basic combo probably won't be any threat to Ye Xiu." Pan Lin said.

"Yes, Qiu Fei needs to set his own rhythm and make things difficult for Ye Xiu to grasp. In other words, facing Ye Xiu, such fluidness isn't actually a good thing." Li Yibo said.

"Yes, Qiu Fei's playing is as precise as a textbook, but the problem is, the textbook was written by his opponent. If he continues to fight like this, he won't be a threat." Pan Lin said.

"His attacks have all been neutralized by Ye Xiu. Even though Qiu Fei has the initiative and is on the offensive, he hasn't dealt any significant damage to Lord Grim. He needs to keep a calm mind and not be so anxious." Li Yibo said.

"Dragon Rises from the Sea!" Pan Lin suddenly cried out. Qiu Fei took advantage of an opening and released a high-level skill.

"It still missed." Li Yibo continued, "There were no problems with the execution of this Dragon Rises from the Sea, but just like what we said before, it definitely matters who you're playing against. Facing Ye Xiu, your perfect execution happens to be the problem."

"But it seems like Ye Xiu hasn't been able to find any opportunity to counter attack." Pan Lin said.

"Uh... Qiu Fei is playing perfectly, so he isn't giving Ye Xiu any opportunities." Li Yibo said.

"In that case, Qiu Fei's playstyle isn't bad then. It's at least put him in a position where he can't lose?" Pan Lin said.

"..." Li Yibo was rendered speechless. This time, I fell into that trap way too easily.　

Luckily, it looks like the tides are turning!

Combat Form used a Sky Strike. Lord Grim attacked to block it, while simultaneously leaping backwards. This time, Qiu Fei didn't quickly follow up. Sky Strike had been blocked and Lord Grim may not have taken much damage, but because of the knockup effect, Lord Grim's leap backwards was affected and went a bit higher than what was expected.

This slight change became a turning point in this match. Combat Form thrust his spear forward with a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

Not many could see such a tiny detail. After seeing the high-level skill come out, the stadium erupted with cheers. Even Li Yibo shouted "It hit!"

But Dragon Breaks the Ranks missed. Lord Grim activated Rotor Wings and flew towards the sky, dodging the attack. The crowd felt disappointed. Li Yibo, who cried out "It hit", felt embarrassed.

"Haha, he used Rotor Wings to dodge it. Only an unspecialized can be so flexible! It looks like our Coach Li isn't too familiar with the unspecialized class either?" Pan Lin left this question hanging, when he saw Li Yibo's expression. He knew that Li Yibo probably wasn't too happy with his teasing, but he couldn't deal with it right now. The match was still underway!

"Falling Light Blade! Lord Grim uses Falling Light Blade in midair to directly come down. Combat Form turns around and stabs with his spear. Oh, it's a Circle Swing! Is he going to catch him? No! Lord Grim pulls his blade back to block the spear. His Falling Light Blade turned from an attack into a block. I'm sure everyone knows. Circle Swing's grab priority is somewhat different from normal grab skills. The spear has to hit first before the grab priority comes into effect. If not, then the grab is neutralized."

"Lord Grim lands at the rear diagonally. Combat Form chases after him. Dragon Breaks the Ranks doesn't have any ending lag, so Qiu Fei was able to react extremely quickly. In that previous exchange, even though Dragon Breaks the Ranks doesn't have a dead angle, Lord Grim's Falling Light Blade was a back attack! Who would have imagined such a young player could make such an experienced decision? Could this be the intuition of a genius?" Seizing the opportunity while the two sides weren't fighting, Pan Lin commented on the previous exchange.

After he finished saying these words, Qiu Fei's Combat Form rushed to Lord Grim's side. A Dragon Tooth came out. It was a very normal combo, but it was timed perfectly.

Lord Grim, who had just landed on the ground, turned around. He lifted his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and opened it up to form a shield.

Knight's Blind Shield playstyle?

Qiu Fei weighed it in his mind. He didn't doubt that Ye Xiu could use any class's playstyle. It was not just Battle Mages. Many of the playstyles for many of the classes in Glory had been created by him. There were so many that it was impossible to count.

Combat Form retreated one step. As he expected, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella was quickly retracted. The umbrella tip opened and an artillery shell flew out.

Combat Form's step back helped win Qiu Fei some time to react. Combat Form twisted his body and dodged the artillery shell.

"Woah, Ye Xiu's weapon opened up. It looked like he was going to use a Knight's Shield Blind playstyle, but in the end, when he attacked, he didn't hide behind his shield. It was still an unexpected attack! But Qiu Fei was ready. Everyone, look. Just before the attack, Combat Form took a stepback, giving him enough time to react. If he hadn't taken that step, no matter how fast his reaction speed was, he probably wouldn't have been able to dodge it." Li Yibo commented.

"Dragon Tooth! Combat Form used another Dragon Tooth. The cooldown on that skill is very low!" Pan Lin said.　

After dodging the artillery shell, Qiu Fei used a Dragon Tooth, which had just gone off cooldown. This simple skill was the fastest counterattack that could be made at this moment. The smoke from the tip of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had yet to dissipate!

But the umbrella canopy once again opened up.

Again?

Qiu Fei didn't dare be careless. He once again chose to retreat one step. However, this time, the umbrella canopy opened up until it was transformed: Myriad Manifestations Umbrella spear form. It thrust towards Combat Form from the same angle.　

Also a Dragon Tooth?

It was a clash between the same skills. In that case, whoever had the higher attack power would have priority. In terms of stats, Qiu Fei believed that his Combat Form didn't lose to Lord Grim. A Level 70 Silver weapon wouldn't be too different from a Level 75 Orange weapon in terms of stats, but the weakness was that unspecialized didn't have armor proficiency.

All 24 Glory classes had armor proficiency. When they used armor that the class was proficient in, there would a bonus in stats. And this was something that an unspecialized character couldn't possess. As a result, even if they were wearing same-level equipment, unspecialized characters lacked armor proficiency, so there would naturally be a disparity in stats.

Of course, more importantly... Lord Grim didn't have any Silver equipment apart from his weapon, so the stats of his equipment were quite obvious. Even though Qiu Fei didn't have the exact numbers, he could do a rough estimate of the capabilities of Lord Grim's equipment.　

Since both of us used Dragon Tooth, I should win the exchange!　　

Qiu Fei verified this thought in an instant. As a result, he didn't retreat and had his Dragon Tooth continued forward.

In this way, the two spears clashed. The degree of precision displayed was astonishing to see. However, right when the two sides clashed, from how the attacks changed due to priority, Qiu Fei determined that this wasn't Dragon Tooth.

Yes! Lord Grim hadn't used Dragon Tooth, but another Battle Mage skill: Double Stab.

The first attack lowered Dragon Tooth's striking power, but the first part of Double Stab was weaker in priority than Dragon Tooth. However, after the first stab, Dragon Tooth's speed had been greatly reduced, while the second stab came like lightning towards Combat Form.

Use the first hit to interrupt and the second hit to strike!

A bunch of words floated in Qiu Fei's mind. It was a technique commonly used by Ye Xiu. At the same time, it was also when Qiu Fei played for Guild Excellent Dynasty against Happy. When he fought against Ye Xiu, who had been using Soft Mist, Qiu Fei had missed the opportunity to use that technique, which Ye Xiu had pointed out to him.

A year had passed since then.

Last time, he missed the opportunity to use it. This time, he was hit by that very technique…...　

Thoughts floated through Qiu Fei's mind.. He thought of that match last year to when Ye Xiu was still in Excellent Era to when he was still in the training camp.

Team Excellent Era was a top team in the Alliance. The scale of their training camp was far greater than most teams. Among these trainees, nine out of ten dreamed of becoming One Autumn Leaf's successor, even if that trainee didn't play a Battle Mage. Nothing would affect this dream of theirs.

Qiu Fei had played a Battle Mage from the beginning. From day one in Glory, he had loved this class at first sight.

That year, Team Excellent Era won the champions for the third time in a row. God Ye Qiu's fame soared like the sun.

But this God never gave anyone a chance to meet with him in person. The only indication of him was the character that stood on stage.

Battle God One Autumn Leaf. The heroic pose displayed when he fought was deeply imprinted into Qiu Fei's mind. Later, he joined Team Excellent Era's training camp. However, he was different from the other kids. His dream wasn't to become One Autumn Leaf's successor. He wished to bring his own character and leave the same mark in battle like that year's One Autumn Leaf.

Who took a young child's dream seriously? As he gradually stood out in the training camp, Qiu Fei became titled as One Autumn Leaf's successor.

This was a position that who knew how many trainees envied. However, Qiu Fei's dream never changed. He liked his own character much better. He liked his Combat Form, and in Excellent Era's training camp, he finally got to see God Ye Qiu with his own eyes. God Ye Qiu was completely different from what he had imagined. The mysterious God Ye Qiu, who never appeared in public, wasn't as arrogant as most people thought he was. Everyday, with a cigarette in his mouth and smoke circling around him, he chatted with everyone at Club Excellent Era. He was the Alliance's number one player, but even Club Excellent Era's janitor could proudly say that he had fought a match against Ye Qiu before.

The janitor wasn't lying. Numerous people in the club played with this God before. Rumors said that whenever these people got into a conflict in game, if they couldn't win, they would pull Ye Qiu over to play for them, and Ye Qiu would happily go over.

God Ye Qiu dominated the Alliance, but he enjoyed Glory in the simplest and most ordinary ways. Qiu Fei had seen him play on an alternate account not just once or twice. Every time, the account was different too.

"Don't tell anyone!" The God would always look at him, "In a bit, I'll gift you a good piece of equipment." The God would always pat his shoulder and say.

How could there be any good equipment? The alternate accounts that God played on had the worst equipment. Who would have imagined that behind these trash characters stood the God who controlled the most powerful character in the Alliance, Battle God One Autumn Leaf.

Chapter 1012: New Skill

The God that Qiu Fei saw with his own eyes wasn't so spectacular that it was impossible to look at him, as he had originally thought.

The real God was very normal and simple, but it was easy to see that his love for Glory came from the heart.

Competition wasn't just about winning; it was a joy in and of itself.

Qiu Fei really liked this quote from the God and was eager for the day he could experience the joy of competition. He never relented in his efforts, hoping that this day would come sooner. Some of the other trainees laughed at him for being dumb. To them, it was way too soon for him to even be thinking about succeeding God Ye Qiu.

That wasn't how Qiu Fei thought. God Ye Qiu's successor? This was just a title given to him by others. As for him, he hoped to stand beside God Ye Qiu on the battlefield, enjoying the match and pursuing victory together! Although he was coincidentally also a Battle Mage and it was rather hard to become a core member when there was a class overlap, but, no one ever said that it was impossible, right?

Qiu Fei had worked hard to achieve this goal, and that God would occasionally come to the training camp to give him guidance or play a training match or two with him. His habit was to point out flaws during the battle and then find a chance to personally demonstrate them. There was a reason that he was a master of all classes. Excellent Era's training camp did consist of more Battle Mages, but there were plenty of other classes. That God could give guidance to any player of any class, even more imposing than the fabled cheat.

Qiu Fei hadn't lacked that God's guidance back then. Each time it would be his problems that were pointed out before that God showed them how to deal with the said problem.

　

Last summer, when the two met unexpectedly, that God had fought a training match of unprecedented standards, except that time, that God hadn't had the chance to show him how to fix those problems. Now, after a year, that God had finally displayed the way to combo after cancelling a Double Stab. Though this might have been a coincidence, Qiu Fei couldn't help but think of that training match he had last year. Was the unfinished demonstration finally being completed in this match? He couldn't dodge this strike...

"Combat Form has been hit!"

With the commentator's yell, Lord Grim followed up on the hit that Qiu Fei couldn't avoid.

"Sky Strike! Shuriken! Moonlight Slash! Gore Cross! Earthquake Sword! Shadow Cloak! Eh! Er… er…" Commentator Pan Lin was shouting out all the skills as Lord Grim used them, but then his voice trailed off. He wanted to cut in again a few more times, but before he could announce the skill, Lord Grim was already using the next skill.

All of them were level 20 and under skills with little end or starting lag, and Lord Grim's combo was kept at an extremely fast pace, and in addition, he wasn't using any combinations Pan Lin was familiar with. Thus, after a few skills, Pan Lin could no longer keep up with the combos and could only shut up in disappointment.

　

"Is he going to just keep this combo up for the rest of the match?"

Qiu Fei found Lord Grim's combo very alien. He was very much familiar with these skills, but the combination created from them wasn't something within his realm of study. His mind couldn't keep up with the combo. This wasn't just a lack of experience, but it was like stepping into an entirely new realm, as if he was going up against a class from a different game.

What made Qiu Fei feel even more helpless was that Ye Xiu predicted all of his attempted countermeasures, avoiding the chance of him fighting back and prolonging his own offense. The few plans Qiu Fei had tried to execute were all quickly foiled because Ye Xiu managed to adjust before Qiu Fei had a chance to properly put them in motion, causing all of them to fail.

"Will none of these do? Then it seems like I have no choice…"

The airborne Combat Form timed himself to grasp a chance and suddenly twisted. Lord Grim pursued him and made to counter, yet Combat Form's raised spear didn't stab towards Lord Grim, but rather at the ground beneath him.

　

A halo of light descended from the spear and sunk into the ground. Following that, a pulse of magic spread through the earth and Combat Form swung his spear in the air. Suddenly, the ground seemed to tear apart and chunks of earth were blown into the air exactly where Lord Grim was.

The new level 75 Battle Mage skill: Shattering the Lands! The skill could transfer destructive magical energy and eventually erupt like that to land a sneak attack on an opponent

Level 75 skills only appeared a long time after Ye Xiu had left Excellent Era. Ye Xiu hadn't helped Qiu Fei master these skills, so he had mastered this skill independently. This was finally something that Ye Xiu couldn't easily predict. This Shattering the Lands interrupted Lord Grim's offense and helped Qiu Fei balance out the situation.

"Very nice. This Shattering the Lands was used perfectly. As a level 75 skill, there's no standard method of using it yet, so every player uses it according to their own method. We don't know how well Qiu Fei has mastered these skills either, but in that instant just now, Shattering the Lands was used beautifully, immediately cutting off any possibility of Lord Grim prolonging his offense combo and giving him a wonderful chance to strike back."

"Combat Form advances!"

　

Having interrupted Lord Grim's combo, Qiu Fei immediately had Combat Form strike back. He started with Dragon Tooth, a typical opening, but still one of the most commonly used for Battle Mages, and Qiu Fei used it with the most focus he could gather.

Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm, Circle Swing… These four skills were the lowest level skills for Battle Mages, but the small and simple combo formed through these four skills was something any Battle Mage could use with fluency. Under Qiu Fei's meticulous mechanics, the combo was flawlessly executed. In an instant, the four skills were all used, but they were still easily neutralized by Lord Grim. Many people knew how to execute these skills flawlessly, but their countermeasures had also long since been perfected.

Lord Grim easily dodged the four skill combo, but he didn't expect Qiu Fei to suddenly perform another unexpected action, unleashing another level 75 skill.

Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

The spear was whirled, whipping up the winds with a magic pulse, and the magic pulse was injected into these winds, raging towards their target alongside the spear.

That was when Lord Grim opened up his umbrella, hiding behind it lightly, unafraid of wind or rain.

This time, Qiu Fei didn't back down, and instead stepping forward when the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up, slamming his attack right down against it.

Chapter 1013: One More Hit

The new Level 75 skills were studied by everyone. It didn't matter what skill level one was at. In the end, it was still something new. Those at a higher skill level would use it very effectively. Those at a lower skill level would easily get their attacks neutralized. While at the pro level, it was no longer as simple as if the timing was right or wrong, better or worse. What mattered was suitability. Every player had their own style. Every character had different stats. As a result, how a skill was used would be different. The variances from standard combos came from these differences. Pro players would make adjustments to these combos depending on their strengths and their style.

Qiu Fei was no longer that young training camp kid. He had always dreamt of his character standing on stage. From the very start, he never blindly imitated anyone. He had his own understanding of the Battle Mage and his own playstyle. It was true that Ye Xiu had studied the new Level 75 skills, but that didn't mean he could predict how every player would use them. Ye Xiu had a good understanding of Qiu Fei, but it was like what Li Yibo had analyzed. No one could predict how young players grew. After another year of growth along with Qiu Fei's own understanding and utilization of the new Level 75 skill, Qiu Fei had finally created his own style.

Falling Flower Palm!

Combat Form slid forward and smacked the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. Shields not only reduced the damage from an incoming attack, but effects like knockbacks were reduced significantly too. However, the reduction was directly proportional to the shield's weight. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella could swiftly change into different forms. As a result, could be determined that the weapon shouldn't be too heavy. Therefore, when the umbrella switched to shield form, Qiu Fei was confident that it would be unable to completely block Falling Flower Palm's knockback effect.

As expected, when the Falling Flower Palm struck the umbrella, Lord Grim was forced back. The path of the attack had been from bottom to top. As Lord Grim slid back, the umbrella also moved up, leaving a huge hole. Qiu Fei wanted this result and attacked with a Tyrant's Destruction. Even though he couldn't completely see Lord Grim, he knew that his spear would reach him.

The umbrella suddenly collapsed with a bang. The umbrella tip transformed into a gun and fired a round of bullets. Qiu Fei reacted quickly. Combat Form borrowed the momentum from Tyrant's Destruction to twist his body and dodge it. However, Lord Grim borrowed the recoil of his gun to slide even farther back, causing Combat Form's Tyrant's Destruction to miss.

"Wow... is this for real? The transformations from Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella are truly too unexpected." Pan Lin sighed, seeing Qiu Fei's attack miss.

"What's more important is that it can change forms instantly." Li Yibo said.

"But Qiu Fei isn't done yet!" Pan Lin shouted.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Combat Form raised his spear and a dragon roared out. Ye Xiu had predicted it though. Lord Grim forcefully changed directions while sliding back, but to his surprise, this Dragon Breaks the Ranks didn't move in a straight line. There was a slight curvature to it. Lord Grim tried to move away, but in the end, he fell into Dragon Breaks the Rank's path. Dodging was impossible. With no time left, Ye Xiu could only have Lord Grim Guard. This pure defensive skill had been completely maxed. Although it could reduce the damage from the attack, Dragon Breaks the Ranks had a much higher priority. Lord Grim's right hand holding the sword collapsed to the side under the pressure. Lord Grim was knocked back and also stunned by the attack.

"Beautiful!" Pan Lin cried out. He hadn't thought that after Qiu Fei's first attack missed, he would follow up again to quickly make up for it.

"Mm, this attack was very brave. Qiu Fei guessed that Ye Xiu would have Lord Grim dodge, but would he dodge left or right? I don't think he knew, but he still had Dragon Breaks the Ranks move in an arc. This is like a penalty kick. Left or right? He had to make a gamble. Qiu Fei is playing very decisively!" Li Yibo said.

"If that attack hadn't hit, the big opening would have been patched up." Pan Lin said.

"Of course. But he made the correct guess and grasped an opportunity. Glory is just this amazing." Li Yibo said in admiration.

"Yes. Even though Ye Xiu quickly put up a Guard and reduced the damage, he was still stunned by Dragon Breaks the Ranks. Qiu Fei has already started his combo." Pan Lin yelled, "Sky Strike into the air and using Chasers to keep the target afloat and stunned. This is a conventional Battle Mage combo, but this combo is also very difficult to pull off!"

"Correct. It's exactly because executing this combo is so difficult that it's given rise to the "Random Chaser Combo", which is much easier to execute and still very formidable. More and more players are starting to use it nowadays. In fact, it's actually very rare for someone to execute the original combo anymore." Li Yibo said.

"But in theory, this combo is impossible to escape from." Pan Lin said.

"That's only in theory." Li Yibo smiled, "Even Ye Qiu at his peak was only able to pull off an infinite inescapable combo that one time, no?"

"Haha, the first classic in the history of Glory. I've seen that clip. It's truly incredible." Pan Lin said.

"Yes, classics can't be reproduced. After that, even Ye Qiu was unable to do it again. Usually, an inescapable ten hit combo is already considered quite good." Li Yibo said.　　

"But we know that for the Random Chaser Combo, fifteen hits within a short time frame isn't anything difficult." Pan Lin said.

"True. The Random Chaser Combo's burst is much better and is easier to perform. In real combat, I think it's a lot more practical." Li Yibo said.

"But Qiu Fei is choosing this more difficult to control combo."

"He doesn't have a choice. The Random Chaser Combo requires a certain number of Chasers to pull off. There has to be at least four. However, Ye Xiu intentionally limited the number of times that they exchanged blows, making it impossible for Qiu Fei to produce many Chasers. Qiu Fei is choosing this combo out of helplessness."

"Then what about other combos?"

"Uh... well, if he can get ten or so hits from this combo, then the damage is quite considerable. Qiu Fei probably doesn't want to let this opportunity go so easily."

"Yeah, he's doing well right now."

"Yes, neither too slow nor too fast. It's already his seventh hit."

"Eight."

"Usually, ten hits isn't a problem. We'll have to see how long he can continue."　

While the two commentators discussed this, Qiu Fei had already reached ten hits. He stared at the screen, not daring to relax. He knew the difficulty of this combo and he knew how well his opponent understood it, but it was exactly because of his opponent's mastery over it that he could develop this combo into an unbreakable one.

Ten hits!

The passing line had been reached. Qiu Fei still didn't relax. It was a rare opportunity, and he needed to do as much as he could with it.

Eleven, twelve, thirteen....　　

The combo continued. Truthfully speaking, Qiu Fei didn't feel like it was that difficult. His brain seemed to be frozen. He was no longer thinking. His fingers moved instinctively, making it so that Lord Grim never left his spear's tip, making it so that the Chasers constantly flew about ready to use at any time.

Fifteen, sixteen. Qiu Fei felt excited. He felt like his condition today was extraordinary. Originally, he had been planning on finding an opportunity to end it with a high-level skill when it was about time, but he felt like he could keep going on.

All the way until death?

Pan Lin and Li Yibo started discussing this topic. The viewers were hoping for it, but Qiu Fei wasn't thinking about that.

One more hit!

That was the only thought occupying his mind. One more hit. He single mindedly pursued each hit, and he succeeded hit after hit all the way until twenty!

Qiu Fei's Combat Form, facing a Battle Mage master, had performed a twenty hit combo.

This was more than enough to make the crowd go wild with cheers. Excellent Era's fans felt incomparably proud. They had such a talented player! They felt like they were invincible.

But at the twenty-first hit, there was finally a slight deviation.　

No one discovered this deviation. Not even Qiu Fei did. He had already started his attack. The commentators and viewers were all waiting for this attack to strike.

But when this attack came, Qiu Fei saw Lord Grim's movements.

Twenty second hit?

Qiu Fei was the first to question it.

The attack hit, but Lord Grim had already transformed into smoke.　

Shadow Clone Technique!

When Qiu Fei realized it, the first thing he thought of was his back. However, the attack came from beneath.

Underground Tunneling Technique!

Lord Grim tunneled out from the earth and attacked. He followed up with a Knee Strike to send Combat Form up into the air. The combo started and in an instant, the comboer and comboed switched positions. Combat Form floated in the air as Lord Grim started his combo performance.

The crowd had been counting Qiu Fei's combo. When they were about to shout twenty two, Lord Grim's clone was destroyed and the words were stuck in their throat. In an instant, the combo count was reset. It was no longer Combat Form comboing.

"What a pity." Pan Lin wasn't worried about Qiu Fei. He was just sad that the brilliant combo had been interrupted.

"Being able to execute such a combo against Ye Xiu as a Battle Mage is already very outstanding. Only Ye Xiu would have been able to seize that tiny opening."

Li Yibo said solemnly, but where had that tiny opening even been? He had absolutely no idea. He didn't even know, and he said with certainty that Qiu Fei had exposed an opening. Ultimately, it was because he was also convinced that the original combo studied meticulously by Ye Xiu was unbreakable if performed perfectly.

Chapter 1014: Can’t Tell

The commentators had a lot to say to the audience on the combos of a battle mage, but when Lord Grim begin his offensive, Pan Lin was only able to keep up with announcing the skills for a while before he fell silent once more. The same thing had happened twice in one match: being forced to shut up because he couldn't keep up with the pace of the actual match.

The last time, Qiu Fei had unexpectedly used a level 75 new skill, interrupting Lord Grim's combo, but this time, he didn't seem to be able to find a similar opportunity. Combat Form was airborne, as if suspended there. Lord Grim darted about him, landing different skills on him continuously.

　

"Uh… This…" Pan Lin felt like he should say something. After switching to Qiu Fei's view, he spoke up with some uncertainty. "He's using Vanishing Steps, right?"

"Yes, it's Vanishing Steps." Li Yibo was much more confident on this than Pan Lin.

However, after confirming this, the two couldn't help but exchange a glance. They had both realized something was a little strange.

No matter when a high-end technique like Vanishing Step was used, it would count as a climax to the match. So shouldn't they commentate about this with some sort of passion?

Yet what did they do? They were both unnaturally calm. This was because the person on the field was called Ye Xiu. To a normal player using Vanishing Step was a climax, but Ye Xiu using Vanishing Step, wasn't that as simple as eating?

In reality, both of them knew that was too much of an exaggeration. No matter who was behind it, the use of Vanishing Step would never be as a easy as eating. Like a software that a CPU could only use smoothly when at 90%. Even if Ye Xiu had better hardware, there was still a limit to his actual abilities. Comparing him to the other Gods of the Alliance, on par was the best description.

Yet when Ye Xiu used these high-end techniques, Pan Lin and Li Yibo would think it very normal. If it was another God, like Wang Jiexi, Huang Shaotian, Zhou Zekai, no matter who it was, Pan Lin would probably be willing to yell about it until his voice gave out.

That was what you called influence.

In the hearts of these people, who had been with Glory for a long time, there would always be an unshakable and powerful figure, and that figure was, without a doubt, Ye Xiu. When he accomplished something extraordinary, people had higher expectations of him, and what was extraordinary became ordinary.

It's just a Vanishing Step, that's all.

If someone dared say that casually, they'd probably get slapped by the millions of people that played Glory.

　　

But when you added Ye Xiu to the sentence, it suddenly seemed much more reasonable.

It was because of this that Pan Lin and Li Yibo kept their cool when Ye Xiu used Vanishing Step. By then, the program director had cut the shot to Qiu Fei's view already, waiting for them to commentate on this spectacular moment.

"So, Vanishing Step, what Ye Xiu is using right now is actually a very high end technique, Vanishing Step. What we're currently broadcasting is Qiu Fei's view. You can see here that Lord Grim's figure never appears in Qiu Fei's view. Huh?"

Just as Pan Lin said this, Lord Grim's figure appeared in Qiu Fei's view.

"Chance!" It was then that excitement got to Pan Lin and he suddenly yelled.

The broadcasted shot switched back to the battle at large: Combat Form was still suspended in the air, Lord Grim was still darting about, his attacks not stopping… The situation hadn't changed at all.

　

"Ah, what a shame!" Pan Lin sighed. He thought that it was Qiu Fei who had missed the opportunity. Li Yibo coughed a little, but couldn't really correct Pan Lin on this. They were live!

The so-called chance that Pan Lin had been yelling about, wasn't actually any sort of opportunity. The foundations to the Vanishing Step were built on finding an opponent's blind spot and attacking from there. Here, landing the attack was the ultimate goal and walking into the opponent's blindspot was simply a method to achieve this goal more easily. So, when you could easily hit an opponent, there was no need to expend any excessive effort into finding the said blindspot.

The reason Lord Grim had wandered into Qiu Fei's view was because in that moment, there was no need for him to conceal his attack using Qiu Fei's blindspot.

He actually managed to do that!

If he didn't check Qiu Fei's view, there was no way Li Yibo would've noticed that. After noticing it, Li Yibo was shaken. He didn't know that Ye Xiu had managed to reach this stage with this skill. Using Vanishing Step continuously was also very tiring. If one was able to use it like this, then it would reduce a lot of unneeded mechanics and effort, but at the same time, there was a lot more precision and accuracy needed in terms of judgement and awareness.

Li Yibo was certain that no player in the current Alliance was able to use Vanishing Step so masterfully. Li Yibo felt that what he had just seen was a coincidence with Ye Xiu's actions. If it really had been used purposeful, then that was terrifying. At the age Ye Xiu was at, he was already approaching the end of his pro career, yet his technical ability was still at such heights. It was terrifying even to think about it.

Suddenly, Li Yibo felt that the broadcasting room was rather cold.

"Chance!" It was then that Li Yibo heard Pan Lin yell out in disappointment again. He, on the other hand, had gotten completely distracted and had no idea what had just happened. He couldn't really go and ask, so he could only say, "Such a shame. He really shouldn't have missed that opportunity either."

　

"Yeah, Qiu Fei has already wasted two good chances," Pan Lin said.

Two?

Li Yibo was stunned, but quickly recovered. Pan Lin was still making Lord Grim's appearance in Qiu Fei's vision during the Vanishing Step out to be an error on Ye Xiu's part, and a chance for Qiu Fei! It wasn't a good time for him to rain on that parade, but he didn't want the experienced people watching the tv broadcast thinking that he, Li Yibo, wasn't up to standard, unable to even notice something like this.

He felt conflicted, but what he heard was Pan Lin counting Lord Grim's combo. He couldn't keep up with the pace with the skill names, but he could easily count it. One, two, three, four, five...

Wait, one two three four five? Why was the count resetting?

Li Yibo had missed too much while he had been momentarily distracted, and hadn't even managed to catch up when Pan Lin yelled out again, "Ah! It broke, chance chance chance chance… Ay, what's wrong with you, Qiu Fei!"

Pan Lin's tone was extremely frustrated, and Li Yibo kept an eye on the match this time. Just now, Lord Grim's combo really did break and Qiu Fei didn't take the chance to counterattack either.

"This really shouldn't have happened," Li Yibo commented, "Although Qiu Fei is a player without much experience in official matches, he should still have the ability and awareness to try and grasp this chance. However, from Combat Form's movements, it doesn't seem if he even intended to even try."

　

"Yes, starting from Ye Xiu's counterattack until now, Qiu Fei has already missed three chances to turn the tables. Seems like this young player is a little too young. His rhythm has been messed up by Ye Xiu's single wave of counterattacks!"

"It won't be easy for him to get back into the right mindset in this sort of desperate situation."

"That's very true!"

In the audience, Liu Xiaobie was watching the projection while listening to what was coming from his earphones. However, at that moment, he pulled them down with an expression of disdain. "What bullshit."

　

"What's up?" Xu Bin turned his head around to ask. Liu Xiaobie had found the Excellent Era fans too noisy so he put his earphones in. He watched the match occuring in stadium, but he was listening to the commentary on his phone. Then he had heard the two analyzing the current situation and didn't know how to react to it.

"Those two guys! They said Qiu Fei missed three chances," Liu Xiaobie said.

　

"Three chances? Which three?" Xu Bin was puzzled.

　　

"The first time was when Lord Grim's figure appeared in the shot of Qiu Fei's view. They thought that this was an error in mechanics on Ye Xiu's part, that it was one of the chances," Liu Xiaobie said.

"That… wasn't that because there was no need to use Vanishing Steps to attack?"

　　

"Right? And the two false combos, they thought that the combo had been broken and it was a chance to counterattack," Liu Xiaobie continued.

Even Gao Yingjie stared wide eyed, obviously finding this unbelieveable.

Xu Bin, hearing this, just smiled. "It's natural that they can't tell with their lack of skill."

"But that's not what they think," Liu Xiaobie said.

　

"Yeah, so why are you listening to live commentary! Isn't it much clearer if you just look yourself?" Xu Bin said.

"These guys are too noisy, though," Liu Xiaobie said.

　

"Currently it isn't very noisy, right?" Xu Bin smiled.

It naturally wouldn't be very noisy right now. Ye Xiu had successfully counterattacked and his offense still hadn't stopped yet. Seeing Combat Form's life falling continuously, the Excellent Era fans were extremely anxious.

　

"I'm really not sure what they're expecting. Do they really think this rookie can wipe out Ye Qiu… er, Ye Xiu?" Liu Xiaobie said.

"So long as it's a match, nothing's impossible!" Xu Bin said.

"But at least don't hold such high hopes!" Liu Xiaobie said.

　

"I say, you seem to have high hopes for Happy defeating Excellent Era. According to your logic, you shouldn't hold such high hopes either!" Xu Bin said.

　

"No I don't…" Liu Xiaobie's retort was weak. "How about you, Little Gao."

"What are you trying to make him say?" Xu Bin didn't know if he should cry or laugh. This change of topic was a little too random, no?

"He really is strong." Gao Yingjie really did say something.

"Are you talking about that Qiu Fei?" Liu Xiaobie said.

"Do you think it's necessary to point out that God Ye Qiu is strong?" Xu Bin mocked.

"It's Ye Xiu," Liu Xiaobie nitpicked.

Xu Bin smiled. Ye Xiu or Ye Qiu, names were just a way to refer to people. They weren't important. He didn't care, so he still used Ye Qiu out of habit.

"As for this young man…" Liu Xiaobie began considering this seriously after hearing Gao Yingjie's comment. "He really is quite strong." He nodded, saying, "I think he'll be a strong rival for you in the future."

　

"He already is," Gao Yingjie said.

"Let's see how he deals with the current situation for now!" Liu Xiaobie said.

　

"If it was you, what would you do?" Xu Bin asked.

Liu Xiaobie didn't reply and Xu Bin didn't pry. In reality, all three of them were already thinking about what they would do in this situation if they were the ones on the field.

Chapter 1015: All Out

False combo.

This technique wasn't like Vanishing Step. Vanishing Step was a purely high-level technique. It was only possible to perform when the user's experience, awareness, and tech skill reached a certain level.

False combos were completely different. It wasn't just pro players that could do them. Even normal players often linked skills with false combos. This technique was similar to the previous Battle Mage combo executed by Qiu Fei. The skill floor was low. Anyone could follow that approach and do a short combo, but making a 20 hit true combo that was impossible to break, even by a God like Ye Xiu, wasn't so easy to perform. Even Qiu Fei himself probably wouldn't be able to replicate it if he tried again. Back in the old days, Ye Xiu's zero to death combo on his opponent had only been performed once.

It was because of the endless possibilities that made Glory so fun to watch.

False combos had its own unique characteristic. Everyone could use them, but when it was used, even the commentators and analysts might not be able to recognize it. Even the pro players fighting needed to ponder over it.

The three Team Tiny Herb players among the spectating crowd knew that these were false combos. Qiu Fei naturally knew it even better than them. False combos weren't counted by the system, but for a player, false combos were even more difficult to deal with because the theory behind false combos lay in the player being unable to make any sort of counterplay. Along with Vanishing Step, Qiu Fei was in extremely dire straits. The poor crowd was also unaware though. The commentators misled the viewers. They saw that the combo counter had clearly reset, but Qiu Fei failed to counterattack. Ye Xiu would then quickly start his combo count again. Everyone felt sorry for Qiu Fei.

How could they know? It was actually the hardest to deal with when the combo count reset.

As a result, when this scene happened for the third time, the crowd started letting out sounds of dissatisfaction. Li Yibo noticed that something wasn't right.

After retiring, Li Yibo didn't study Glory as devotedly as he had before. He was already having trouble keeping up with the times. When he commentated a match, there were often times when he felt like he was inadequate. However, at these times, this guy would reassure himself and activate the plausible-explanation high-level skill. When he saw the combo reset again and Qiu Fei still being helpless, Li Yibo's intuition told him: it's time to activate that skill.

He carefully studied this combo reset and the two previous ones. Li Yibo had once been a pro player and knew a lot about false combos. After analyzing it for a bit, he finally came to a realization.

F*ck. I really do need to activate that skill. Li Yibo felt somewhat annoyed.

Beside him, Pan Lin was still wondering if there was a problem with Qiu Fei. Li Yibo lightly coughed.

Pan Lin's heart suddenly became tense. Mother of god! Li Yibo is casting his high-level skill! If Li Yibo was preparing to use his skill, then it meant that they had previously said something wrong.

"This is... Qiu Fei seems to have been out of form for awhile now. Could something have happened to him? In order to be cautious, I think we should do a careful recap." Li Yibo said.

Pan Lin listened and knew that the high-level skill was imminent. As expected, Li Yibo carefully analyzed the previous sections and came to the conclusion: it was because of false combos.

"So it's like that….." Pan Lin could only go along with it. He felt somewhat ashamed for his previously misleading commentary. He didn't have Li Yibo's thick skin and couldn't calmly say that it was originally like this and that. It was as if their mistakes hadn't been committed by them.

"False combos aren't counted by the system, but practically speaking, they should also be considered combos. If we count those... then Combat Form has been struck by a 32 hit combo already. Of course, these 32 hits are just an informal calculation. It won't be listed as a statistic. I just wanted everyone to know about it." Li Yibo said.

"How is Qiu Fei going to break out of the 32 hit combo?" Pan Lin's focus returned to the match.

How is it going to be broken?　

As soon as these words were said, Lord Grim's combo count reset. Combat Form once again fell into a predicament. This was the fourth false combo.　　

It really is difficult…...

Qiu Fei wasn't like what the crowd thought. He wasn't doing nothing and standing there taking the beating. He had been trying his best the entire time, trying to think of a way to break free from his predicament. He just hadn't rashly used any skills yet. Mashing random keys when the situation wasn't right was a noob's method. Pro players would never do that because... skills were most threatening when not used.

Qiu Fei remembered these words. These words had been said by the opponent in front of him and had helped him eliminate many of his bad habits in the beginning.

He was unable to return the favor to his coach. He could only prove himself through victory.

These were Qiu Fei's thoughts. He didn't say them out loud because he knew that the other side knew. Both sides were going all out in this match. This was the best proof.

What were his old coach's efforts for? Wasn't it for all of this moment on the stage?

After Combat Form was dealt two devastating combos by his opponent, he didn't have much health left. At this moment, other players might have given up already. They probably wouldn't go so far as to randomly start mashing their keyboard, but they would almost be at that point. However, Qiu Fei didn't think about it. He hoped to see this match through with a professional attitude. He would clearly be aware of what he was doing at all times. These words... were probably also said by Ye Xiu.

It just that now, everything he could do had already been completely sealed.

This was a true match. It was no longer a coaching one inside the team. The other side wouldn't hold back and give him room to guide him. The other side would do his best not to give him any opportunities.

Opportunities were somtimes seized, but opportunities sometimes needed to be created!　　

Dragon Rises from the Sea!

Combat Form, who had been taking a beating the entire time, suddenly moved. A spear came downwind and magic undulations spread like waves as the spear stabbed forward.

It was just that... the direction of this attack was slightly off. Ye Xiu was using Vanishing Step, so Qiu Fei couldn't see him. This attack had been purely a guess. Unfortunately, he guessed incorrectly.

Another attack from Lord Grim fell onto Combat Form, but at this moment, Combat Form boldly used Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

A high-level skill was released, but the aim was still off. Quite a few people shook their heads. They felt like Qiu Fei had given up and started testing his luck.

To their surprise, Cloud Whirling Windstorm's magic undulations, along with the waves from Dragon Rises from the Sea, collided. Clouds and mist seemed to form at their intersection. Combat Form's figure suddenly became hazy.

"This is?" Everyone was stunned. They had never seen this scene before.

New technique?

These two words popped up in everyone's eyes. Pan Lin had already started yelling.　

"Dragon Rises from the Sea and Cloud Whirlwind Windstorm can produce such an effect! I've never seen this combo before. It's a combination created by Qiu Fei while facing a predicament. The collision between these two skills produce an effect that hides the character. This is an opportunity to turn his situation around. Wow….." Pan Lin paused halfway through. On stage, Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella moved and tore through the mist, throwing Combat Form down from the air with a Circle Swing. After Combat Form smashed into the ground, two sweeping attacks followed. Combat Form was still unable to break out of the combo. His created technique didn't seem to be that worthy of praise.

For a moment, Pan Lin was at a loss. Who would have thought that Li Yibo would pick it up: "What a pity. Ye Xiu was still able to catch him. Qiu Fei's usage of these two skills was very successful. Against another opponent, he might have been able to turn the situation around. Unfortunately, his opponent is Ye Xiu. Experience helped Ye Xiu accurately catch his opponent in this situation, but we can see that the situation has at least changed. Ye Xiu was forced to stop using Vanishing Step and false combos. After Qiu Fei created this effect, Ye Xiu couldn't continue his previous combo, which was why he used Circle Swing to pull Combat Form back.

"This young Qiu Fei has shown us his creative talent." Pan Lin immediately followed.　

"Yes, he has a boundless future ahead of him. Unfortunately, he'll most likely lose this match. However, he fought well against Ye Xiu, even executing a beautiful 20 hit combo and producing an unknown effect with new skills. Many things can be learned from this match." Li Yibo said.

"Yes, Qiu Fei is making his final effort. He hasn't given up yet."　

"But it looks like there isn't much of a chance….."

"Yeah….."

"Okay, Combat Form has fallen. This match has ended with Team Happy's victory. However, besides the deep impression Qiu Fei has given with his performance, he was able to take away about half of Lord Grim's health." Li Yibo said.

"A part of that was from the back and forths in the beginning. In the middle, there was that incredible 20 hit combo and that final struggle at the end.

"Yes, being able to win an opportunity to attack in the final moment is due to his beautiful combination of the two new skills."

"In comparison, Coach Li, what do you think of the winner Ye Xiu's performance?" Pan Lin asked.　　

"An abundance of experience and correct decision-making." Li Yibo gave seven words as a comment. This was a comment that applied to any player that wasn't a rookie, but what else could Li Yibo say? He didn't understand unspecialized characters at all. If he wanted to give a more detailed analysis, he didn't know where to start. He was depressed that Ye Xiu would still be playing in the next round and show off his unspecialized combos. He could only brace himself and continue commentating. This time, he needed to be more careful. He couldn't make a mistake like not seeing a false combo.

The commentators treated Ye Xiu's matches as a formidable enemy. As for Team Excellent Era, after Qiu Fei came down, the player who stood up was their ace player and team captain of the new generation: Sun Xiang.

Chapter 1016: You’re Too Hard to Predict

"You played well." Sun Xiang actually acted like a captain for once and comforted Qiu Fei, who was returning to the bench. Qiu Fei smiled, but didn't say anything before returning to his seat, but his gaze was aimed at Excellent Era's competition booth. On the field, they didn't have any way to communicate with words. Everything was based on their mechanics, attacks, defense, movement, and dodges. In this match, Qiu Fei had given it his all, but still lost. However, there would always be defeat in competition. He might've lost this time, but next time he'd win for certain, no matter who he was up against.

After giving his encouragement to one of their players, he casually glanced towards Happy and suddenly raised his voice. "It's just a shame that you left a Ye Qiu with only half his health for me. Even if I win, there will be no honor in it! Well, there's no helping it, seems like all I can do is clear him off quickly!"

Chen Guo's temper flared. If she had something in her hand, she'd have thrown it at him by now. After calling out arrogantly, Sun Xiang walked towards the competition booth with his head held high. Pan Lin and Li Yibo had also begun commentating on the line ups of each team in the television broadcast.

　　

"Sun Xiang is the third to go up. If we consider this, then Excellent Era's plans for the group arena is clear. They want to finish the group arena up in three rounds, hoping to earn at least three points," Pan Lin said.

"Yes, considering the new rules, three points is an absolute advantage in the group arena. Two points can be considered being one step ahead and one point doesn't have much impact. You have to fight with your all in the team competition. If you lose, then the opponent has at least one point and the two sides will have to play a matchbreaker," Li Yibo said.

"If you can have the security that you at least won't lose, that counts as a psychological advantage, doesn't it?" Pan Lin said.

"This sort of psychological advantage will only matter towards the very end," Li Yibo said.

"Under the current rules, the team ace should appear fourth or third. Excellent Era has placed Sun Xiang as their third player, a very standard offensive arrangement. However, from the current situation, I feel like they could have been a little more daring and placed him second," Pan Lin said.

"I think Excellent Era is still wary about Ye Xiu's strength. If it were any other God, they could be a bit more offensive, but Ye Xiu knows them all too well," Li Yibo said.

"But they also know Ye Xiu very well!" Pan Lin said.

"Unfortunately, Ye Xiu has changed classes since then," Li Yibo said with a smile.

"Ok, now Sun Xiang has entered the competition booth and the two characters are being loaded into the game. On Excellent Era's side, we have Excellent Era's current captain, Sun Xiang with his account, One Autumn Leaf! And on Happy's side, his opponent is the ex-captain of Excellent Era, Ye Qiu, now called Ye Xiu, and One Autumn Leaf's previous owner." As Sun Xiang entered the stage, the match entered the preparation stage and Pan Lin excitedly began to introduce them. His words reflected what angle the audience's anticipation came from. Sun Xiang's identity and account were clearly emphasized. As for Ye Xiu? His old identity and old account were emphasized. Lord Grim, Happy, these crucial words that should've appeared in the introduction hadn't been mentioned once.

"Now for the countdown; the match is about to begin," Pan Lin said.

"This is a battle between the current and ex captain of Excellent Era! The account, One Autumn Leaf, that was once Ye Xiu's companion for so long is now in Sun Xiang's hands and has become the opponent Ye Xiu has to defeat. I wonder how he feels, facing this familiar and, you could say, closest ally. How will he perform?" As if afraid that someone wouldn't be able to catch the drama behind this match, Pan Lin went over the highlights again as the match officially started.

The two characters appeared on the map simultaneously. Without hesitation, Sun Xiang immediately pushed One Autumn Leaf into a sprint, foregoing strategic positioning entirely. Sun Xiang had thought and felt that it would be a shame that he would probably not have a chance to face Ye Xiu in an official match using One Autumn Leaf. He really wanted to use a spectacular victory to establish his ownership over One Autumn Leaf, and the previous user Ye Xiu was the best stepping stone in his eyes.

He hadn't thought that, after a year and a half, he really did get the chance to meet Ye Xiu in an official match. Though this stage wasn't as impressive as he had hoped for, the amount of attention this match had gained was satisfactory. Especially all the publicity done by the media, it made this all the more appropriate opportunity to perform his sacrifice.

However, due to the new rules, he couldn't have Ye Xiu duel him one on one. He could only act in accordance with the rules. Now, he had finally got the chance to face off against Ye Xiu. It was a shame that Ye Xiu was already at half health from his fight with Qiu Fei. This was frustrating to Sun Xiang. If he could be second in line, that would have been perfect. However, the team wanted to emphasize security, so he had to be third. This was agreed on by their boss, Tao Xun, making it so that Sun Xiang couldn't object.

Now look. Their victory was secured, but his perfect plan to crush Ye Xiu was completely ruined. There was no honor in winning against a Ye Xiu with only half his health!

　

"Where are you, Ye Xiu? Stop hiding, come out and fight me." Sun Xiang pressed forward with One Autumn Leaf towards the center of the map. Not seeing Lord Grim, he immediately went to yell at Ye Xiu in the public chat.

"Don't rush me, I'm recovering my health," Ye Xiu replied.

Recovering health? Sun Xiang was stunned for a moment. He had no idea that the stadium was filled with booing now. From the very beginning of the match, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim never advanced. With a shamelessness that rivaled his teammate, Wei Chen, he had hid in a corner and began to heal himself.

That's right, heal himself. Though Unspecialized could only use level 20 and under skills, but, for the players to fully experience the differences between classes, these low leveled skills displayed their class' distinctiveness. Clerics had two level 20 and under healing skills. Small Heal and Small Cure. One was a chant to recover health and the other was an instant cast. Though the effects weren't as good as high level healing spells, even level 75 Clerics still needed to utilize these two skills. Low level skills had advantages that high level skills didn't. Small Heals had a shorter chant, and Small Cure had a shorter cooldown.

In the pro scene, these advantages were very crucial. They often needed to be able to quickly use skills. By the time the slow chant of a Holy Heal was complete, the one who needed the heal might've died already.

The current Ye Xiu didn't use any Small Cures. Instant casts like this had cooldowns, and they usually weren't very short, so they were usually saved for dire situations, but chants were alright. They didn't have cooldowns so Lord Grim was chanting continuously, the white flash of a Small Heal hadn't dimmed since the round began.

Apart from that, Lord Grim had a Recover on him, too! He could use skills from all 24 classes. Amongst the 24 classes, Paladins could also heal! Recover was a low level Paladin skill, and was a healing buff, a legendary ability that even Clerics were jealous of. While on a character, that character would be healed every three seconds for a total of 18 seconds. Currently, Lord Grim's health stayed at a rhythm of jumping up once every three seconds. This made it hard to tell what rank his Recover was. This guy wasn't stopping with the heals at all.

Apart from the boos of the Excellent Era fans, this scene elicited a heartfelt speechlessness from everyone present.

Bringing healing to a one on one? It wasn't unheard of. While Clerics and Paladins couldn't really fight one on one, but there were still two other classes in the Priest class category, Knights and Exorcists. Level 20 and under skills were usable throughout the same class type, that meant Knights and Exorcists could also learn and use these healing skills.

.

Did that mean you were invincible if you brought healing to a one on one? Those who had some experience knew it wasn't so simple. Knights and Exorcists could learn a few low leveled heals, but their effects were incomparable with Cleric and Paladin healing. First of all, the two had bonuses from class specialization, and then healers also had special equipment to boost their healing. Healing was something unrelated to physical and magic attacks. If Knights and Exorcists wanted to boost their own healing abilities, they'd have to sacrifice other stats. After this sacrifice, no one would feel like it was unfair that they had healing abilities.

So healing in a one on one wasn't very rare, but people like Ye Xiu, who hid their character in a corner to continuously healed themselves without restraint was unheard of. The entire audience was struck dumb.

Even Pan Lin and Li Yibo were speechless for a long time upon seeing Ye Xiu's actions.

This should've been a drama filled match! Look at how pumped Sun Xiang was! Yet Ye Xiu had immediately turned this match down a shameless path.

"Ye Xiu's Lord Grim… is currently healing himself, er…" Pan Lin commentated. His passion from before had been completely extinguished. It wasn't like you could expect him to yell out in excitement "wow, so awesome, this God immediately hid himself away at the beginning of the match and started chanting heals continuously! The healing isn't stopping!" That wasn't something Pan Lin could do.

"Yeah, he's healing…" Li Yibo's comment was also very weak.

"The effects aren't as great as that of a Cleric or Paladin," Pan Lin said.

"Of course, he has no specialization bonus," Li Yibo said.

　

"He doesn't have any healing equipment either," Pan Lin said.

"He's relying entirely on his stats to heal."

"A shame we don't know if his weapon has any healing bonuses or not."

The two chatted had a discussion without any substance.

"But if he keeps healing, won't that put a huge strain on his mana usage? How is he going to battle after that?" Pan Lin finally found a problem to discuss.

Just as he said this, a blue light descended on Lord Grim.

"This is?" Li Yibo was stunned, and saw Lord Grim's mana suddenly shoot up.

"Wish… Prayer?" Pan Lin stared in shock.

"It's Wish Prayer…" Li Yibo wanted to cry. It was way too hard to commentate for this God's matches. You're too hard to predict!

Chapter 1017: Not That Careless

Wish Prayer - Cleric skill. It recovered 30% of the target's mana over 10 seconds. As the skill level increased, the maximum mana recovery could reach up to 60%. It had a 10 minute cooldown.

Lord Grim was currently casting Wish Prayer. His character's mana was rapidly increasing. Everyone stared with their eyes and jaws wide open.

Let alone in the individual competition, Wish Prayer was rarely used, even in team competitions. Even though it had astonishing effects, a 10 second cast time was way too easy to interrupt. As a result, even if it was used in a team competition, it could only be done when an opportunity arrived, allowing for two or three seconds of recovery at best. But in reality, it was very rare for a team competition to last so long that either side ran out of mana. It was even more rare in the individual competition. Running out of mana was usually only seen in the group arena.

However, Clerics and Paladins didn't play in the group arena. As for Knights and Exorcists, who would add this skill to their weapons as a skill bonus, no one had ever made such an absurd choice.

　

You're out of mana mid-battle, but you can recover it? And such a substantial one too? It sounded amazing, but in practice, its usage was extremely limited. Setting aside the fact that it was already rare for one to run out of mana, even if it happened, in a 1v1 in the group arena, 10 seconds of standing still would be like treating the opponent like air. If the opponent knew you could do this, it's not like they would just wait for you to recover your mana.

Then what about recovering during the start of the match like what Ye Xiu was doing? In that case, there was enough time. However, this scenario required so many prerequisites that the chances of it happening were next to nothing, so the value of this skill was too miniscule. For a pro player, this type of extravagance could be considered a crime.

As a result, everyone was staring at Lord Grim like they had just witnessed a crime. It was like they were at a crime scene.

The commentator Pan Lin and honored guest Li Yibo were also speechless. As for Sun Xiang? He had no idea that Ye Xiu had used Wish Prayer. Ye Xiu had been talking about healing just before. He had been surprised at first and realized that unspecialized characters had the ability to heal themselves, but he wasn't worried. He felt like beating Ye Xiu, who was only at half health, would be winning with an unfair advantage! It's all good now though. He's giving Ye Xiu some time to breath. Wouldn't that make his victory all the more worthwhile?

Thus, despite knowing that his opponent was recovering, Sun Xiang had One Autumn Leaf stroll over, letting others know that he wasn't worried one bit.

"Haha... Sun Xiang doesn't seem to care about what Ye Xiu is doing..." Pan Lin immediately said after seeing it.

"Yes, he's quite confident." Li Yibo said.

"But might he be a bit overconfident?" Pan Lin wondered.

"Mm, are you talking about Ye Xiu or Sun Xiang?" Li Yibo asked.

Pan Lin looked at Lord Grim recovering his mana and then at One Autumn Leaf strolling over: "Hm, both...."

They couldn't keep going on like this. Was this really a life and death match between two teams? These two guys weren't being serious at all. This was the Challenger League Finals, not two players sparring in-game!　　

"Wait a second. Let me recover my health and mana."

"Sure, take your time."

These were words that players would often say to each other when sparring, but the same thing was happening in a serious tournament. How weird. How weird.

"Hahahaha..." Pan Lin could only laugh. He didn't know what to say.　　

At Excellent Era's bench, boss Tao Xuan was personally presiding over the match. His two arms were folded across his chest and his expression was calm. However, if you looked at him closely, you would notice that Tao Xuan's two hands were tightly clutching his own arms.

If he didn't vent his emotions that way, Tao Xuan was truly afraid that he would stomp over in anger. Sun Xiang was a player who he generally liked, but his arrogance truly made his head hurt sometimes.

It's fine….. When Sun Xiang faced other opponents with arrogance and stomped on them, Tao Xuan felt quite good. During those moments, he was fine with Sun Xiang's confidence, even if he did what he was doing now. Tao Xuan might even laugh, feeling like his team was brave and mighty.

But Tao Xuan's attitude was completely different with Ye Xiu being the opponent.

It was a sort of contradictory feeling.

For example, when Xiao Shiqin left the stage with a GG, although Tao Xuan had truly felt pleased with this conduct, he also felt a bit of regret. If Xiao Shiqin had worn Ye Xiu down a bit more, that would have been great too. Xiao Shiqin's behavior made Excellent Era look weak and not like a powerhouse at all!

You can't have it both ways*. This was the contradiction that Tao Xuan felt.

At this moment, Sun Xiang behavior could be regarded as the air of a powerhouse, but seeing Ye Xiu's Lord Grim healing his health and even finishing with a 10 second Wish Prayer without being interrupted, Tao Xuan couldn't stay calm.

Unfortunately, Sun Xiang remained calm. The difference in thinking made him somewhat annoyed.

Fortunately, Ye Xiu didn't continue challenging his heart's limits. After the ten second Wish Prayer, Lord Grim finally came out from the corner.

"Are you here?" Ye Xiu asked in the chat.

"What? You're done recovering?" Sun Xiang replied.

"Pretty much." Ye Xiu said.

"Pretty much? I advise you to recover a bit longer. I'm not in a hurry." Sun Xiang said.

"Huh? What's that sound?" On Excellent Era's bench, one of the players heard a strange noise.

The teammates next to him immediately kicked his foot and gave him a sharp glance. That player looked over and saw the boss grinding his teeth…...　　

"If I don't remember incorrectly, this is the first time today that the players have chatted with each other." Pan Lin said.

"Yeah, it seems like it." Li Yibo said.

"Hahahaha" Pan Lin chuckled again. The two sides had finally talked to each other, but couldn't the content be a bit more professional? The conversation between Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang was too much like what Pan Lin had imagined normal players to be like.

"It's good enough. I don't want you to lose in such an unsightly manner." Ye Xiu continued to type in the chat.

"Those should be my words to you." Sun Xiang fired back.

"You can keep them!"

"To you!"

"Keep them!"

"To you."

"Keep them."

The crowd was in an uproar. It wasn't because the two were just talking nonsense, but rather during this time, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim quietly circled around to flank One Autumn Leaf.

"With just that weird mix and matched gear, you think you can beat me? You've already forgotten One Autumn Leaf's stats? Do you need me to remind you?" Sun Xiang seemed to be completely engrossed in the chat. His character wasn't moving at all.

"While Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang were talking, Lord Grim circled around to behind One Autumn Leaf. Sun Xiang doesn't seem to be aware of this either. He's just typing in chat. Could it be that Sun Xiang can't touch-type and needs to look at his keyboard to type?" Pan Lin yelled.

"Hahaha..." Li Yibo laughed while glancing at Pan Lin. However, he noticed that Pan Lin was completely serious. That wasn't a joke? You're being serious? A pro player not being able to touch type? Do you think a pro player looks down at his keyboard when playing?

"Close, close. Lord Grim is nearby." Pan Lin shouted. The crowd roared even louder as if to warn Sun XIang. At Excellent Era's bench, Tao Xuan couldn't bear it anymore. This Sun Xiang was too much of a child!

"Ye Xiu's pathing was successful, but the key point is chatting to divert the enemy's attention. Sun Xiang is in range to be attacked. Is he going to choose to attack? Sun Xiang doesn't seem to know!" Pan Lin shouted.

At this moment, Sun Xiang typed out a new message in the chat.

"We've already chatted for so long. What's going on? Could you be behind me?"

"Woah!" Pan Lin cried out in surprise. Then, he saw One Autumn Leaf turn around directly towards Lord Grim. His spear, Annihilating Evil, pointed forward.

"So it turns out Sun Xiang wasn't as we had imagined... to be so... careless." Pan Lin hesitated. He almost said "stupid".

"Haha, I don't think such a low-level mistake would happen to such a skilled player." Li Yibo acted as if he knew it all along.

Sun Xiang turned around and began his offense.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

One Autumn Leaf initiated with the move that Tang Rou liked to use the most, but just from the visual effects, the difference between One Autumn Leaf and Soft Mist could be seen.

Were there any changes to One Autumn Leaf's equipment?

Ye Xiu could see this instantly. One Autumn Leaf had changed a lot of his equipment. Some parts had been completely swapped out. Some had slight changes in appearance. The club's R&D team wasn't going to waste materials solely to change the appearance of equipment. A change in appearance meant a change in stats. In the eyes of the viewers, One Autumn Leaf was still One Autumn Leaf, but for Ye Xiu, who was incomparably familiar with this character, One Autumn Leaf had been changed beyond recognition.

After dodging the Dragon Breaks the Ranks, Lord Grim Aerial Rifled backwards to pull away from One Autumn Leaf.　

"Haha, this is you after recovering? It might be too little." Sun Xiang looked at Lord Grim's condition and typed a string of words.

Lord Grim hadn't advanced classes, nor did he wear any healing equipment, so his healing was rather weak. During this time, he had only recovered to 70% health. Because his heals were weak, his mana consumption was high. Ye Xiu couldn't heal to full health. If he did, a Wish Prayer might not be enough to recover his mana.

For a Level 75 character, low-leveled healing skills without a class advancement and without specific healing equipment were very weak.

Chapter 1018: At a Standstill

As Sun Xiang typed this out, his character never paused. One Autumn Leaf did a horizontal sweep with his spear after his Dragon Breaks the Ranks, using Tyrant's Destruction. Lord Grim had already been pulling away when he dodged the Dragon Breaks the Ranks, seeming to already be out Tyrant's Destruction's range and in a good position to counterattack. However, Lord Grim didn't stop backing away there. Just as he stepped back, the mud and stone on the ground were swept across. A place where Tyrant's Destruction shouldn't have reached had been affected by the sweeping effect through the force of this attack.

"Oh oh, this is Evil Annihilation's bonus effect, Landslide, which increases the range of attacks. However, the opponent is Ye Xiu, who obviously knows this better than anyone. You can see that he even considered the effect of Landslide in his dodge."

"The chances of these bonus effects on weapons activating isn't actually very high, but in an actual match it's better to prepare for the worst possibility," Li Yibo sighed.

Boom!

The two were still talking about Tyrant's Destruction when an explosion occurred on the field.

As he backed away, avoiding the attack, Lord Grim had discretely thrown out a grenade. Pan Lin and Li Yibo hadn't noticed at all. It was only until it exploded that everyone gasped in surprise.

The inconspicuous movement had fooled everyone, all except his current opponent, Sun Xiang. One Autumn Leaf's immediate pursuit made a sudden halt in the middle, obviously waiting for the grenade to go off. The timing was just right, so it looked like he had somehow ran right through the explosion, but avoided taking any damage whatsoever, Evil Annihilation still closing in on Lord Grim.

"Sun Xiang is eagerly going on the offensive, but it seems like Ye Xiu doesn't intend to face him head on," Pan Lin cried out.

"That's for certain. Veterans have an advantage in experience. Against young opponents, especially ace players like Sun Xiang, they have to fully utilize this advantage. Facing their opponent head on would be… would be…" Li Yibo was unable to continue, because Pan Lin had only said 'seems like'. This was a guess he had made in accordance with Lord Grim's act of retreat. Yet now, Lord Grim opened up his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and parried One Autumn Leaf's attack, a true act of facing someone head on.

　

"Not bad!" In this direct face off, Sun Xiang actually found the time to type a message. One Autumn Leaf stepped diagonally, sending out a Sky Strike from a side angle.

　

Lord Grim didn't even turn his view, whipping out a sword from the handle of the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella as he jumped diagonally backwards and using a Collapsing Mountain as he avoided Sky Strike.

"Ah, a Collapsing Mountain in place. This is a type of technique that uses a backwards jump to cancel out Collapsing Mountain's forward jump. Ye Xiu is able to perform it with such ease. It's clear to see how familiar he is with the foundations of Glory. He truly deserves his title of Glory's Textbook," Pan Lin called out.

One Autumn Leaf turned, continuing his half-finished Sky Strike and using it to blockLord Grim's Collapsing Mountain. However, Collapsing Mountain had far greater priority than Sky Strike, so it was impossible to complete this block with just Sky Strike alone. Yet, by then, One Autumn Leaf had already jumped back, avoiding the Collapsing Mountain entirely.

"One Autumn Leaf dodged it… But why did he use this Sky Strike to block, adviser Li?" Pan Lin asked.

"Heh, there's no particular reason. It's just a habit of pro players to help them get into the rhythm of battle quicker," Li Yibo explained.

"I can't stand it anymore!" In the audience, Tiny Herb player Liu Xiaobie had been listening to the commentary on his phone as he watched the match again, but then yanked out his earphones once more.

"What is it this time?" Xu Bin asked.

"They said that there was no reason to One Autumn Leaf's Sky Strike just now," Liu Xiaobie said.

"Oh? That's not right. If it weren't for the block done with that Sky Strike, there would be no avoiding that Collapsing Mountain," Xu Bin said.

"The block done with Sky Strike slowed down the speed at which Collapsing Mountain descended and, at the same time, used the force to speed up his backwards jump," Gao Yingjie said.

"Commentators nowadays are getting more and more unprofessional." Liu Xiaobie put the earphones back in even as he said this and shook his head, making Xu Bin and Gao Yingjie rather speechless.

The battle raged on.

Neither of them managed to gain the advantage. Though both were continuously losing health, this exchange of health was carefully controlled and neither of them managed to land any critical hits. Fine techniques such as the Sky Strike block and Collapsing Mountain in place were endless in this battle. Audience members like the three Tiny Herb pros found it spectacular, but it was a shame for those who were watching the stream. Pan Lin and Li Yibo would probably only see 70 percent of finesse in this and in that 70 percent, they would misexplain 20 percent of it. This was probably one of the problems caused by the late start and rapid progress of the Pro Alliance of Glory.

Though they might have missed many amazing details of this match, that didn't affect the enjoyment for normal spectators. This fast and chaotic rain of attacks from both sides was exactly what the audience loved the most.

However, Tao Xuan, sitting on Excellent Era's bench, was anxious. To be honest, he liked this sort of spectacular match as well. This beautiful scene was exactly what Tao Xuan hoped for for Excellent Era. But… not at a time like this. Who was Sun Xiang's opponent? Ye Xiu! The person, whose ability had deteriorated, whose performance had slipped, who had been replaced by Sun Xiang. To make sure this went smoothly, Tao Xuan had put in a lot of effort. Yet now, Ye Xiu was fighting Sun Xiang to a standstill. This was already slapping Excellent Era's face harshly. Like this, it was hard to say who would win and who would lose. Though Lord Grim had started the match with 70 percent of his health and was at a disadvantage from the beginning, this standstill wouldn't last until the end of the match. There would definitely be fluctuations and peaks in performance in the match, especially from Ye Xiu, who was behind. How could he possibly let himself die slowly in this exchange of damage?

Tao Xuan couldn't stay calm. Even after telling himself that One Autumn Leaf was the stronger character and Sun Xiang was younger and had more energy, he just couldn't build up any confidence when it came to facing Ye Xiu.

"The match is at a standstill right now,"

"Er, I feel, that Lord Grim actually has the slight advantage right now," Li Yibo said.

"How come?" Pan Lin was confused.

"Because the characters have a difference in power. Although the level 75 Orange equipment has helped Happy greatly reduce the gap between them and Excellent Era, this reduction is only in basic stats. However, if you take a detailed look, Orange equipment can't be as perfect as Silver equipment," Li Yibo said.

"But we can also see that Team Happy does have some Silver equipment. Wei Chen's Warlock, Windward Formation, is even at pro level with 8 pieces," Pan Lin argued.

"Heh, but you can't judge Silver equipment just by the number of pieces of Silver equipment you have. What's the biggest advantage of Silver equipment? They're specially tailored to suit the player. Only if it suits the user's playstyle and needs can it be utilized to its fullest.In contrast, if a piece of Silver equipment isn't tailored to their needs and only made to maximize stats, it would still be stronger than Orange equipment of the same level, but it will lose its greatest advantage. Some players like faster attack speed, some players want each strike to do more damage. If you give attack power equipment to a player that prefers speed, the equipment is good, but it doesn't suit their style, so how well can its stats truly be utilized?" Li Yibo smoothly explained.

"I understand now. You mean to say that Team Happy's Silver equipment might not necessarily have reached that level of specialization," Pan Lin said.

"Heh, first of all, Team Happy doesn't have that much Silver Equipment. In addition, we don't know how Happy obtained their Silver equipment, but I doubt that they have a development team working on it like Excellent Era does. So they don't really have much flexibility with their Silver equipment. If they have Silver equipment then they will use it. They don't have much choice. It'll be very hard for them to reach perfection!" Li Yibo exclaimed.

"You're very right, Adviser Li. If we look at it from this perspective, it'd actually be very hard on Ye Xiu to have Lord Grim fight Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf to a standstill. It's hard to believe that he still has this ability at this age," Pan Lin said.

"In the end, all matches depend on performance. When we say a player's ability is deteriorating, we don't get that conclusion from just one or two matches, but from a long period of observation. In this period, he might perform spectacularly sometimes. This sort of fluctuation is common for everyone. The performance in single match can't really tell us anything. Zhou Zekai might lose in a one on one battle, but can we say that the player that beat him is now the new best player in the Alliance?" Li Yibo said with a smile.

"I understand what you mean now." Pan Lin nodded.

"Okay, let's continue watching the match. The two are still at a standstill and both characters have lost around 20 percent of their health. However, since Lord Grim only had 70 percent in the beginning, he's currently falling behind. Hey, Adviser Li, do you think Ye Xiu will suddenly escape halfway through the battle to replenish his health and mana again?" Pan Lin suddenly asked.

"I doubt Sun Xiang will give him the opportunity to do that. If he's going to let his opponent run away to heal so easily, then I'll probably even be able to beat him."

"Hahahaha." The two began to laugh in the live broadcast.

That was when Sun Xiang typed out a another sentence in the channel. "I say, isn't it time to speed up now?"

"Speed up?" Pan Lin yelled out in shock. "Does this mean Sun Xiang hasn't been going all out before now?"

"This… is probably a purposeful suppression of the rhythm so he can suddenly speed up and throw his opponent into chaos!" Li Yibo said.

"Speaking of, the two sides seem to be doing a lot of communicating in this match!" Pan Lin said.

"Yeah, Sun Xiang usually doesn't say much in matches! This is surprising. Seems like Ye Xiu is a very different kind of opponent for Excellent Era. From the conversation between the captains of new and old, Sun Xiang probably hopes to prove he can do better than Ye Xiu with a victory here!" Li Yibo guessed.

"So, is he going to speed up?" Pan Lin asked in excited hope.

Chapter 1019: Wound

Shattering the Land!

The Level 75 Battle Mage skill was heroically used by One Autumn Leaf, clashing against Lord Grim's attack. One Autumn Leaf's powerful equipment was displayed. Lord Grim's attack should have possessed a short hitstun effect, but the hitstun couldn't even be seen. Even though it hurt One Autumn Leaf, it didn't stop the skill from coming out.

He already has a clear grasp of my character's stats!

Ye Xiu thought to himself. Due to Lord Grim's full set of Orange equipment, Lord Grim's stats weren't a secret. The only variable was the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. If this were a normal weapon, Sun Xiang would have most likely grasped the weapon's stats much faster, but because the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella had many forms each with different stats, more effort was needed. However, daring to take the attack while using Shattering the Land meant that Sun Xiang had a solid understanding of Lord Grim's stats. Sun Xiang knew that his attack would be unable to interrupt One Autumn Leaf's skill.

Sure enough, despite Lord Grim's attack dealing damage, One Autumn Leaf remained unmoved. Shattering the Lands came out. One Autumn Leaf thrust his spear into the ground and then pulled it back. A wave spread out in a circle around One Autumn Leaf. Compared to Qiu Fei's Combat Form, the power was one step higher. The Battle God One Autumn Leaf's might truly began to show.

Sun Xiang's timing was on point. His luck burst forth too. His spear, Evil Annihilation, triggered Landslide, increasing Shattering the Land's attack range. For a high-level skill that already possessed high killing power, the addition the Landslide effect only made it more obvious.

Lord Grim was unable to escape from the skill's wide range and was sent flying into the air along with dirt and stone. This was just Sun Xiang's opening move too. One Autumn Leaf ran behind Lord Grim and stabbed towards Lord Grim's heart from the back with a Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.

Getting behind the opponent was a move that pro players always did when comboing. First, it increased the damage due to it being a back attack. Second, it was harder to defend strikes from behind. These types of movements could be considered as a beginner-level Vanishing Step. The difference was that the goal of Vanishing Step was to combo the opponent without the opponent knowing the user's location, so it wasn't as simple as a back attack.

This Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart was extremely sharp. A sneak attack from the back might have been impossible for anyone else to defend against, but Ye Xiu was too familiar with Battle Mages. He didn't even need to look. He could just listen to know that it was a Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart coming from behind him. He had distinguished it even amidst the quaking noise caused by Shattering the Lands.

Without turning around, Lord Grim put his umbrella on his shoulder. With a whoosh, the umbrella canopy opened up into its shield form to block the attack. Ye Xiu didn't have any other options available. Sun Xiang was too fast, and One Autumn Leaf's attack was also ferocious. Ye Xiu didn't have time to do any complicated motions.

The shield form was the lightest of the shields. Even though its ability to reduce damage wasn't bad, its priority was simply too low. After taking this Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, Lord Grim was launched even higher into the air.

Sun Xiang targeted where Lord Grim would fall and had One Autumn Leaf wait over there, but then he saw Lord Grim retract the canopy of the umbrella on his shoulder and saw the umbrella ribs start to spin into a Rotor Wing.

Sun Xiang wasn't going to let him go. Even though One Autumn Leaf couldn't fly, Lord Grim couldn't fly forever. Rotor Wings had a limited skill duration. The flight speed wasn't fast either. One Autumn Leaf firmly chased after Lord Grim.

Who would have imagined that Lord Grim was only faking it. After tricking Sun Xiang to take a few steps forward, he quietly dropped a grenade without warning.

"Haha." Sun Xiang even type a sneering emoji. One Autumn Leaf turned around. Evil Annihilation swung up and moved along a beautiful arc, directly striking the grenade mid-air.

Amidst the cover of the explosion, Lord Grim disappeared without a trace.　　

Not good!

Sun Xiang's heart tensed. He didn't dare be negligent and hastily moved to pull away. Three Anti-Tank Missiles fell from the sky. Using the cover of the explosion, Lord Grim shot them in a triangle, trapping One Autumn Leaf in the middle.　　

Sun Xiang's frightening mechanics were displayed at this moment. The three Anti-Tank Missiles were shot in a tight formation, yet this guy was actually able to get One Autumn Leaf to slip through the tiniest gap between two of them to dodge the missiles.

Beautiful! However, no applause came. With their omniscient view, they could already see it clearly. Lord Grim had used Shadow Clone Technique to return to the ground. As for One Autumn Leaf? He was looking up in the air, attacking the clone.

Blood splattered.

When an Assassin or a Ninja approached an unsuspecting target, even a God couldn't escape from the sneak attack because the attack came without any warning.

Only then did Sun Xiang realize he had fallen for it. One Autumn Leaf rushed forward, while turning around and slashing with his spear. He first had to get away from his opponent before doing anything else, but when he turned around, there was no sign of Lord Grim. There were only so many skills that could make a character disappear. However... with 24 classes, there were too many skills to search through. Sun Xiang already reacted quite quickly, but it was still too late. By the time One Autumn Leaf jumped up and stabbed down with his spear, Lord Grim had already tunneled out from the ground.

Underground Tunneling Technique!　　

Ye Xiu had used this move against Qiu Fei. Through his memory of that, Sun Xiang was able to make an accurate decision. Unfortunately, he was slightly too slow. Ye Xiu struck first. Lord Grim came out of the ground, dodged Evil Annihilation, and once again slashed at One Autumn Leaf's neck.

Then, a Falling Flower Palm.

Ye Xiu didn't use the same move set as he did against Qiu Fei. Instead, he used a Falling Flower Palm to throw One Autumn Leaf backwards. Sun Xiang had grasped Lord Grim's stats. How could Ye Xiu not also grasp the completely reworked One Autumn Leaf?

Were all of these changes to fit to Sun Xiang's style? It didn't seem like it in Ye Xiu's eyes. Sun Xiang's Battle Mage playstyle wasn't anything original. From how Sun Xiang played, Ye Xiu could even see images of himself. And for that type of playstyle, One Autumn Leaf's original set of Silver equipment had been the most optimal. The new level cap didn't revolutionize any sort of new playstyle, so the equipment configuration didn't need to be altered at all. The only thing that needed to be done was upgrade the level and stats of the silver equipment.

However, Ye Xiu noticed that One Autumn Leaf avoided this approach. If it was just to fit Sun Xiang's playstyle, then there didn't need to make such drastic changes. Then why did they do it? Ye Xiu had a good guess. Excellent Era wanted Ye Xiu to face an unfamiliar One Autumn Leaf. They didn't want Ye Xiu to have the advantage of being too familiar with the character.

They succeeded. Ye Xiu was very unfamiliar with this One Autumn Leaf. As for Sun Xiang? Even though he had enough time to familiarize himself with it, that didn't mean it was completely suitable for him either. This completely changed One Autumn Leaf made it so he no longer knew the enemy anymore, but it also lowered Sun Xiang's synchronization to the character at the same time.

This was a double-edged sword. For now, the damage to Ye Xiu was greater. Ye Xiu lost a huge advantage.

As for Excellent Era's wound? If it was just limited to Sun Xiang's capabilities, then the wound wasn't that big. Sun Xiang just wasn't able to reach his maximum potential. That didn't mean he was terrible all of a sudden. If switching a character made a pro player's skill level drop to zero, then that pro player was too awful to be considered a pro.

This wound needed to be made bigger! That wasn't easy to do though.

Just knowing that Sun Xiang was unable to play to the best of his ability wasn't really going to help Ye Xiu win. What he needed to figure out was why Sun Xiang couldn't play at his peak and what Sun Xiang was being limited by. This was how he would beat a strong opponent.

The price he would need to pay to find the answer would be extremely high. It required him to take Sun Xiang's different attacks.

Lord Grim didn't have much health remaining though and was on the losing end. By the time he found the answer, would it be too late to counter attack?

Nothing was certain, but Ye Xiu had made his decision.

Because he was certain that this wasn't an individual competition, but a group arena. Even if he couldn't win, he could pave the way for their next player. In the group arena, only one person could play at a time, but it was also a competition between two teams. Even if he couldn't win, he could still provide the win conditions for their next player. This was how the group arena should be played.

After using Falling Flower Palm, Ye Xiu had Lord Grim charge forward bravely. Right now, he had the initiative. If he had the opportunity to kill Sun Xiang, he obviously wasn't going to mind, but..... Sun Xiang clearly wasn't going to be so polite. One Autumn Leaf's high character stats made it so that Lord Grim's attack effects were reduced. The knockback from Falling Flower Palm wasn't as far as Ye Xiu had anticipated. From this point, it could be seen that the changes done to One Autumn Leaf by Excellent Era were successful. They disrupted what should have been a flow that Ye Xiu was familiar with.

Evil Annihilation and Myriad Manifestations Umbrella once again clashed. One Autumn Leaf's priority advantage was very obvious. Every time the two weapons collided, Ye Xiu had to do more to neutralize the attacks.

"The two sides are fighting again. Ye Xiu is trying to play more intelligently, but Sun Xiang is sticking close to him. It can be seen that Ye Xiu's stamina is going down already. In this exchange, he seems to have given more Chasers to Sun Xiang. In the beginning, he had been doing his utmost to limit the Chasers, but now..... It seems like he's not able to do it anymore....." Li Yibo observed the situation and felt like victory was already leaning towards one side.

"But Ye Xiu has maintained the possibility of counter attacking at any time." Pan Lin said.

"Yes. He's not panicking. He's still playing very calmly. However, what I'm worried about is that if this continues, will Ye Xiu still have the energy to play well in the team competition? In this match, because of the difference in characters, Ye Xiu is clearly spending more effort and energy to get this fight to be evenly matched!" Li Yibo remarked.

Chapter 1020: Not Like This

Li Yibo had been making mistakes throughout the match, but this time, he was on point. At Happy's bench, Wei Chen saw the way the round was going and started getting uneasy.

"What exactly is he planning?" Wei Chen called out.　　

"What's wrong?" Chen Guo hastily asked. She was also extremely nervous. She wanted to close her eyes and wait until this round was over before opening them again. Hearing Wei Chen suddenly speak out, Chen Guo immediately wanted to ask how he thought this round would go. All she saw was that the health on boths sides were dropping. Neither side seemed to have the upper hand. However, Lord Grim had less health at the start, so if this continued on, Lord Grim would be the one to fall.

"He's already lost reason. If he lets his emotions affect him, how is he going to play in the team competition?" Wei Chen was somewhat mad. Chen Guo could see that Wei Chen was truly angry, but... she didn't understand what Wei Chen was talking about.

"Don't worry. He definitely has a reason for playing like this." Widely known as being wild, Sun Zheping was actually very calm at the moment. Even though he was talking to them, his eyes never left the stage.

"If he plays like this, even if he beats Sun Xiang, what's the point? To satisfy his vanity? To tell everyone that One Autumn Leaf's successor isn't as good as him?" Wei Chen's words were difficult for Chen Guo to accept. In her eyes, even though Ye Xiu had his problems, he wasn't that type of person. If he cared about that, how could he have let Excellent Era prance around him as they pleased?

"What are you talking about!" Chen Guo was also getting angry.

"If he keeps on playing like this, how is he going to play in the later team competition?" Wei Chen said.

"What's wrong with that? Which pro player doesn't play in the team competition after the individual competition?" Chen Guo said.

"You don't understand shit." Wei Chen was indeed feeling anxious. His speech became much more intense. He wasn't in the mood to explain it to Chen Guo. He had carried a lot of doubt and hesitation before reaching this point. He knew very well that the current Alliance no longer had a place for him. Any pro player nowadays needed him to rack his brains to beat. Even so, he had persisted until this day because his dream still burned brightly in his heart and because he trusted the person who had convinced him to return. Even though they had once been opponents in the past, it was for that reason that he understood Ye Xiu's thirst for victory.

When Wei Chen came out on stage, he lost to Xiao Shiqin. It took him, Tang Rou, and Mo Fan to take down Xiao Shiqin. 3v1. This type of performance wasn't worthy of any praise. Wei Chen also felt disappointed and worried because of the outcome. However, he wasn't discouraged because he knew that this was only a small portion of the finals. The match hadn't ended yet.

However, when he saw Ye Xiu's performance, his concern turned into panic. Ye Xiu was the pillar of the team. If even Ye Xiu lost his reason and began to only care about himself, how could the far weaker Happy have any chances of winning?

Chen Guo looked at Wei Chen. She didn't bicker about his impoliteness because she knew that Wei Chen was too scared of losing. He would be thirty this year. After seven years of retirement, getting this one chance to return to the pro scene could already be considered a miracle. He hoped to return to the Alliance with Happy more than anyone else. This was his last chance. He was an outdated player with no future for growth. His only hope lay in Happy. The greater the hope, the greater the despair.

Chen Guo didn't argue with Wei Chen. She wasn't good enough. She really couldn't see anything strange about the situation, but she believed that Wei Chen wouldn't be worried over nothing. However, she was more willing to believe in Ye Xiu. Even if she couldn't understand it, she knew that Ye Xiu definitely wouldn't be like what Wei Chen worried for. Losing his reason and only caring about himself was only good for playing Super Mario.

"You must have made a mistake. I believe in him." Chen Guo said firmly. Wei Chen stared blankly for a bit and then sighed: "I hope so."

"Yes, so it's like that." Sun Zheping had been watching the match intensely the entire time. At this moment, he suddenly spoke out, "Old Wei, look carefully."　

"Oh?" Wei Chen stared blankly again.

"This guy is looking to give me trouble!" Sun Zheping unexpectedly smiled.

"You guys….. What are you guys talking about? What did you see?" Chen Guo was puzzled.

"A chance." Sun Zheping said.

"What?"

"A chance to win." Sun Zheping said.　　

"He can win this round?" Chen Guo was wild with joy.

"It's hard to say if he can win this round, but Sun Xiang will definitely go down." Sun Zheping said.

"What do you mean?" Chen Guo didn't understand.　　

"You just wait for the show to start!" Sun Zheping said as he continued to stare at the match.

Chen Guo wanted to go crazy. She really hadn't noticed anything wrong. She looked to her left and right. Wei Chen and Sun ZHeping were watching the match intently. On the other side, she saw Tang Rou's puzzled look. She also didn't understand what Sun Zheping was talking about.

The anxiety in Chen Guo's heart burned. Suddenly, she thought of a bright idea and took out her cellphone.

This match was being broadcasted. She didn't understand, but the broadcast had a commentator and expert discussing the match. She wanted to see what their thoughts were.

Chen Guo used her cellphone to listen to the broadcast, but it would have been better if she hadn't. As soon as she started to listen, her eyes were about to pop out. The commentators were saying that Ye Xiu was in an unfavorable position.　　

Correct!　　

Correct, unfavorable.

Chen Guo could also see it. Lord Grim was losing health faster than One Autumn Leaf. His health already wasn't as high to begin with. If he was bleeding faster than his opponent, the disparity between One Autumn Leaf and Lord Grim would only widen.

What's going on?

Chen Guo really didn't understand. Neither Li Yibo nor Pan Lin could give a good answer either. From Sun Zheping and Wei Chen, she could only see them focused on the match.　

"What's going on, senior? It looks like you're looking weak!" Sun Xiang suddenly said in the chat.

"If this keeps up, how are you going to make me lose? I really don't understand." Sun Xiang continued.　　

"I'm afraid that if this continues, you won't understand how you died!"

"Could you be an NPC? When your health reaches 10%, you'll suddenly go berserk?" Sun Xiang chattered incessantly.

"Today's Sun Xiang is really... uh, talkative..." Pan Lin sighed. Ye Xiu didn't respond though. There wasn't any conversation.

Sun Xiang seized the opportunity to talk trash: "Why aren't you talking? Is the pace too fast? There's no time for you to type?" After Sun Xiang taunted, he typed a bunch of emojis, showing that he had energy to spare.

"It's about right." Ye XiuXIu suddenly replied and added a sunglasses emoji.

"What?" Sun Xiang was still asking!

"You said it! When my health reaches 10%, I'll go berserk. It's such a rare opportunity to meet. I can't leave you disappointed!" Ye Xiu said.

"Is that so? I'm looking forward to it! But it looks like... your health has already reached 10%? Where is it?" Sun Xiang said. He even had One Autumn Leaf look left and right as if he were looking for the berserk.

"I'm coming." Ye Xiu typed. Sun Xiang heard a sharp whistle from behind his character and hurriedly had his One Autumn Leaf dodge to the side. A shuriken flew past him.

Lord Grim was standing in front of him, but the shuriken had actually come from behind.

Boomerang Shuriken?

Boomerang Shuriken wasn't a skill name, but rather a technique. When using a Ninja's Shuriken, throw in a curve such that the shuriken would return like a boomerang.

Sun Xiang wasn't surprised that Ye Xiu could do it, but how come he hadn't noticed when he threw that shuriken?

Sun Xiang attached a lot of importance to this match. Even though he spoke a lot, he was very focused.

Yet even so, he hadn't noticed when that Shuriken had been thrown. His brain quickly went over the previous exchange. There had just been one tiny moment when he turned away and Lord Grim disappeared from his view, yet Ye XIu had actually grasped that tiny opening?

Sun Xiang was surprised, but just that alone wasn't enough to beat him.　

If that was what a berserk entailed, Sun Xiang was afraid that he would laugh so hard his teeth would fly out.

This obviously wasn't the berserk. After One Autumn Leaf dodged the shuriken, it started.

Lord Grim stepped forward. His Myriad Manifestations Umbrella changed into a spear and slashed up with a Sky Strike.　

Sun Xiang didn't dodge it. One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation faced it with an attack to block it.

But Lord Grim started to move the spear horizontally. The Sky Strike's trajectory was no longer a straight line, but a curve.　　

Sun Xiang didn't fear this type of change. He had One Autumn Leaf chase after the Sky Strike, as if he wouldn't rest if the two spears didn't clash.

Who would have thought that Lord Grim would have moved his spear back. Sky Strike once again went along its original trajectory as the Sky Strike continued.

It was too late for Sun Xiang to make any adjustments. He hastily jumped backward. Sky Strike suddenly swayed in front of his eyes.

Dragon Tooth!

The umbrella shot at him like a viper.

His spear's block was off and One Autumn Leaf was in midair. In that instant, Sun Xiang's mind went blank.

He actually wasn't able to respond to such a simple attack. His hands felt his keyboard and mouse, unable to do anything. What's going on? How did this happen?

Chapter 1021: Overturning the Sky

Dragon Tooth looked like a normal attack. For a low-level skill like Dragon Tooth, if only the damage was considered, the powerful One Autumn Leaf wouldn't even bother to block it. However, the value of Dragon Tooth didn't lie in the damage, but rather the stun effect that it carried. Dragon Tooth could be considered the most used skill among Battle Mages. It had the greatest coverage. It could be used to start a combo, and in theory, could be used as a follow up for any skill.

In theory…..

Facing One Autumn Leaf, turning theory into reality wasn't easy.　

Because One Autumn Leaf was too strong. Due to the character's resistances, the stun from Dragon Tooth would be significantly reduced, leading to many follow-ups with Dragon Tooth being unviable against One Autumn Leaf. This was why God-level characters were fearsome. It wasn't as simple as having higher defense and attack. Strong resistances greatly limited the opponent's options. These limitations weren't just the result of piling stats on a character. The R&D teams would adjust the character's stats depending on the player's tendencies. The character's stats would try to make up for the player's weaknesses, as well as support the player's strengths.

This was the problem that Ye Xiu saw with Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf.

One Autumn Leaf's switched equipment was still very good, but the synergy between the character and player wasn't as perfect. Strictly speaking, this tiny imperfection couldn't be considered a hole, but Ye Xiu couldn't be any more familiar with Battle Mage stats and One Autumn Leaf's original stats. Ye Xiu analyzed it bit by bit and turned it into a hole.

Eating a Dragon Tooth mid-jump backwards?　

In the eyes of the spectators, so what?

With One Autumn Leaf's stats, the stun effect would disappear in a flash. One Autumn Leaf happened to be jumping backwards too. There wasn't any opportunity for Lord Grim to make any follow-ups after the stun. That jump looked like a beautiful and successful dodge.

That's what everyone thought. No one thought that this stun effect wasn't the important point. It was the attack itself that was important. Because before this, Sun Xiang had been stunned, which allowed the Dragon Tooth to hit.　　

The Sky Strike changing directions twice tore at the slight imperfection in the synergy between Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf. If this had been the original One Autumn Leaf, Sun Xiang would have been able to block it.

But now, he couldn't dodge or block it. This was the scariest part about this attack.

Sun Xiang was at a loss as One Autumn Leaf landed on the ground. Lord Grim didn't chase after him, but the spear in Lord Grim's hands did. Magic undulations coiled around the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella into a humongous dragon.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's spear form actually transformed into a high-level skill.

Even though this skill could only be at the lowest rank one, this was already an incredibly powerful skill considering Lord Grim's skill set.

One Autumn Leaf hastily rolled to the side. From those movements, it seemed as if Sun Xiang was panicking.　

Ye Xiu hadn't hoped for this attack to hit. After Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, he had hidden a follow-up attack. But this follow-up attack wasn't actually needed.

This guy... dodged too far, no?

Sun Xiang's movements had been too excessive. It was outside of Ye Xiu's expectations. Moreover, Sun Xiang didn't counter attack as soon as the first clear opportunity appeared. It seemed like he was still thinking about that previous Dragon Tooth.

Has his focus been disrupted?

That would be a pleasant surprise.

Ye Xiu hadn't expected Sun Xiang's mental state to tilt after that attack. If a player wasn't focused, the player's reaction speed and playing would slow down. At the highest levels of play, this was enough to be fatal.

Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella transformed into a gun form. Three Anti-Tank Missiles shot towards One Autumn Leaf.　　

If this was the usual Sun Xiang in peak condition, he would have just taken these attacks and charged through them, but at this moment, Sun Xiang's reaction speed was clearly a lot slower slow. By the time he started moving, the missiles had already reached his face. He could only make a roll and dodge these missiles in a crude manner.

Lord Grim quickly approached. Sky Strike!

Sun Xiang tensed up. He still didn't understand what had happened previously, but he was certain that it wasn't a coincidence. Ye Xiu had definitely done it intentionally. Changing the arc of Sky Strike twice was to allow the following Dragon Tooth to hit. Even though there weren't really any follow up after that Dragon Tooth, that was just one time. What about next time?

Sun Xiang didn't dare to be negligent. When the Sky Strike arrived, he chose to dodge it.　

Ye Xiu smirked. Sun Xiang gave up on blocking with an attack and instead chose to dodge. For Sun Xiang, that was equivalent to giving up on what he was best at.　

Blocking with an attack fit Sun Xiang's personality best. It was also what was easiest for him. He was still very good at dodging, but it wasn't what he liked to do. If he had a choice, Sun Xiang would very rarely choose to dodge. But now, he felt compelled to choose what he didn't like to do.

That was easier than I thought!

Ye Xiu thought to himself and had Lord Grim continued chasing. It was just a Sky Strike. It wasn't enough for him to gain the upper hand. Ye Xiu had many more things for Sun Xiang to enjoy, all of which happened after Lord Grim's health dropped to 10%.

Sun Xiang was in a daze.

Ye Xiu's attacks weren't sharp, but they were very precise. Every attack targeted a vital point. He hit where it hurt.

Sun Xian felt uncomfortable. In his three years as a pro player, he had never felt so uncomfortable before.

It wasn't like he had never fought against Ye Xiu before. When he had been part of Team Conquering Clouds, he had fought against Team Excellent Era three times. And in two of those, Sun Xiang and Ye Xiu had faced each other in the individual competition.

Even though he lost both times, Ye Xiu had been using the Battle God One Autumn Leaf. On the other hand, Sun Xiang was using a so-so pro character from a mid to low tier team.

Although he lost, the fights had been very close. Sun Xiang had had a good chance of winning.

If he, too, had a character like One Autumn Leaf, perhaps the results would have been different!

That was what many people said after those matches. That season, Sun Xiang had been a spectacular rookie. Using a normal character, he challenged Ye Qiu and the Battle God One Autumn Leaf. Losing by only a sliver of health, even in defeat, Sun Xiang basked in glory.

If I had One Autumn Leaf, I definitely would have won.

It wasn't just others who thought that. Sun Xiang thought that as well.

Later on, he came to possess of One Autumn Leaf. Because of him, Ye Xiu was forced to leave the team and announce his retirement. This made Sun Xiang truly feel like the winner. He looked forward to the future awaiting him.

And then under his lead, Excellent Era was like a wild horse out of control and was relegated…..

This was an embarrassment. It hadn't been easy for Sun Xiang to accept.　

He wanted to prove himself. But the Challenger League? Lead Excellent Era back into the Alliance through the Challenger League? How could that be considered proof? For Excellent Era, this should be as easy as eating food. What's more, after getting relegated, they even got Xiao Shiqin to come over.

It looked like he could only endure for this upcoming year.

That was what Sun Xiang originally thought. However, then there were rumors of Ye Xiu forming his own team and joining the Challenger League.　

This piece of news was like a stimulant for Sun Xiang.

After switching ace players, Team Excellent Era's placings improved slightly before directly falling into relegations. The controversy over Sun Xiang was quite big. Comparing him to the former captain Ye Qiu was very normal.

The club firmly stood by his side the entire time, but in reality? Sun Xiang needed to prove himself.

The Challenger League wasn't enough for him to prove himself. Sun Xiang could only impatiently wait for the next year, so he could shut up those who said he was worse than Ye Qiu. Who would have thought that an opportunity would arrive in the Challenger League? This instantly made the Challenger League interesting. For him, this was a stage meant for the two of them. How well would Team Happy perform? How would he lead Team Excellent Era? The finale would only happen when the two sides clashed. It was a finale that he and the media would look forward to.

That year, he lost because his character wasn't as good as One Autumn Leaf. And now, he possessed One Autumn Leaf. He would let Ye Xiu witness just how powerful his Battle God was.

At this moment, Sun Xiang didn't hurry to beat Ye Xiu. He was like a cat playing with his food, showing off his superiority. Just winning this match wasn't enough. He needed everyone to see that beating Ye Xiu was a trivial matter to him.

But now….. Why was it like this?

"Another attack hit. This was a Sword Slash chasing after One Autumn Leaf. It was a very accurate read. What's going on? We know that going berserk at 10% health was just a joke, but why did it actually happen when Lord Grim's health reached 10%? Even though Lord Grim didn't follow through with any combos, it was obvious who had the upper hand. Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf seems to be struggling. What's going on?" The commentator, Pan Lin, shouted, but he didn't get a response like he had anticipated. He turned to look at his casting partner. Li Yibo was puzzled. He clearly wasn't prepared for something like this to happen. He had been singing Sun Xiang high praises the entire time, saying how Sun Xiang was playing well and suppressing Ye Xiu.

How did Ye Xiu suddenly overturn the sky in the blink of an eye? Moreover, why was the advantage so obvious?

What's going on? You're asking me?! I'm the one who wants to find someone to ask! Today's match was making him feel very depressed.

Chapter 1022: Rolling Meat

Lord Grim, who only had 10% health remaining, clearly held the upper hand. A professional commentator wasn't needed to see that. Lord Grim's 10% health seemed to be immovable as if he had become invincible. On the other hand, One Autumn Leaf was like an open faucet, gushing blood. Even a Berserker wouldn't trade their health like this. This was irrefutable proof that One Autumn Leaf was at the disadvantage.

One Autumn Leaf still had half of his health left. In the previous exchanges, Sun Xiang had been constantly giving Lord Grim heavy injuries. He had felt the thrill of a predator playing with its food. He had felt like the fight was under his complete control. Ye Xiu seemed to be struggling, trying to hang onto his life. It's useless. Your time is already over…..

Sun Xiang had been preparing to say these words the moment he won, but at this moment, the situation had flipped. No, to be more accurate, who had the upper hand was even more clear now. Before, Sun Xiang could feel his opponent's struggle, but now? Sun Xiang couldn't even struggle. Every attack from Lord Grim would make his head go blank as he failed to come up with any sort of counterplay.

Where did I go wrong?

Sun Xiang was feeling fretful. He watched as his health slowly bled away. He originally had fifty percent of his health left. In the blink of an eye, it turned to thirty percent. When his health reached twenty percent, he thought to himself: what had he done so far? He couldn't even struggle. He had been waiting for this opportunity to come for so long and this was going to be the outcome?

In this match, the wide disparity between both sides could be easily seen.　

He was young and brimming with talent. He was destined to leave his mark on the Glory Alliance in the near future. On the other hand, his opponent had been in retirement for a year. His most resplendent achievements had been made six years ago.

He possessed the Battle God One Autumn Leaf. If the Battle God claimed second, no character would dare to claim first. On the other hand, his opponent had only just started leveling his character when the tenth server opened. It was a small character with a name that even begged to be laughed at. (TL: A more accurate translation for Lord Grim would be Please Don't Laugh)

He had gone into the fight at full health, while his opponent had just finished an intense match and only had half of his health left. Even though Lord Grim was given time to recover, it was only until 70% health. The two sides hadn't started from the same line.

For this match, let along losing, Sun Xiang wouldn't even accept an even match.

But now, he seemed to be walking towards the abyss of defeat with every step he took, while Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was behind him, pushing him closer towards that abyss.

Lose like this?

No!

Sun Xiang's spirit suddenly rose as he saw Lord Grim slash towards his head. He immediately had One Autumn Leaf scrunch up into a ball and roll to the side. He wasn't out of Lord Grim's attack range. It could be be said that this dodge wasn't successful. It was a roll that no skilled player would have done.

But Sun Xiang did it. Not waiting for the commentators to note this mistake, One Autumn Leaf dodged the blade, but didn't get up and instead continued to roll to the side.

It was too ugly to look at. Along with Lord Grim's swing and the rolling One Autumn Leaf, it made the viewers think of the phrase: rolling meat**.

This wasn't a good phrase. To make people think of this phrase signified just how unsightly One Autumn Leaf looked right now. The character that was known as the great Battle God and always viewed as Glory's number one character, it could actually move in such a vile manner?

The crowd instantly fell into silence. Excellent Era's fans had trouble responding. As for Excellent Era's players? Tao Xuan was embarrassed. He even glanced to his left and right like a little thief, as if he didn't want others to see One Autumn Leaf's unsightly appearance.　

Unfortunately, his hopes wouldn't come true. It wasn't just the crowd that saw this, but also the millions of people watching the broadcast.

The entire Glory world might have frozen at this moment. One Autumn Leaf actually rolled several times in a row to get away from Lord Grim's combo.

Would Ye Xiu be startled by this ugly move? Of course not.

No one knew better than him that, although One Autumn Leaf's several rolls looked very ugly, these rolls were truly effective. Sun Xiang managed to save himself from Lord Grim's combo with that.

The rhythm had been broken!　

At this moment, the other side would most likely counter attack, and with Sun Xiang's personality, the counter attack would only be that much more impatient. Ye Xiu didn't dare to be negligent. He hastily had Lord Grim move back two steps to distance himself from his opponent. However, Ye Xiu discovered that One Autumn Leaf did the same thing.

Not only was Sun Xiang not in a hurry to counter attack, he had his character retreat to distance himself.

"This guy... focused again?" Ye Xiu was startled.　　

The two characters confronted each other. Neither side made any rash moves. One Autumn Leaf was at 20% health. Lord Grim was at 10% health.

One Autumn Leaf's advantage was obvious, but he looked to be on the losing side. Not rushing forward to attack in this type of situation wasn't Sun Xiang's style. This guy was the type to think of himself as invincible, even if he only had 1% of his health left and would charge forward proudly to fight with his opponent. But at this moment, he unexpectedly chose to retreat?

Normal players might not understand what this implied, but those who understood Sun Xiang's style would immediately notice this abnormality.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo quickly explained this abnormality to everyone.

Was this a talent about to go berserk? The two commentators concluded.

The two characters started to move. They didn't rush forward, but instead moved horizontally, slowly closing the distance between them.

Lord Grim had long-ranged attacks, but he didn't use them at this moment. Instead, he maintained practically the same rhythm as Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf.

"Both sides have began to play more cautiously. Neither side plans on making any rash moves." Li Yibo said.

"This makes me think of when two masters confront each other in wuxia stories. Even though they're just standing still, neither side has any holes. Whoever moves first is the first to expose an opening." Pan Lin said.　　

"Wow, it really does feel like that." Li Yibo said.

"Then is Sun Xiang about to burst forth?" Pan Lin asked. He was clearly hoping for this to happen.

However, that wasn't what happened.　　

After the two sides carefully moved around, in the end, they started fighting again. Soon afterwards, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf was suppressed again.

A talent about to go berserk?

What a joke! Pan Lin and Li Yibo once again felt like they had fallen into a trap.

"Sun Xiang doesn't seem to have any way out of the combo!" Pan Lin returned back to the previous topic. When the two sides fought a few minutes ago, that was pretty much all he said.

The match seemed to have gone back to the old road. Only Ye Xiu knew that that wasn't the case.

Before, he had been carefully probing out the level of synergy between Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf and then found small holes he could exploit. But now, it was the reverse. Sun Xiang had started testing what those problems were using Ye Xiu's Lord Grim.

Previously, Sun Xiang's mind kept going blank. He wasn't focused, making it so he wasn't able to figure out where the problems lay. But this time, it was different. He was fully focused now. Sun Xiang was keenly inspecting where his problems were.　

The holes that Ye Xiu had found were being patched up

One Autumn Leaf's health was still bleeding away. Excellent Era's fans watched on with worry, but Sun Xiang wasn't the same. The more he played, the calmer he became. He found the problems one by one.

These holes that Ye Xiu had uncovered couldn't help but make Sun Xiang somewhat fearful.

These were problems that he himself hadn't been aware of, yet Ye Xiu was actually able to find them? And everything had been figured out during the match?

He really is terrifying…...　

This was the first time Sun Xiang felt fear. He had fought against Ye Xiu twice before. Even though he lost both times, the only thought he had was that he only lost by a little bit. If he was the one with One Autumn Leaf, then he would certainly have a crushing victory.　

It was only now did he wake up from his delusion. One Autumn Leaf's title as Battle God hadn't come from just the Silver equipment on him. It was a character that had been raised step by step under Ye Xiu's control.

The title was granted to the character, but in reality, the title should be granted to the player. It was the player who brought glory to the character.

Sun Xiang finally understood just how terrifying the Battle God was.

However, this wasn't going to stop Sun Xiang's desire to win. His pride always told him that no matter how great the opponent was, he was better.

The holes were quickly repaired. As soon as he figured out the problems, he just needed to be more aware to eliminate them. The imperfect synergy between him and his character was still there, but that itself wasn't fatal. It just meant that it wasn't perfect.

Sun Xiang had actually been quite happy about this discovery. His imperfect form could beat Ye Xiu. Wasn't that even greater evidence of his skill?

The opportunity to counter attack was almost here! Sun Xiang looked at One Autumn Leaf's health. Ten percent. He had also locked onto this moment. On the other hand, Lord Grim's health hadn't gone down since then. It was pretty much at ten percent too.

Perfect. Everyone's on an equal playing field. A fair victory begins now!

When One Autumn Leaf's health dropped to ten percent, Sun Xiang finally sounded the horn to counterattack.

Chapter 1023: The Classic 0.03% Kill

Dragon Tooth!

Sun Xiang didn't do any theatrics. He used the simplest of initiations for Battle Mage combos.

After jumping backwards a little to avoid it, Lord Grim swung with a Sky Strike.

Sun Xiang immediately composed himself to deal with it. When Ye Xiu had managed to use this to create an opening, he had done so by changing Sky Strike's trajectory. So this time, Sun Xiang didn't bother to get One Autumn Leaf to block and instead sidestepped by three body units, swerving to Lord Grim's flank.

Lord Grim twisted, Sky Strike chasing after him. That was when One Autumn Leaf suddenly blocked it.

Could there be any more variations to Sky Strike?

No, the upwards stabbing of Sky Strike wasn't endless and limitless. If you kept stabbing up up up, then wouldn't you just end up throwing your weapon away?

　　

One Autumn Leaf's three body unit sidestep had pulled this Sky Strike far enough so that it couldn't be modified any further. Even so, Sun Xiang didn't hold back from his habitual reaction: block.

This actually wasn't just Sun Xiang's personal habit and style. Battle Mages needed their attacks to hit in order to stockpile Chasers. Blocks were considered hits by the system, so they could also produce Chasers. Thus, all Battle Mages would block if possible.

　

The current Sun Xiang didn't deviate from this and neither did the past Ye Xiu.

So, Ye Xiu knew that while Sun Xiang had done a lot of dodging before, he would still choose to block when it came down to it. He couldn't just dodge instead of block to cover for his openings because if he did that with a Battle Mage, he would only be reducing his own strength.

Blocks were mostly defensive techniques for other classes, but for the Battle Mage, blocks were an offense in a defense. Then, when their opponent became too concerned about not letting the Battle Mage create Chasers and intentionally avoided the blocks, the true fatal power of the block was revealed: it had created chaos in the opponent's rhythm.

Thus, no Battle Mage would easily let go of blocks. For Sun Xiang to temporary give up his habits and resort to dodging so often was an extremely rare and commendable effort. His pride wouldn't allow him change his style so completely. He had experienced the terror of fighting Ye Xiu, but he wouldn't cower because of it. He wanted Ye Xiu to experience his skill, too.

The block swept forth brazenly.

This Sky Strike had lost the effect and power it originally was meant to have, so Ye Xiu obviously wouldn't send it over and gift One Autumn Leaf with a Chaser. Sky Strike was cancelled and One Autumn Leaf's block hit air.

This created a great opening to take advantage of. The block of a Battle Mage would bring this sort of trouble to their opponent. Should you let him block or not?

Ye Xiu had chosen the latter, giving Sun Xiang a chance to mount an offensive.

A Falling Flower Palm was thrown out at Lord Grim.

Mounting an offense often necessitated a lot of low level skills, as they were fast to activate. As for powerful skills, if you didn't pave a road for them, you would already be late to the game by the time you unleashed them.

As for this quick Falling Flower Palm of One Autumn Leaf's, Ye Xiu didn't seem to have much of a choice but to have Lord Grim return with his own Falling Flower Palm.

The palms of the two characters hit, and released a magical pulse that swept up the dust and dirt around them. Lord Grim's figure skidded backwards. How could Lord Grim compete with One Autumn Leaf in priority for the same skill? This clash had still given One Autumn Leaf a Chaser. Battle Mages had a total of five Chasers, unleashed through one of five low level skills, Sky Strike, Dragon Tooth, Double Stab, Falling Flower Palm, and Circle Swing. Because of Chasers, Battle Mages relied on low level skills a lot.

Falling Flower Palm had ended with Lord Grim being pushed back. As for One Autumn Leaf? One Autumn Leaf had managed to gain a Fire Chaser, which was immediately sent out by Sun Xiang. A magical pulse like a flickering flame swirled around One Autumn Leaf's arms. This was the visual effect from the strength buff that the Fire Chaser gave. As for that big fireball of a Chaser, it had already sped towards Lord Grim. Sun Xiang was about to prepare a follow up attack when something flashed in front of his eyes.

What was that?

Sun Xiang didn't have the time to think, subconsciously having One Autumn Leaf to dodge.

But it was too late!

That thing had come too fast and by the time Sun Xiang noticed it, it seemed like his Fire Chaser had cracked open as if something trying to worm its way through.

　

Lord Grim's attack used the Fire Chaser as cover. The finesse this required was unreal. Sun Xiang hadn't noticed it at first, only reacting when it had shot through the Fire Chaser, but by then it was already too late.

He was shot!

Lord Grim had sent out a bullet and One Autumn Leaf was immediately stunned when it hit.

This wasn't the small stun from a normal shot. That miniscule effect would do nothing against a powerful character like One Autumn Leaf.

This was a Stun Bullet, a low level skill of the Spirfire class and stun was its crucial effect.

Then, a blade flashed and cut the Fire Chaser in half before striking the stunned One Autumn Leaf with a Sword Draw.

In this exchange, it was clear that One Autumn Leaf had not benefited. The only gains he had was the Fire Chaser that was buffed his strength.

　

However, the one with the initiative was still Lord Grim. After the Sword Draw, the Myriad Manifestation Umbrella didn't change forms, already following up with a Collapsing Mountain.

One Autumn Leaf hastily dodged, jumping backwards, while stabbing forth with Evil Annihilation, hoping to pull Lord Grim into a Circle Swing.

Lord Grim's sword swerved. The Collapsing Mountain missed One Autumn Leaf entirely and struck Evil Annihilation instead.

One Autumn Leaf gained another Chaser, but who would be more clear on the gains and losses of these Chasers than Ye Xiu? He knew which Chasers he could afford to give and which he couldn't. He wasn't the kind of person who would be troubled by a Battle Mage's blocks because, unfortunately, he was the one who created this playstyle.

Giving One Autumn Leaf a Chaser had allowed Lord Grim to close in.

Sun Xiang was uncomfortable. He had thought he had the situation under control, but he never expected that it would spiral away from him again.

That was when Ye Xiu stopped using those openings and came at him head on with these attacks.

The careful preparation Sun Xiang had made to deal with Ye Xiu's tricks was for naught.

Of course, he wasn't afraid of this direct and straightforward brawl, and would even have an advantage due to his young age and stamina. Yet now, he had to keep his guard up against another possibility, where he might fall into a trap due to a subconscious action. So, he had to stay absolutely focused.

With Sun Xiang completely focused, it wouldn't be easy to distract him, but having to focus on so many aspects was definitely draining. It was good that Sun Xiang was young so he could endure.

Let's see who'll make it to the end!

Sun Xiang gritted his teeth, advancing and having One Autumn Leaf meet Lord Grim blow for blow, while also paying attention to the modifications each of Lord Grim's strikes could go through, determined to not fall into that real life stun again.

The overall situation resulted in a deadlock.

The health of both sides dropped, nine percent, seven percent, six percent...

Who would reach zero first?

No one could guess. In this moment, either side could be the victor. However, looking at the big picture, Ye Xiu had been at a disadvantage when the match began, so he had already won by being able to reach this point, fighting Sun Xiang.

Unfortunately, that wasn't how matches were judged. The true victor was the one who was left standing.

Who would it be?

Many people in the audience stood up, as if they wouldn't be able to see clearly otherwise. However, after they did that, the people sitting behind them really couldn't see. Some people began to argue and others just stood up as well, thus, the majority of the present audience had come to their feet to continue watching the match.

The Excellent Era fans had already forgotten to cheer. This crucial moment made them just as tense as the players on the field.

Curse Arrows!

That was when Lord Grim summoned several small black arrows with Curse Arrows while dodging One Autumn Leaf's attack, hoping to slow down One Autumn Leaf's momentum.

However, when victory was in grasp, Curse Arrows? That wouldn't be able to kill him, so there was no way he was letting this chance go!

One Autumn Leaf advanced in spite of the damage. Stronger characters held an advantage in situations like this. Often, they could afford to be more aggressive than other characters, because in situations where other characters couldn't hold on, they could.

Slide Kick!

Seeing One Autumn Leaf charge forth, Lord Grim didn't retreat and charged as well.

One Autumn Leaf jumped up, spear stabbing down at the Slide Kicking Lord Grim with a Circle Swing.

Lord Grim rolled to avoid it and knelt on one knee, swinging open the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella and shooting furiously with Gatling Gun.

Sun Xiang was even more direct. One Autumn Leaf, falling from his jump, shook his spear and suddenly, a tumultuous magical pulse exploded out from Evil Annihilation. He had somehow managed to unleash a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky in the time it took for Lord Grim to roll!

Gatling Gun's bullets came in a flood, but compared to Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, who would die?

Sun Xiang smirked. Unspecialized was something no one had much experience dealing with. However, since it had popped up, and they knew there was a possibility of facing it, why wouldn't Excellent Era put effort into researching it?

　

The only thing Excellent Era lacked was the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella. As for unspecialized accounts, they had began levelling several of them up after realizing they might meet Ye Xiu and Lord Grim in the Challenger League.

Excellent Era had spent no expense to deal with Ye Xiu. They had tried to research the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, but in the end they had gotten nowhere. However, if Excellent Era didn't look into the possibilities one could achieve with an unspecialized and such a weapon, then they didn't deserve to be called a pro team.

There was no contest in who would benefit in an exchange between Gatling Gun and Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Ye Xiu obviously couldn't just let this exchange happen and hastily had Lord Grim dodge.

Want to escape? It's too late!!

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky's dragon head swerved towards Lord Grim.

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, Dragon Raises it's Head! The audience exploded into cheers. From their perspective, this was the deciding strike in the match.

However, it wasn't. Lord Grim's movements were extremely precise. He seemed to have calculated Rising Dragon Soars the Sky's pathing and, with a single step, was already behind the dragon's head.

That was when everyone saw that the dragon head, which had already swerved to the side twisted even further, almost in the completely opposite direction.

"Ah!!" Pan Lin screamed in excitement in the live broadcast, "Dragon Raises it's Head? No, this isn't it. This is no long Dragon Raises its Head, it's already a Dragon Looks Back!!" The new technique for Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had been christened by Pan Lin.

　

"Spectacular! This is probably a technical modification made possible after the level 75 update." Even Li Yibo, who was usually rather calm and tried to appear omniscient, couldn't hold back his excitement anymore.

"Rising Dragon Soars the Sky hits! This is a new technique, Dragon Looks Back! As expected of a team with the Battle God. They are a representation of the greatest skill level a Battle Mage can reach. In this match alone, we've witnessed two new Battle Mage techniques." Pan Lin yelled. He was about to announce victory, but then suddenly saw that, while Lord Grim had been hit by the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, he hadn't died. He had managed to perform a Guard behind his back, managing to catch this attack.

However, the amount of damage Guard could reduce was limited and Rising Dragon Soars the Sky wasn't something it could neutralize. Lord Grim, a Guard at his back, was thrown forward by this attack, skidding all the way in front of One Autumn Leaf. However, his health wasn't completely gone. The broadcast immediately switched to a close up. 0.03 percent. Lord Grim's health had fallen to the point where they needed two digits after the decimal point to express it. This was probably an amount that One Autumn Leaf could destroy with a punch, even after throwing away Evil Annihilation.

Yet, the current One Autumn Leaf was still trapped in the ending lag of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. No matter how amazing Sun Xiang's mechanics were, it was impossible for him to do anything right now.

Lord Grim had been pushed directly in front of Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf by One Autumn Leaf. He only had 0.03 percent of his health left, but he struck the true deciding blow.

The entire stadium had gone silent and the commentator Pan Lin gaped. In this moment, he couldn't think of anything to describe the scene before him.

Such a spectacular Rising Dragon Soars the Sky Dragon Looks Back didn't manage to kill the opponent, but instead pushed the opponent in front of himself and sent himself to death?

Pan Lin had originally thought out what he was going to say.

Sun Xiang, using a mutation of Rising Dragon Soars the Sky even more spectacular than the Dragon Raises its Head that Ye Xiu created, managed to defeat Ye Xiu. What a meaningful, amazing way of succeeding the old with the new. This scene could've been a perfect ending to this battle, turning it into a classic moment remembered by all those who played Glory!

But now it was all gone!

All Lord Grim did was Guard. Though placing a Guard behind a character's back had some degree of difficulty, it was still a level 20 and under skill. How could that possibly compare to Dragon Looks Back?

0.03 percent!

Just that 0.03 percent, an amount of health that would be lost in any exchange, somehow managed to last till the end. If it didn't, then so long as Lord Grim was killed, the classic moment wouldn't have to be changed, even with that Guard.

Yet now, nothing was the same.

　　

The sixth match of the Challenger League finals went to Happy, Ye Xiu, and Lord Grim.

That's right, Lord Grim.

Chapter 1024: That Also Counts as a 1v3?

On stage, the last one standing was Lord Grim. One Autumn Leaf lay at his feet. One Autumn Leaf had once brought Ye Xiu boundless glory. This time, it was his opponent, and it fell by his hand.

The crowd was silent. Team Happy's few fans had also forgotten to cheer.

He won?

They had a hard time believing it. One Autumn Leaf's Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had been filled with vigor. Dragon Raising Its Head into Dragon Looks Back. Such a crazy technique made them believe that Lord Grim had fallen. But the last one standing on stage was Lord Grim. What exactly happened in that moment?

The broadcast took great pains to replay that moment. In comparison, Ye Xiu's final blow to One Autumn Leaf wasn't anything special. He just took advantage of the ending lag from One Autumn Leaf's high level move and did a quick combo. Neither side had much health left, so a quick combo was enough to finish off One Autumn Leaf.

The broadcast replayed the clip. It followed Lord Grim and showed the moment he blocked the Dragon Looks Back from behind.

0.03% health. The clip intentionally zoomed in on Lord Grim's health.

"What a spectacular block. However, it was extremely risky. That final 0.03% health left is evidence of that. If that block had been off in the slightest, it would have been a different result." Pan Lin came out of his disappointment and commented on the replay. For him personally, he had no bias towards Ye Xiu or Sun Xiang. He just wanted more to talk about. Sun Xiang's Dragon Looks Back giving the final blow to Ye Xiu would definitely have been much more exciting. Pan Lin looked at things from the media's point of view. He had hoped for more flashy performances. The outcome made him a bit disappointed, but he had to admit that this fight had been a brilliant one.

"Coach Li, 0.03% health. Do you think that Ye Xiu actually planned for that to happen or was it just luck?" Pan Lin asked.

"..." Li Yibo was annoyed. Can you not ask me to guess what Ye Xiu was thinking?

Pan Lin saw Li Yibo furrow his brows without saying anything. He immediately feigned as if those words were just a sigh and switched topics.

In the crowd, Team Tiny Herb's three players were discussing this question.

"Probably luck? 0.03% health? That number is too precise. I think it's luck." Liu Xiaobie expressed. As a Blade Master, he naturally had a deep understanding of blocking and knew the difficulty of executing such a block.

"Under normal situations, it'd be nearly impossible to calculate, but Ye Xiu should have a very good understanding of his opponent's character, no? So it's possible that he could have such a precise calculation." Xu Bin said.

"But One Autumn Leaf is a bit different than before from what I see." Gao Yingjie said.

"Hm, that's true." Xu Bin nodded his head.

"So it's luck?" Liu Xiaobie said.

"It's hard to say..... In any case, you can't be careless when facing him." Xu Bin said.　　

"Will he be our opponent in the future?" Liu Xiaobie mumbled softly. Ye Xiu's victory had completely changed the atmosphere in the stadium, but the problem was that Happy was still on the losing side. Team Excellent Era still has two players left. As for Happy? Lord Grim only has 0.03% health. He pretty much doesn't count... even if he tried to hide and recover his health, his opponent probably wouldn't give him enough time. Moreover, Wish Prayer was still on cooldown. In the group arena, there was no recovery after a round was complete. Whatever state you are in when the round ends will be the same at the start of the next round.

Happy was still in a disadvantageous position. Excellent Era was a pro team that had experienced hundreds of matches. They wouldn't be shaken by a single loss even if it was their ace player.

Liu Xiaobie wasn't wrong. However, he neglected the relationship between Ye Xiu and Excellent Era.

If it were any other player that took Sun Xiang down, Excellent Era could regain their calm and continue with their advantage, but it was Ye Xiu who took down Sun Xiang, the one who was supposed to be his successor. However, Sun Xiang lost. The implications of this loss were simply too great.

The instant One Autumn Leaf fell, Team Excellent Era's boss Tao Xuan almost went insane. The importance of this confrontation was as important as the entire finals, yet they lost in such a manner... Lord Grim only had 0.03% health left. People might not stress this small detail. Ye Xiu won. Sun Xiang lost. That was the result. In view of this result, people might talk more about how Lord Grim wasn't at full health from the beginning. Tao Xuan could imagine how the media would ask sharp questions about this fight. How would he explain it when the time came?

Tao Xuan's expression was incomparably ugly. Excellent Era's other players subconsciously kept their distance from their boss. At this moment, Sun Xiang exited the stage to their bench. His gaze was filled with incredulousness. He had actually lost. He had faced a character who was inferior to One Autumn Leaf and was also not at full health, yet he still lost to Ye Xiu.

Why did it turn out this way?

Am I really not as good as him?

This was the first time Sun Xiang doubted himself because this time, he couldn't find any excuse. His gaze shifted to the other side at Happy's bench, but he unexpectedly saw Ye Xiu also exit the stage.

Sun Xiang stared blankly.

Why did Ye Xiu come out? Players were not allowed to leave the stage in the middle of a match. Doing that was equivalent to forfeiting!

At this moment, the referee jogged over to Happy's seats.

"What are you doing? You don't know that players are not allowed to leave the stage mid-match?" The referee asked. Leaving was absolutely not permitted, but special circumstances needed to be treated appropriately. For example, if something happened to a player's health or condition. As a result, the referee still asked.

"I know, but I only have so little health remaining. Is there any point in continuing?" Ye Xiu said.

"Can't you.... Do that something?" The referee was reserved. He felt too embarrassed to say heal himself.

"Haha, it's fine. I did a 1v3! I should give the other players a chance!" Ye Xiu said and continued to walk down from the stage. This move could only be deemed as a forfeit. There weren't any other penalizations.

The referee stood there in a daze.

"1v3? When did he 1v3? Did he accidentally miscount?"

How puzzling! The screen in the stadium showed the scoreboard for the group arena. The referee took a glance and nearly coughed blood.

From this meticulous scoreboard, it could clearly be seen that Lord Grim had won against Life Extinguisher.

As a result, in theory, Ye Xiu did a 1v3. That was certainly true. Xiao Shiqin had left the stage in that confrontation!

But who didn't know the circumstances? Xiao Shiqin had used up all his mana. The two hadn't done anything to each other. Xiao Shiqin just typed GG and left. This type of victory counted as a statistic, but how could the player be so bold as to actually count it as one?

1v3? That counts as a 1v3?

Chapter 1025: Unexpected

After completing a 1v3, Ye Xiu came offstage. Fortunately, these words had only been spoken to the referee. If the whole stadium had heard him, the wind from the boos could probably directly blow Ye Xiu out of the building.

Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang left the player booths at almost exactly the same time. Naturally, they also reached their seats in their respective team areas at around the same time.

Those on Happy's side naturally showed Ye Xiu a level of respect normally reserved for heroes, but what about Excellent Era? Tao Xuan was extremely gloomy. Yet, he still had to pat Sun Xiang on the back and console him. "Not bad. You were only off by a tiny bit."

Indeed!

0.03%

Wasn't that just a tiny bit? Yet, this small bit had been the difference between heaven and hell. Sun Xiang felt infinitely conflicted, and could only stare at Team Happy's side. In regards to the boss's words of comfort, he said nothing, only nodding his head before sitting alone to the side.

"We have to win the next round!" At this moment, Tao Xuan gave a desperate command. Even though they were a well-known and experienced team with all kinds of knowledge in coping with difficult situations, Sun Xiang had been defeated by Ye Xiu. This wasn't as simple as an ace player losing a match. Ye Xiu had always had an unusual effect on Excellent Era.

Although Excellent Era was still clearly in the lead, the entire atmosphere of the stadium had changed after Ye Xiu's victory. All the Excellent Era fans had become uncharacteristically silent, as had the previously prideful and arrogant Sun Xiang.

After warning the next player to go on stage, Tao Xuan once again glanced over towards Happy's side, his heart sinking at what he saw.

Sun Zheping!

Surprisingly, Happy's fifth player in the group arena was actually Sun Zheping.

Tao Xuan glanced at Xiao Shiqin, someone he relied heavily on. Prior to the competition, when they were deciding their lineup, the vice captain had guessed that Sun Zheping wouldn't come onstage during the group arena.

As a first-generation God, Sun Zheping would obviously receive a lot of media attention after suddenly joining Happy. Many reporters present were looking for an opportunity to interview him.

With Sun Zheping's personality, he obviously wouldn't cover up his hand injury. He calmly informed the reporters of his current situation. Thus, Xiao Shiqin's had assessed the situation and reached the conclusion that Sun Zheping would only be able to play in one of the rounds, either the group arena or the team competition, in the match against Excellent Era.

After all, the difficulty in facing Excellent Era couldn't be compared to that of other teams. Unless Sun Zheping decisely forfeited the round when the tides of the battle turned, his hands would definitely have to weather an enormous amount of strain. If he appeared in both the group arena and the team competition, the burden would really be too heavy for him to bear.

Except, he was an extremely strong player. This could be easily seen in the few matches in which he had appeared on stage before. As a result, Xiao Shiqin had believed that he would definitely conserve his strength during the group arena, and instead come out during the more important team competition.

However, Sun Zheping was actually Happy's last player in the group arena. This was very unexpected in Xiao Shiqin's eyes. In this position, if the previous players fell behind, a huge burden would be placed on Sun Zheping's shoulders. Like right now, he would have to face two players back-to-back. Regardless of whether he won or lost, after facing this kind of strain, would he still be able to compete in the team round?

"Could it be that the reports by the media were false?" Tao Xuan wondered.

"That's not likely ..." Xiao Shiqin replied. He had entered the Alliance at a time when the Hundred Blossoms duo, Zhang Jiale and Sun Zheping, had been at its peak. Thus, he had a good understanding of this God. This kind of scheming behavior outside of a match wasn't in line with Sun Zheping's personality at all. In Xiao Shiqin's eyes, this man was the type of person who wouldn't hide his true circumstances. Even if he made a mistake, he was the type of person to face it head on like a real man instead of trying to pretend it didn't happen. To make a big deal out of something like a minor hand injury really didn't seem like something he would do.

These years of retirement would be enough enough for him to change his temperament. Yet, seeing his performance on stage, he seemed just as fierce, wild, and untamed as before.

In light of these circumstances, there was only one plausible explanation: Sun Zheping would not be appearing in the team competition.

Then, who would be appearing in the team competition?

In this way, Excellent Era's lineup for the team round would be disrupted. Xiao Shiqin had no idea that Sun Zheping, the definitive number two player in Happy who could even be called Ye Xiu's equal, would actually not be appearing in the team competition? This was actually as unexpected as one not bringing a Cleric to the team competition!

In any case, the lineup for the team competition had long since been decided. There was no way to change it now. Luckily, he would be able to give the other players instructions during the team competition. When the time came to battle, he would simply have to make adjustments based on the situation! Xiao Shiqin took a deep breath, stopping his train of analyses and conjectures. He turned back to calmly watch the match.

From Team Happy, Sun Zheping stepped onto stage.

Excellent Era sent out Shen Jian, a Striker player.

This was likely the only group arena match today in which Happy appeared to be the stronger contender on paper.

Sun Zheping was a former God. Although he had retired for many years, it was due to an injury, not because his condition was slipping. Zhang Jiale, who had been a player of the same generation as him, was still lively on stage. If not for the hand injury, Sun Zheping shouldn't be any worse than Zhang Jiale was now, so he should still be at the same level of an All-Star.

What about Excellent Era's Shen Jian then? In Excellent Era, he could probably only be considered average.

Before Sun Xiang came to Excellent Era, when Excellent Era's troop arrangements during the team competition were relatively stable, the lineup was made up of Ye Xiu's Battle Mage, Su Mucheng's Launcher, Liu Hao's Spellblade, Guo Yang's Qi Master, and Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric. He Ming's Elementalist was usually their sixth player.

Shen Jian could be considered their substitute player. Depending on who their opponents were, he would sometimes have a chance to go onstage.　

After Ye Xiu left, Excellent Era was relegated. Right afterwards, both Liu Hao and He Ming were traded for Xiao Shiqin, and Guo Yang left soon after. Of Excellent Era's original lineup, only Su Mucheng and Zhang Jiaxing remained. As a player with a decent amount of strength and battle experience, Shen Jian also naturally rose in the food chain, joining the main roster.

Excellent Era was a powerhouse team. Being able to rise to the position of a substitute player showed that Shen Jian already possessed an impressive amount of skill. In a weaker team, he might even be considered a strong member. However, in the face of Sun Zheping, this kind of player was evidently still not enough. Right now, the only thing that made people worry was that Sun Zheping had retired due to an injury, before suddenly appearing in the scene once more after so many years. It was said that he still hadn't entirely recovered. Then, when all was said and done, how much strength did this player truly have left? His previous performances could be considered powerful, but Excellent Era's level was not the same as those other teams. Shen Jian was previously only a sub for the team, and even now, he was just a normal player on the main roster. If he was tossed in a team like Mysterious Fantasy or Jade Dynasty, he might even become their core player!

In the face of this kind of player, would Sun Zheping still be able to showcase the same kind of overpowering performances he had before?

This competition left the audience in this kind of suspense. In this match, the attention wouldn't be focused on Excellent Era's player. In the spotlight was Sun Zheping, the former number one Berserker.

Yes, the topic had once again become focused on Sun Zheping. Team Happy ... why were they always casually tossed to the side?

Chapter 1026: Meeting Force with Force

The audience still hadn't recovered from the spectacular fight between Ye Xiu and Sun Xiang. The next round had begun, but the stadium was still silent.

However, this wouldn't affect the players on stage. When they entered the player booths, the players and characters became one. This was the mindset that they currently put themselves in.

Shen Jian's character was a Striker, which was a purely offensive type character similar to Sun Zheping's Berserker. The Striker's weapon was their body, so it had the shortest attack range of the 24 classes. However, this class represented the principle that a shorter weapon was more dangerous. When fighting in close quarters combat, their attack speed was ranked the fastest among the 24 classes. Strikers, Assassins, and Grapplers were known as the Nightmare Trio when it came to close combat.

When the match started, both sides showcased the straightforwardness of their respective classes. They didn't move strategically, but headed straight for the center of the map to fight.

Speaking of character strength, Excellent Era held a clear advantage. Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep didn't have any Silver equipment at all; all of his equipment was orange. This could be considered a disadvantage because all of his stats were known by the opponent. Shen Jian could carry out the fight according to Another Summer of Sleep's stats and bonuses. Although Shen Jian's Striker was a sub Excellent Era, Excellent Era was still a powerhouse team. The subs wouldn't have characters too different in strength compared to the characters of the starting roster. Shen Jian had a set of ten Silver equipment, a number enough to make most players drool. In reality, a powerhouse team might not have a small number of Silver equipment even for substitute characters. The real difference between the God-level characters lay in the quality. This was clearly related to the the distribution of a team's resources. It went without saying that the ace and core characters would get prioritized when it came to using these resources, and naturally, the equipment given to these core characters were much more suited to the players' playstyles.

Shen Jian was promoted to a starter in this season, so his character also received more attention. Since he was better than he was last season, he couldn't wait to use his upgraded character to show a brilliant performance. However, this could only happen after they cleared the Challenger League.

There was a wide gap between the characters' stats, but Sun Zheping showed no trace of being courteous. When the two met, he immediately made the first move. Another Summer of Sleep swung the greatsword in his hand and launched a Collapsing Mountain.

Due to a Striker's limited attack range, they often failed to attack first. However, this didn't mean that they would be stuck in a passive state. Shen Jian's response was very tough. He activated Reinforced Iron Bones, and rushed towards Another Summer of Sleep's Collapsing Mountain with swinging fists.

Sun Zheping? He was famous, but this did not mean Shen Jian would be afraid of him. They were both pro players, so even if his opponent was a God, his opponent's strength wouldn't in another league. If he turned soft every time he faced someone of a higher level, how could he even participate in a match? As a new main roster player, Shen Jian didn't have many chances to show himself. Since he got to meet a figure like Sun Zheping in the match against Happy, it seemed like a good opportunity to reveal himself.

The number one Berserker? Very well, I'll use an even more fierce and crazy way to beat you.

Shen Jian thought to himself and then controlled his character to charge forward.

Reinforced Iron Bones increased his character's physical defense, but more importantly, it also granted Super Armor.

Super Armor made the character immune to all forms of CC apart from grabs. In this way, although he faced a cut from the opponent, it didn't affect his Striker's advance at all. He only lost a bit of health from this attack, but his attack continued as normal. Shen Jian neither avoided nor blocked the incoming attacks, and pushed forward with Reinforced Iron Bones. This revealed his intention to fight straightforwardly.

Sun Zheping unexpectedly reacted extremely fast. He leapt up and cancelled Collapsing Mountain in midair. Another Summer of Sleep then swung his sword. It seemed like an Upward Slash, but this blow from Upward Slash seemed to release magical waves as if ripping apart the air.

This was a low-level Spellblade skill, Wave Wheel Slasher, which used a magic boundary to seal a target before spinning and slicing the target. All four swordsmen classes typically put at least one point into it. They wanted it for its Super Armor piercing effects.

Shen Jian saw this, but didn't have any other options available. He could only choose to retreat. However, Sun Zheping had reason to not let him escape. After Another Summer of Sleep's jump, he landed and reached out to grab Shen Jian's Fighter. This was a Berserker grab Soul-Devouring Crimson Grip.

The Striker jumped back as Shen Jian chose to give way again.

Another Summer of Sleep wasn't in a hurry to rush up this time and let out a Sword Draw instead.

Shen Jian's Striker was still under the effects of Reinforced Iron Bones, so he wouldn't be beat back by this blow. He rushed forward to smash the sword's light with his body, and swung his fists once more.

However, Another Summer of Sleep held his sword in front of his chest and attacked with the Blade Master's Lunge. 'Tu-tu!' The two blows landed on the Striker. It was true that a Striker buffed with Reinforced Iron Bone wouldn't be affected by the skill effects, but the sword was pointed at his chest. If he continued to advance, wouldn't his character be pierced by the blade? Although this was a game, it couldn't be too illogical. The two lunges held up the person like a stick, and managed to postpone the incoming force of Shen Jian's Striker.

Shen Jian was unwilling to give up; there was no big deal in losing a bit of health after activating Reinforced Iron Bones. However, it would be a mistake to not seize the opportunity to attack. The Striker that was stabbed twice continued to push forward tenaciously. This time, Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep retreated. He jumped back repeatedly without turning around.

"Where are you going!" Shen Jian cried out in his head and forced his character forward even faster. The Striker used Straight Punch to try to close the gap.

Who would have thought that after Another Summer of Sleep's two backwards jumps, he would take out the sword behind his back? As Shen Jian rushed forward, the Great Sword thrust out and slashed straight down.

Demon-Slaying Slash!

Apart from its outstanding damage, Demon-Slaying Slash could also lower the target's defense. When this skill was fully upgraded, a blow could reduce the target's defense by 30% for eight seconds.

All of this couldn't be avoided when one activated Reinforced Iron Bone. Even if it was activated, the damage from the skill was rather heartbreaking. There seemed to be no convenient chance to attack, so this Demon-Slaying Slash caused Shen Jian to hesitate a bit before finally choosing to dodge.

At this point, even commentators like Pan Lin and Li Yibo were able to clearly see through Shen Jian's hesitation, let alone Ye Xiu. This guy was set on fighting resolutely and tough, but obviously that wasn't his original style. So when he fought with truly tough players like Sun Zheping, he backed down. No one understood why he activated Reinforced Iron Bones and wasted the skill's effect in the end.

Wasting Reinforced Iron Bone was a huge mistake. This was because when Strikers used this skill, they would usually neglect defense and receive a large amount of damage. If a player couldn't find an opportunity to beat the opponent enough to cough up litres of blood in this situation, what was the point of even using this skill? Shen Jian not only had no reason to, he was literally selling his blood too. No, it wasn't even selling blood. By selling blood, there was some profit to be made. Shen Jian was purely giving out blood.

Pan Lin and Li Yibo gave a thorough analysis of Shen Jian's terrible opener. Judging from this aspecte, there was quite some distance between Shen Jian and the top Gods. After all, Pan Lin and Li Yibo could comment on it with such ease. When Ye Xiu was on stage before, the two kept on falling into traps. It's obvious that they weren't skilled enough to the point that they wouldn't even be able to finish a single level of Contra if not given 30 lives.

By failing to grasp an opportunity with Reinforced Iron Bones and taking a lot of damage, Shen Jian knew how badly he fought and immediately became restless. Was Sun Zheping the kind of person to give his opponent any chance to catch his breath? His attacks grew stronger blow by blow. He waved his greatsword around like a windmill and slashed crazily.

Apart from "No wonder he's the Number One Berserker", "As expected from the Number One Berserker", and "Look, this is the power of the Number One Berserker", the two commentators had nothing else to say. They couldn't help but refrain from giving any blunt comments on Sun Zheping's performance. They had fallen into too many traps today, if they fell into another one again, all 30 of their lives would be used up.

On the Excellent Era bench, Tao Xuan's expression was extremely gloomy.

Shen Jian's resolute attitude before he went on stage caused him to feel very much at peace. Although he gave a must-win command, there would always be wins and losses in a match. Tao Xuan obviously knew about this principle. The must-win command was a type of resolution, so the player would feel pressured as well as motivated. Whether it was a win or a loss, Tao Xuan would never bring out the must-win command to criticize a player.

In addition, he clearly knew about Sun Zheping's skill. If Shen Jian couldn't take him down, he wouldn't say much, but he was losing in such an unsightly manner. Tao Xuan was angry at how Shen Jian was trying to appear fierce even though he was weak inside. If he fought like this, it would look better if he had just typed 'GG' the moment he stepped on stage!

Unfortunately, no one could point out anything in this match, and Shen Jian continued to fight with fear. Using a fierce and crazy way to defeat Sun Zheping? This plan was long forgotten. An alarmed Shen Jian even forgot to win at this point. He was too busy thinking about how he could survive as if this were an apocalypse.

Shen Jian lost without any turning points or any glimmers of hope. His performance was worse than Tang Rou's and Mo Fan's. Even though the two couldn't take down much of Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher's health, at least they had a few moments of brilliance that belonged to them. They used their efforts to clearly express their intentions.

Shen Jian? He had intentions when he went on stage, but it was smashed to pieces in two blows by Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep. His thoughts were rather weak.

"Shen Jian was obviously unprepared." Pan Lin said.

"Yeah, he might have expected Sun Xiang to finish everything, so he wouldn't have needed to go on stage." Coach Li expressed his agreement.

"He probably didn't think he would be fighting a strong opponent like Sun Zheping."

"It was quite unwise of him to try to match Sun Zheping with force."

"Yes, Han Wenqing is the only Striker in all of Glory that could use such a method to fight Sun Zheping."

"Even though Sun Zheping retired many years ago, he shouldn't be underestimated like this!"

"Yes!"

"Too careless."

The match ended with this.

Winner: Team Happy, Sun Zheping, Another Summer of Sleep.

Chapter 1027: Seize the Competition

Shen Jian walked off stage in a daze. The Excellent Era fans booed due to their discontent for the first time this match. Previously, Xiao Shiqin's 1v3 didn't need to be said. All the boos had been meant for Happy. Afterwards, Qiu Fei and Sun Xiang lost, but the crowd didn't react as harshly. The performances from Qiu Fei and Sun Xiang weren't bad. The fans didn't even look at the results. They also cared about the process.

Shen Jian's performance clearly didn't make them feel satisfied. It was just that compared to the boos towards Happy, the boos from the Excellent Ea fans were still much more polite. Amidst these boos, there was even some applause to encourage their team's players.

Shen Jian returned to the bench with his head drooped down. Tao Xuan patted his back and said a few consoling words before telling him to go rest. Tao Xuan was still the boss of a veteran team. He naturally wouldn't be so childish as to lose his temper like Jade Dynasty's Xiao Jie.

Excellent Era's final player was about to come on stage. Everyone stretched their necks waiting for this person to go up. Whether it was intentional or not, Tao Xuan stole a glance at Happy. On Excellent Era's side, Su Mucheng stood up.

As expected…...

Chen Guo thought to herself.

No one mentioned the possible conflict. Would Su Mucheng represent Excellent Era today? And now the truth had finally been revealed.

Su Mucheng glanced at Happy's side. Her gaze didn't expose too many things. She turned around and walked towards the player booth. On the other hand, Tao Xuan suddenly turned his head to look at Happy. No, to be more accurate, he looked at Ye Xiu. His eyes seemed to be filled with delight as if he were making fun of him.

What's that supposed to mean?

Chen Guo didn't understand. She turned her head to look at Ye Xiu and saw an expression she had never seen before on his face. Is that anger?

Yes, anger!

Even after Ye Xiu was kicked out and painted black by Excellent Era, he had always stayed calm. He's angry? Why? Because Su Mucheng was sent out?

Chen Guo felt like that wasn't the reason. Tao Xuan's expression when Su Mucheng went out was probably why Ye Xiu was angry. Chen Guo was still pondering over it, when she saw Ye Xiu stand up and walk over to Excellent Era's bench, to Tao Xuan.

Tao Xuan was still sitting down. He didn't move and simply raised his head slightly. He looked at Team Excellent Era's former captain. They were once good friends, who got to know each other in game. At that time, they were like brothers that had gone to hell and back together. Afterwards, he raised enough money to form a team and he pulled over his brother to become his team's captain. The two gradually stopped calling each other brothers and now, the two had become enemies.

"What's the meaning of this?" Ye Xiu had restrained his anger. He looked at Tao Xuan as calm as ever.

"I hope she'll give a good performance." Tao Xuan smiled, while giving an irrelevant answer.　　

"So it's like that." Ye XIu seemed to have gotten the answer he wanted and returned to his seat.　

Chen Guo really wanted to ask, but... she was too afraid to. Ye Xiu no longer showed any anger like before, but his expression was gloomy. This was also an expression that she had never seen on him before.　

"Calm down." Wei Chen suddenly said.

"Mm." Ye Xiu nodded his head. He didn't argue back or question him. He simply nodded his head, saying that the current him wasn't calm at all.

Ye Xiu wasn't calm?

Chen Guo felt like something must have happened. But what? Chen Guo looked at Wei Chen. She knew that he should know the answer. She used her eyes to tell Wei Chen, he could either die or explain the situation to her.

"Ahem….." Wei Chen was attacked by her glance. He gave a cough and then scooted over.

"Do you know why Su Mucheng was put last?" Wei Chen said.　　

Sure enough, it had to do with Su Mucheng.... Chen Guo thought to herself, but was there some sort of special meaning in it?

"Excellent Era is doubtful of Su Mucheng, but that they can't openly say that. After all, Su Mucheng is very popular. Just look at the crowd's reaction." Wei Chen said.

Yes, the stadium was already cheering. Shen Jian's embarrassing performance didn't wipe out their passionate cheers for Su Mucheng. She was only walking on stage and the crowd was going wild.

"So she's been placed last." Wei Chen said.

"Why?" Chen Guo still didn't understand.

"For one, this is their treat to the fans. If you look at how Excellent Era ordered their line up for the group arena, they planned to finish the group arena with three players, so the chances of Su Mucheng coming out is very small. However, she's at least a part of the line up, showing that they trust her. As for placing her last, that could be explained as a safeguard. This is completely reasonable." Wei Chen said.

"Mm." Chen Guo nodded her head in understanding.

"But if the situation arises and Su Mucheng needs to come out on stage, what then? She carries the burden of Excellent Era winning the group arena. Each and every move of hers will be watched with rapt attention. If she truly has ideas of sandbagging, I'm saying if!!!" Wei Chen said sandbag, Chen Guo's expression changed, so he immediately stressed the word if, "Then if anyone notices it, her reputation... will be completely destroyed."

"F*ck!" Chen Guo suddenly became angry. She shot a death glare over to Excellent Era's side. Unfortunately, no one was looking at her.

"I'm just saying if. Of course, you and I believe that Su Mucheng is a professional so she wouldn't do that. However, in such a sensitive match, even if she doesn't sandbag, if she loses, she'll most likely arouse the suspicions of others. For a match, a first impression holds more weight than the details. Any mistakes she makes could be viewed as sandbagging... so for Su Mucheng, she can only win. She cannot lose. If she loses, she'll be affected negatively." Wei Chen explained everything very thoroughly. After saying this, he put up his guard, making sure that their bold boss wouldn't flip a table over and try to murder someone.

What he didn't expect was that, after he finished explaining, Chen Guo didn't react aggressively like he thought she would. Chen Guo watched as Su Mucheng walked onto the stage; her expression was filled with bitterness.

Su Mucheng didn't want to win this match, but she had no choice but to. What type of conflict was going on inside her?

Chen Guo didn't know if Su Mucheng was aware of Excellent Era's intentions. After hearing Wei Chen's words, she felt like it wasn't really hard to figure that out, but even so, it was thanks to Tao Xuan leaking out such a delighted expression that Ye Xiu and Wei Chen realized it. If not, no matter how shameless the two of them were, they might not have thought much of it.

From this view, Su Mucheng might realize this despicable plan. What would she do to resist?

Would she directly type GG and leave? Use this type of reckless way against Excellent Era's coercion? Even though Chen Guo would feel great if that happened, the aftermath would be very worrying for Su Mucheng. Because the consequences were just like Wei Chen said, a complete loss in reputation. No matter the reason, a pro player was not allowed to violate the competitive integrity of the esport. It was for this reason that Excellent Era dared to treat Su Mucheng this way.

The current Chen Guo couldn't bother with getting angry at Tao Xuan. She also understood why Ye Xiu was so quick to restrain his anger. It was because the person everyone was concerned about was about to face this difficult situation. Was there time to worry for her? Who was in the mood to split their attention towards Tao Xuan?

What would she do?

Seeing Su Mucheng walk on stage and load in her character, Chen Guo's heart leapt to her throat.

Then, the match started. The two characters loaded into the map. Chen Guo watched Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain carefully and finally let out a sigh of relief.

Su Mucheng at least didn't say GG.

The two characters moved. Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep went straight for the center of the map. Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain moved more tactfully and quickly reached a place that Li Yibo called "an excellent sniping spot".

Launchers had the longest range out of all 24 classes. Utilizing the terrain, hiding, and constantly kiting the opponent with long-ranged attacks was the usual strategy, especially against an extremely aggressive player like Sun Zheping. This method of kiting could wear away the opponent's mental state and health. Su Mucheng should be using this method to covertly attack.

This was Coach Li's analysis, but the crowd saw Su Mucheng's Dancing Rain stand up on the wall with her heads held high and the cannon on her shoulders. She didn't seem to have any intentions of hiding. She completely exposed herself on the high grounds and started firing at Another Summer of Sleep.

Li Yibo's mouth dropped wide open. He had experienced a hundred battles, but this time, he couldn't save himself because Su Mucheng's slap to his face was too quick. As soon as he finished saying that she would hide, she stood up heroically and started firing. This pose was less like taking the initiative and more like shouting out loud "I'm attacking!!"

Chen Guo hadn't given up on listening to the commentators. When she saw the huge difference between Su Mucheng's play and the commentator's analysis, her heart suddenly thumped.

Su Mucheng didn't directly go so far as to say GG, but was she planning on boldly sandbagging to slap Excellent Era's face?　　

Artillery fire instantly covered Chen Guo's mood. The heavy suppression made it impossible for the aggressive Sun Zheping to charge at her directly.

Under the pursuit of artillery fire, Another Summer of Sleep ran behind a wall, planning his next step, when an enormous force lifted him up from behind. Another Summer of Sleep was overturned along with that wall from Su Mucheng's barrage.

"Excellent Era... are they planning on fighting force with force against Sun Zheping?" In the crowd, Team Tiny Herb's three pro players could see the pros and cons of that strategy.

Chapter 1028: It Ends Here

Su Mucheng's performance caused many of her die hard Excellent Era fans forget to cheer because this kind of strategy was indeed very different from her usual style.

When Ye Xiu was still on the team, Su Mucheng's Launcher had always played a supportive role. Her character's coordination with One Autumn Leaf had always been very distinct.

After Ye Xiu left the team, his successor, Sun Xiang, didn't have this same kind of implicit understanding with Su Mucheng. Dancing Rain's position on the team also appeared awkward for a time.

Fortunately, Su Mucheng rapidly adjusted herself, transforming from a support player into one of the main damage dealers. Yet even so, her style still wasn't as aggressive and unyielding as what she was showing today.

In reality, not being aggressive and unyielding was something that many people often accused female players of. Team Misty Rain's Captain Chu Yunxiu had constantly been flamed by critics because of this, to the point that it was considered one of her trademark weaknesses.

Except now, Su Mucheng was actually showcasing this kind of tough playstyle, making many people feel taken aback. Even a player like Sun Zheping had been suppressed to the point that he had no way to directly attack. It was obvious how intense her firepower had to be to reach this point.

Sun Zheping's Another Summer of Sleep and the wall behind him were both overturned, but Dancing Rain's offensive didn't stop for a moment. Only now could it be seen that Su Mucheng's original positioning of Dancing Rain on high ground wasn't to conceal her character to discreetly launch a sneak attack. Instead, it was done in order to obtain a wider field of view so as to allow her Launcher's attacks to cover a larger area. Attacking from afar allowed her to utilize her strength to the maximum.

Another Summer of Sleep still hadn't climbed out of the pile of rubble from the broken wall. A Stinger had long since been launched and had split in midair, the fragments raining downwards. This skill shot out at an arc. Although the distance the projectile could travel wasn't actually that long, Dancing Rain was currently towering above all on the high ground. The range of this skill had been increased a lot because of this.

The Stinger exploded above the ruins, turning the area into a sea of fire in the blink of an eye. Another Summer of Sleep suddenly rose, sweeping off the fragments of stone on his body. Looking at him, it really felt like a dramatic change.

However, Su Mucheng didn't let up at all. Dancing Rain had long since finished charging up a Laser Rifle. In the instant that Another Summer of Sleep burst forth, the laser beam was also released. Another Summer of Sleep's awe-inspiring pose didn't last even a second before he was pushed back by the Laser Rifle, sliding quite a distance. His feet had carved out two parallel grooves as he traveled.

At this moment, the stadium finally recovered and exploded in applause.

Facing Sun Zheping, a player who was defined by his aggressive playstyle, Su Mucheng was actually able to answer with aggressive plays of her own! Furthermore, her opponent didn't even have an opportunity to respond! If they didn't applaud for this kind of brilliant performance, what would they applaud for?

In comparison, Shen Jian's previous performance, which had been like a sheep in wolf's clothing, was unbearable. Except at this moment, who was even still thinking about his clumsy display? It was only brought up because the commentators used it as a comparison when they were looking for topics to talk about. After that, they went back to speaking about Su Mucheng's beautiful performance.

It really isn't easy ...

Even Sun Zheping, who was currently onstage, felt a sense of sorrow. He had lost many matches before, but there had been very very few in which he had absolutely no opportunity to advance on his opponent. Today, the beautiful Su Mucheng had set her heart on showcasing her power! Honestly, when he saw Su Mucheng go onstage, Sun Zheping had had some doubts about the quality of the match. Right now, since he was helping Happy compete, he obviously wouldn't shy away from any topics or problems regarding Excellent Era. He knew that Su Mucheng was in a very tangled situation. In this kind of match, would a beautiful girl still be able to display her full strength? In his heart, there was originally a question mark.

Now, however, the question mark was smashed to pieces. Su Mucheng had fought to the point that he had no way to push forward. This was practically exceeding her full strength.

However, although Sun Zheping understood Su Mucheng's inner turmoil, he wouldn't go easy on her during the competition. In his opinion, these were two completely unrelated things. In any case, all he was concerned with was winning the competition. It didn't matter who his opponent was. It didn't matter what the situation looked like. It didn't matter how he felt, or what his state of mind was. On the stage, outside of victory or defeat, there was nothing else ...

If strength wasn't enough, then what about tactics?

No, this was never Sun Zheping's style. It hadn't been many years ago, and it wasn't now. Perhaps there were many people secretly watching, watching to see if Sun Zheping had lost some of his former grandeur after being forced to retire due to an injury. Sun Zheping wanted these people to know that, even if he had a hand injury, even if he could only fight at a high skill level for a few minutes each time, in these trifling minutes, he wouldn't back down. He would press onwards with the same vigor, because that was his style. This was Sun Zheping. The grace and elegance of the Number One Berserker would not fade for any reason. Even if it could only manifest for a few minutes, so be it. In these few minutes, everyone would witness the grace, the beauty, the marvel, the brilliance, the excitement, the delight. This was the way of the Number One Berserker.

Another Summer of Sleep suddenly charged forward. Su Mucheng saw this clearly, immediately firing three Anti-Tank Missiles. Another Summer of Sleep raised his sword, releasing a Whirlwind Strike!

The blade of the sword swung towards the incoming projectile. The flames of the explosion were sliced clean in half by the sword, fluttering harmlessly before dissipating next to his body. One, then another, then the third and final one were all chopped in half by Sun Zheping in an aggressive manner. Another Summer of Sleep continued charging forth with large strides.

Everyone was stupefied. Under this kind of suppressive firepower, he actually still wanted to push forward. This kind of style was completely unreasonable. It was absolutely crazy!

Had any other player acted this way, they would likely have been seen as courting death. However, Sun Zheping and his Another Summer of Sleep pushed onwards step by step, beating into the hearts of every person watching. All they saw was this pro player and his character, possessing unyielding determination, tenaciously push forward. Step by step, they never stopped to rest. Perhaps he would die on this road, but never would he even think of compromising.

"This guy!!" At this moment, all of Happy's players felt incredibly moved.

Throwing the game?

If anyone watching this match still entertained these ideas, they really should be dragged out of the stadium and executed by a firing squad a hundred times over.**

This confrontation was one that required full commitment from both sides. There wouldn't be anyone throwing the match, nor would either side back down. Everything this stage represented, everything it embodied, all of it came down to the two players' Glory. At this moment, everything else became truly irrelevant.

Victory! This was what both sides were trying so hard to achieve.

Everyone present was influenced by the players passion. They too forgot everything. At this moment, all their attention was drawn to the confrontation unfolding before their eyes. Their only concern was who would attain victory. Not one person even considered the many consequences that would arise from either side's victory.

Who would win? Who would lose?

No one blinked, all eyes focused on the two characters on stage. Another Summer of Sleep — a character name that sounded extremely languid and laid back. No one knew what was going through Sun Zheping's mind when he came up with a name that had nothing in common with his playstyle. But now, the languidly-named Another Summer of Sleep had finished his Long March.*** Now, he had finally arrived in front of Dancing Rain, and he could finally sink his teeth into the one who had hindered his journey, the opponent who had lined his road with a thousand different obstacles and dangers.

However, it was also at this moment that Dancing Rain finally took a step back ...

Sun Zheping's strike only struck air. He stared blankly.

When he recovered his senses a moment later, he unexpectedly laughed.

He had only been thinking of charging forward, and he forgot. He forgot that Su Mucheng wasn't him. In these circumstances, Sun Zheping would stay and collide his opponent head on. But Su Mucheng, she temporarily retreated. This was something that Sun Zheping would never choose to do. Yet, it indeed was the smarter choice.

I'm going to lose ...

Sun Zheping knew this in the bottom of his heart. His opponent had fought more intelligently, whereas he had perhaps only been recklessly acting without thought all along.

It really was a pity because he wouldn't have many more opportunities to play so recklessly, without a regard for the rules. He really missed the old days, when he so recklessly fight onstage however much he wanted.

Dancing Rain retreated, and in the blink of an eye a Satellite Beam descended from the sky. Another Summer of Sleep had finally reached the last thread of his life, collapsing onto the ground. He brought with him Sun Zheping's profound regret, not only for this match, but for his entire Glory career. Even when he could only compete for a few minutes, he still was that Sun Zheping. Yet, such a short amount of time truly couldn't satisfy him ...

The group arena had finally concluded. Su Mucheng was victorious. Excellent Era finally won one point.

Sun Zheping walked out of the player booth first. The entire stadium was silent. Gradually, however, sounds of applause rang out, eventually spreading to the entire stadium.

In the past, Team Happy had only received booing and derision. Now, they were suddenly being applauded?

Of course not.

At this moment, they were applauding was for Sun Zheping. Although he had lost, through this one match, every person had experienced and appreciated his unyielding fortitude. Why did this kind of player have to suffer the misfortune of a hand injury, which was deadly to pro players? No one could voice the regret they fell. The audience could only send their respect and blessings through applause.

Afterwards, the applause was directed towards Su Mucheng, who had obtained victory for the team. The audience waited for Su Mucheng to exit the player booth. However, they discovered that Dancing Rain hadn't immediately logged off after winning. At this moment, she was still standing onstage.

"My time with Excellent Era ends here."

In the competition channel which had yet to be closed, this sentence suddenly appeared. Before anyone could react, Dancing Rain logged out, disappearing from the stage. Immediately afterwards, Su Mucheng exited the player booth.

For a moment, that inexplicable sentence caused the audience's applause to become scattered. Soon after, under the gaze of everyone present in the stadium, Su Mucheng walked off of the stage towards the team benches. When she passed the Excellent Era bench area, she didn't stop, walking all the way over to Happy's area before sitting down.

The entire stadium exploded. Amidst the commotion it was impossible to make sense of anything. However, Su Mucheng didn't care at all. At this moment, she felt more calm and at ease than she had in a year and a half. She no longer felt any inner turmoil, nor any burden weighing her down. Everything had returned to the beginning, when she had followed her brother and Ye Xiu as they struggled to make a living through video games. It had been hard, it had been exhausting, but they had been content.

Su Mucheng felt tears begin to form in her eyes. She quickly buried her face in the shoulder of the person sitting next to her.

"Leave the rest to me!" That person said.

"Okay...." Su Mucheng agreed. In reality, she had never wanted the spotlight for herself ...

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

** This is the literal translation of 枪毙一百遍. The translators do not condone violence in any form.

*** 万里长征 refers to the Long March that the Communist Party of China took from October 1934 to October 1935 in order to escape from the Chinese Nationalist Party. Literally, it can be translated as "thousand mile expedition," although the Long March reportedly spanned over 5600 miles. This event would eventually cement Mao Zedong's ascent to power.

--Veriquity

Chapter 1029: Starting Lineup

The crowd couldn't calm down. How deep was the friendship between Ye Xiu and Su Mucheng? Because Ye Xiu had always kept a low-profile, his fans didn't know. As a result, Su Mucheng publicly announcing her split with Excellent Era right after the group arena ended and then sitting at Happy's bench was simply too astonishing.

Why?

The crowd clamored noisily, but no one could answer the question. Pan Lin and Li Yibo were also dumbstruck by this outrageous conduct. For a moment, they didn't know what to say.　　

"Su Mucheng.... Su Mucheng..." Pan Lin was the first to regain his composure. He wanted to explain this crazy action, but when the words reached his mouth, he couldn't find the right words to describe his thoughts. He had never encountered such a situation before. No matter how experienced he maybe as a commentator, he was no better than anyone else at the moment.

"Does the Alliance have any rules regarding this?" After stumbling on his words for awhile, he suddenly asked a question.

"What do you mean?' Li Yibo asked.

"The... the..." Pan Lin wanted to say "The rule not permitting players to sit at another team's bench", but he had second thoughts. Su Mucheng publicly announcing her split and defecting to the enemy side had never happened before, but if you said sitting at another team's bench, that wasn't anything new. Sometimes, the players on the two teams were good friends off-stage, so they went over to each other's bench to make some small talk. However, doing that was a somewhat sensitive subject, so there was usually a special precondition required for it to happen.

Su Mucheng was definitely an exception though. She was touching on the "sensitive" subject that everyone was worried about. She displayed this "sensitive" subject for everyone to see.

What should be said for this conduct? Pan Lin was unable to say what he wanted to say. His co-caster, Li Yibo, racked his brains and finally squeezed out a few words: "In any case, Su Mucheng's conduct is inappropriate. No matter what the reason is, such an action is a heavy blow to her team and her fans. It doesn't matter if there's some sort of conflict between her and Excellent Era, this definitely isn't the way to resolve it."

Li Yibo was clearly saying empty words. For Su Mucheng to act in such a way, who would believe she had a good relationship with her team? Su Mucheng and Excellent Era definitely had some sort of conflict and it clearly wasn't a small one. The two of them weren't needed to analyze something so obvious. Everyone in the crowd knew. They were wondering what the conflict was to make Su Mucheng defect to Team Happy.

Was it related to Ye Xiu?

Many people thought that was the reason. After all, Ye Xiu had the closest relationship with Su Mucheng among those in Team Happy.

Opinions differed.

The crowd discussed with each other. The reporters were also looking at their data and racked their brains to analyze the reasons. However, the match was still going to continue. The team competition came after the group arena. The break time was a bit longer than usual. The employees nervously prepped the player booths. The six players participating in the team competition might be different than the five players participating in the group arena, so adjustments needed to be made to the setups in the player booths.

The players competing in the match also had some free time during their rest time. They could go to the restroom and so on. However, no one left. On Excellent Era's side, the color of Tao Xuan's face had already turned purple. He hadn't expected Su Mucheng to actually do something like that.　　

Her way of splitting with the team was too crazy. There was no precedent. The media must be very interested in digging deeper. Once they started digging, they might find a lot of problems, which had been covered up by Tao Xuan the entire time. Because once this fuse was set, it might explode in front of the public. How could Tao Xuan be calm? As for Su Mucheng defecting to Happy, he wasn't concerned about that issue because he knew long ago that this would happen. When Su Mucheng firmly refused to renew or extend her contract, he already knew it was inevitable. Unlike the public, he had a clear understanding of the relationship between Su Mucheng and Ye Xiu. When he renounced Ye Xiu, he had already been prepared to let go of Su Mucheng. Her departure wasn't unexpected, but her way of doing so was.

Tao Xuan had no idea how to handle the situation in front of him. Su Mucheng's actions affected the team. They still needed to play in the team competition. Their hearts couldn't waver right now.　

Tao Xuan was busy trying to stabilize the team, while Happy was jubilant. If one only looked at the atmosphere surrounding the two teams, no one would believe that Excellent Era had just won the group arena by one point. It looked like Excellent Era was losing by a lot.

The crowd clamored noisily for however long the break time was. Everyone was concerned about the issue of Su Mucheng from start to finish. They practically forgot about the following team competition. They still hadn't figured it out, when it was announced that the team competition would be starting soon.

On Excellent Era's side, with Tao Xuan personally stabilizing the situation, the team had calmed down. As teammates, they also knew that Su Mucheng would leave at the end of the season. As a result, they were similar to Tao Xuan. They were mainly surprised by her way of doing so.

"In this team competition, don't give them any opportunities! Good luck everyone!" Tao Xuan clapped his hands in encouragement. The other worries in his heart had been buried for now. In any case, winning this match was what was most important.

"Okay, let's go!" Sun Xiang had lost to Ye Xiu in the group arena, but it looked like he had readjusted his mindset. As the team captain, he walked at the front, leading their team competition players to the player booths.

Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, Qiu Fei, Shen Jian, Zhang Jiaxin. Sixth player - Wang Ze.

The lineups for the team competition had been fixed ahead of time, so they couldn't be changed at the last moment. From this, it could be seen that Excellent Era's number three All-Star player, Su Mucheng, hadn't been a part of the team competition lineup. It could be seen how doubtful Tao Xuan was of Su Mucheng. In the team competition, he didn't have any method of forcing Su Mucheng to play seriously, so he might as well just kick her to the side.

"Are you ready?" On Happy's side, Ye Xiu asked. His words weren't aimed at the entire team, but at a certain someone.

"Yes." A player on the bench nodded his head and stood up. At this moment, the Happy players were being introduced.

Wu Chen. Launcher. Dawn Rifle.

As the introduction echoed throughout the stadium, everyone in Team Excellent Era halted their footsteps.

It was not just them. When the crowd heard this name, they were also stunned.　　

Whether it was Excellent Era or Happy, those who had been following the matches closely were all familiar with this name. But Wu Chen... this person was undoubtedly a part of Team Happy's registered players, but in the offline tournament, he had never made an appearance. And now in such a crucial match like the finals, he would be making his first appearance?

There was no applause from the crowd.

He was a player that had never gone on stage and he wasn't a player that everyone had been looking forward to seeing. His sudden appearance made everyone puzzled rather than expectant. Even the commentators, Pan Lin and Lin Yibo, were crazily ridiculing Happy. It could be considered as them venting their emotions from not knowing what to do about Su Mucheng's actions. They did all sorts of analyses on Wu Chen and most of their conclusions were unfavorable.

"Happy is in a difficult position against Excellent Era, so they thought of putting out a surprise player. However, this player has no experience of what it's like on stage. Suddenly throwing him out in the finals is too rash. Going too far is just as bad as not enough!" Li Yibo concluded.

And at the same time, the players on both sides were walking towards their player booths.

Team Happy. Their players were Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi, and Wu Chen.

Wei Chen and Sun Zheping, the two veterans, weren't participating in the team competition. Sun Zheping didn't participate much because of his hand injury. He couldn't play for too much without his injury flaring up. As for Wei Chen, his age was a reality that couldn't be avoided. His energy was limited. It wasn't obvious in the game. When he pulled an all-nighter and killed monsters, he seemed to be just as energetic as the younger players, but in an intense high-level competition, his energy clearly dropped faster than the others. Happy had fought several intense matches in the offline tournament. Wei Chen had to put in a lot of effort in them. The longer they took, the more tired he felt.

In their plan for the group arena, Wei Chen was supposed to face Sun Xiang. This difficult matchup would certainly put a lot of stress on Wei Chen, so in their plan for the finals, they had Wei Chen participate in the group arena, but not in the team competition. In the end, even though Wei Chen didn't face Sun Xiang, he still had to face an All-Star like Xiao Shiqin. Their original thinking behind the arrangement was still put to use.

Apart from that, there was Luo Ji, who wouldn't be appearing this match. His skill level was rather low, so they couldn't let him play in such a critical match.

The biggest surprise was Wu Chen.

Through this analysis, Wu Chen's appearance might not have been intended as a surprise, but rather out of helplessness.

Wu Chen quietly walked among Team Happy's players. He wasn't aware of the discussion going on because of him. As a player from Team Everlasting that had been a part of the Challenger League for several years, it had been a long time since Wu Chen had received any attention. Even when he was in the pro scene, he had never gotten so much attention.

In the eyes of the pros, his skill level wasn't top-notch.

But he had a dream and he relentlessly pursued it. Wu Chen had been ready for this match for a long time, perhaps too long. He had always been hoping for Team Everlasting to stride past this obstacle and return to the Alliance. Team Everlasting was no longer there, but the dream in his heart had never died.

Get through the Challenger League and return to the Alliance!

Chapter 1030: A Childish Annoyance?

The two teams of players had already neatly filed onto the stage.

The team competition was like an opera. It was a life or death situation. Who won and who lost would decide the fate of both teams. Living meant heaven, while dying meant another year of hell. Yet for Excellent Era, this would be an even deeper hell. Spending two years a row stewing in the Challenger League? Even Excellent Era would be embarrassed to call themselves a powerhouse if that happened. Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, they were both All-Star players and top players in the Alliance. Both of them had sacrificed a year because they had been looking towards Excellent Era's future, but if the future was another year in the Challenger League, it was hard to say if either of them would be patient.

We have to win!

This kind of conviction wasn't something Tao Xuan needed to remind them of. They would certainly have it themselves. The future was what they were all looking towards, yet it was also something that they had to grasp and create for themselves.

What about Happy then? They had no way of sustaining for a year. As far as the outside world had been concerned, every step they advanced to signified their limit, but now, they had reached the final stage of the Challenger League. This was already something very unexpected. Defeating Excellent Era? In the eyes of many, this was something entirely unconceivable. Even those who wanted this to happen didn't think it could.

The disparity in strength was too great.

Many people knew this very well. Even Happy themselves were well aware.

But the fact that no one knew the final result was what made competitions interesting. No one would dare to say who won with one hundred percent certainty. If the results could be determined just by looking at who was stronger on paper, why would there still need to be a fight?

Victory. It would always need to be fought for and earned. It was never about comparison.

The total number of players on both sides was twelve. At this moment, they had all entered their individual player booths. The map for the team competition slowly materialized on stage. The screen displayed the current loading bars of the twelve characters. Introductions were being made for each of the characters.

Wu Chen had never appeared during the offline tournament, so naturally his character had had little exposure. Now, after he suddenly appeared in the lineup, the spectators were suddenly brimming with curiosity about his character. Raising their heads with difficulty to look at Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle, everyone was greatly disappointed.

Dawn Rifle had originally been an important member of Team Everlasting. However, every piece of valuable equipment on him had been peddled away after Team Everlasting was dissolved. Yet, while Happy had been in the process of strengthening their characters' equipment, they hadn't focused on creating any pieces of Silver Equipment suited for the Launcher class, so they could only choose from the selection of level 75 Orange equipment.

Ultimately, Wu Chen managed to pull together a full set of level 75 Orange equipment for Dawn Rifle. In-game, this kind of character would be considered almost unmatched. However, on the professional stage, especially in the face of a powerhouse team like Excellent Era, a full set of Orange equipment, whose characteristics could be determined with a glance, really wasn't enough. Looking at this character, Wu Chen really didn't seem like Happy's secret weapon for defeating Excellent Era.

After both teams' characters had finished loading, the final troop arrangement was finally revealed.

On Team Excellent Era's side, the reserve player was Wang Ze.

On Team Happy's side, the reserve player was Steamed Bun.

Wu Chen was actually part of the starting lineup?

The audience once again erupted in murmurs. After seeing Wu Chen's character, everyone had been more willing to believe that he had come onstage because Happy didn't have any other choice. Thus, when the audience saw that he would be one of the starting players instead, they were once again surprised.

At this moment, the system's countdown ended. The team competition had officially begun.

Map: Ancient Maple Path.

As the designated map for the most important match of the Challenger League, Ancient Maple Path was another very comprehensive one. However, this time, the battlefield had been moved from the city to the countryside. A long, secluded ancient road ran from one side of the map to the other. Both sides of the road were lined with maple trees, the scarlet leaves rustling with the wind. Naturally, this was where the name of the map originated. However, a map couldn't be made up of just a single road. On both sides of the map, behind the trees, there were hills, rivers, mud holes, and scattered stones. Whether or not all of these things should be together in one place wasn't important for a competition map. What was important was giving the map a more diverse feel, especially for this kind of designated map. It definitely couldn't cater to any one playstyle, because this would give an unfair advantage to a team that was well suited to that style. It would be like giving one team the advantage of a home game map!

Match: start.

The characters from both teams spawned at opposite ends of the ancient road. These spawn points were also the designated support zones. Outside of these, there were also four other support zones distributed evenly on both sides of the map.

As soon as Team Excellent Era's five characters spawned, they began skillfully advancing, showing their familiarity with the map.

Qiu Fei's Combat Form was at the head of the group, with Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher following behind at a varying distance. Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Woven Shadow, followed behind, under the protection of these two characters. Woven Shadow was also quite a famous character within the Alliance. As a powerhouse, Excellent Era obviously wouldn't have any weak links.

After his awful performance in the group arena, Shen Jian didn't dare to make any more mistakes. His Striker character acted as a bodyguard for Woven Shadow, not daring to take a single step out of line.

Behind all of the others was Team Excellent Era's ace, One Autumn Leaf. It seemed that the generalissimo was well accustomed to bringing up the rear.

It seemed like a chaotic formation, but in reality every person's position was calculated. Traveling along the ancient road, Excellent Era constantly maintained this formation. Only Xiao Shiqin's character appeared flexible.

In contrast, Happy's side didn't have any of Excellent Era's discipline or tacit understanding. Nevertheless, their movements were still well coordinated. All of the characters neatly walked towards the left, evidently not planning on engaging with Excellent Era's forces head-on.

"How will the two sides perform?" At this time, Pan Lin clearly couldn't wait. From before the contest began until the official start of the match, he had already asked this question four times.

"Happy has elected to take a more tactical approach, which isn't unexpected. The two sides clearly differ greatly in strength, so they will have to employ flexible tactics if they want to win." Li Yibo said.

"But Excellent Era also has a Master Tactician, and furthermore he appears to be performing at his peak today. Will Happy's tactics be of any use?" Pan Lin wondered.

"Let's take a look at Happy's formation first!" Li Yibo pointed out.

Happy's five players all took a detour along the left side of the ancient road. Their sense of direction was very clear. It was obvious that they had come up with this strategy after carefully researching the map. However, Team Excellent Era's footsteps had already come to a stop. Those who studied the map had a clear understanding of where their opponents would enter their field of view if they had gone straight down the road. At this moment, Excellent Era had already reached this spot. Since they hadn't seen anyone from the opposing team, they obviously knew that Happy wouldn't be facing them in a direct confrontation.

This point obviously wasn't a surprise to Excellent Era. The team immediately changed directions, heading towards one side of the road. Seeing this, Pan Lin immediately grew excited, because the direction that Excellent Era had chosen led straight towards Happy! At this rate, the two sides would meet in the northwest part of the map.

The broadcast also cut to display an image of the map, revealing the intricacies of the terrain. Since battle had yet to break out, they had time to let everyone familiarize themselves with the map first!

At this moment, the spectators present became even more nervous. On the projection, both sides' characters were currently tiny dots, hurrying towards their destinations. Excellent Era's five characters still maintained their previous formation, whereas Happy's five people still seemed disorderly. As the gap between the two sides closed, the projection also zoomed in. The terrain and the characters also became more and more focused.

Soon!

Just as this thought crossed everyone's minds, a gunshot rang out. From Happy's side, the one who had caused everyone's surprise, Wu Chen, fired the first shot of the battle.

Dawn Rifle's projectile flew out, but it didn't seem to have any sort of purpose. It randomly exploded somewhere on the ground. It appeared as if this shot had been some sort of misclick.

.\

Except, Team Excellent Era clearly made immediate adjustments. The distance between the two sides had already reached the point at which artillery fire could he heard.

"Their sense of direction is very clear!" Pan Lin, seeing Excellent Era's adjustments, shouted. Just from hearing this noise, Excellent Era had made adjustments and now charged very clearly in Team Happy's direction.

"Is Happy planning on setting up an ambush?" Li Yibo, seeing Happy's action, didn't dare come to a hasty conclusion. In a 5v5 match, the power of an ambush wasn't as powerful as many expected it to be. It was mainly used to grasp an opportunity by catching the opponents off guard, but in a match in which the gap in strength was wide, it only gave initiative. It wasn't enough to win a competition in one fell swoop. Excellent Era definitely had the strength to control the aftermath and take back the initiative.

"It seems .... that this isn't the case ..." Pan Lin said.

Happy's characters didn't spread out and conceal themselves, instead choosing to immediately retreat. Ultimately, they managed to put some distances between themselves and Excellent Era, but the earlier noise meant that the opposing team was very clear that they had been here just recently. As they got closer to the area, they began to guard against Happy's ambush. In the audience's eyes, their extremely careful movements were almost laughable. Excellent Era's fans only hated the fact that they had no way of warning their team that the opponents had already run away.

Excellent Era quickly realized that their opponents had indeed left. Once again, the team's formation was adjusted, widening in order to search a larger area. However, at this moment, another explosion rang out. Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle had once again unexpectedly fired.

Excellent Era once again followed the source of the noise, yet once again Happy turned and retreated, disappearing into thin air. Excellent Era's formation once again tightened to guard against an ambush, making the spectators look at one another in dismay.

If all they wanted was to use this method to wear down Excellent Era's spirit, weren't Happy's so-called tactics too childish? This kind of annoyance, as long as you ignored it, what kind of damage could it do?

As a result, when Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle fired out a third shot, Excellent Era's team still appeared patient, chasing the noise once more. However, Team Happy finally decided to switch things up. The team split into two, with Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle suddenly running off on his own.

Chapter 1031: What Kind of Opponent!

The crowd was starting to grow restless. There was finally a change in Happy's tactics, but that change alone wasn't enough for them to see through their intentions. The poor commentators, Pan Lin and Li Yibo, saw the change, but they remained very cautious with their words. They had fallen into too many traps because of these players, especially on Happy's side. Ye Xiu was definitely the leader of the group. The two of them didn't dare to make any rash guesses, so for the previous "childish annoyance", the two could only grind their teeth and talk about other unrelated things.

Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle and the other four teammates split up. When Excellent Era arrived, they naturally failed to find them for a third time. This failure didn't seem to deter Excellent Era's players. They carefully searched the area like before, but unfortunately, still discovered nothing.

What was Happy planning on doing?

The crowd could wait for the answer to appear, but Excellent Era couldn't. They needed to guess and be prepared. When the answer finally came, what if the answer wasn't something they were prepared to defend against?

A fourth shot rang out. Excellent Era didn't immediately chase after the source of the gunshot like before.

"Wait a second." Xiao Shiqin gave out his first order of this match. There was one small subtlety in this. Orders were usually given out in the team chat to prevent the opponents from seeing them. However, it seemed as if Xiao Shiqin forgot about this detail and announced it for everyone to read.

"Hahahaha." Li Yibo laughed. He was just about to comment on it.

"Go!" But in Excellent Era's team chat, Xiao Shiqin unexpectedly gave out a completely opposite order.

Li Yibo swallowed his words.

Too crafty. I almost fell into a trap again.

On the other hand, the crowd was smiling with joy. As Excellent Era's fans, they felt like Xiao Shiqin's actions were quick-witted. On Happy's side, their supporters saw Xiao Shiqin's actions and shook their heads.

"Those who play with tactics are too dirty**!" Wei Chen sighed.

"Yeah!" Sun Zheping nodded his head.

Just when Team Excellent Era finished pulling off their bluff and prepared to chase after the sound to achieve their aim through a trick, another gunshot rang out. This time, it came from the opposite direction.

Team Excellent Era stared blankly. Everyone stared blankly. However, the crowd could at least see that this gunshot had come from the group that split apart from Dawn Rifle. The only one among them who could make a gunshot was their unspecialized, Lord Grim.

The Myriad Manifestation Umbrella's gunform wasn't a handcannon. His attacks make an exploding noise. Lord Grim had fired Anti-Tank Missiles, but cancelled the skill after the first missile flew out. By doing this, he was able to perfectly replicate the sound of gunfire from Dawn Rifle's handcannon. It must have taken painstaking efforts to perform.　

However, what was his intention?　

Just looking at the idea, it was just as childish as the earlier blank shots to get the enemy's attention.

But this was a confrontation between two Master Tacticians. How could such childish thinking appear in this kind of high-level match?

What was the point of firing gunshots on opposite sides?

All that did was tell the other side that the enemy team had split into two. And then? Was Happy hoping for the other side to split up and give chase? Or was Happy hoping for Excellent Era to focus one target? And then how was Happy going to respond to the Excellent Era's decision?

The purpose of tactics was to give your side an advantage. However, Happy's move didn't seem to be able to get them any advantage. Wasn't splitting the team apart supposed to be a secret? Wasn't announcing it to the enemy team the same as giving away your advantage?

I don't understand. I just don't understand.　

Pan Lin and Li Yibo had their brows furrowed in deep thought. After a long time, they turned their heads and saw the same puzzled look on each other's face before dumbly turning their heads back to the match.

They obviously couldn't explain things that they didn't understand.

Deliberately mystifying things?

Apart from calling it "childish", this was the only other possibility that Li Yibo could think of. However, the problem was that even if Happy was deliberately mystifying things, there had to be some sort of goal in mind. So what if Happy confused Excellent Era with their actions?

Team Excellent Era merely hesitated a bit when they heard two gunshots from two different locations. Soon afterwards, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher resolutely headed towards their original target. The other four characters followed him, maintaining their formation as they continued to move in perfect sync.

The five players had chosen to bite Wu Chen.

Let alone him just being a player from a relegated team, even a top God from the Alliance would be at an absolute disadvantage.

What was Ye Xiu thinking?

Everyone was puzzled.

This time, it wasn't just Pan Lin and Li Yibo who weren't skilled enough to understand what was going on. The three Team Tiny Herb players were also confused, unable to see through Ye Xiu's intentions.

If they couldn't guess, they could only keep watching and wait for the answer to come to them.　　

Team Excellent Era moved swiftly, an advantage of having powerful characters. Strong characters were strong in all aspects. Attack and defense were just one part of the equation. As a team, equipping a character might not simply be for the sole purpose of improving one's own individual strength, but rather for the purpose of synergizing with the other characters in the team.　　

For example, take movement speed. Every character had their own movement speed. The entire team's movement speed depended on the slowest team member. Perhaps this character didn't need high movement speed, but sometimes, in order to increase the speed of the entire team, this character would need to wear equipment that was pointless alone. However, for the team, it was a very meaningful upgrade.

And this was another layer to research into Silver equipment. It wasn't just about higher stats, but rather how Silver equipment interacted with each other in a team.

Happy clearly weren't at that level yet. Even in the Alliance, only a few powerhouses had reached this step. Team Excellent Era had a new addition, Life Extinguisher. Just like how the player needed to meld into the team, the character needed to as well. And now it looked like Excellent Era had done a good job. Whether it was Xiao Shiqin or Life Extinguisher, Team Excellent Era was already a single entity. Their movements didn't seem to be crude in the slightest.

Their advantage in movement speed allowed Team Excellent Era to get closer to Team Happy bit by bit. Happy's equipment was simple and crude. The vast majority of their equipment was Orange, so their stats were known, giving Excellent Era a rough estimate of the strength of Happy's characters. The movement speed of Happy's character was one of these estimates.

After missing three times, Excellent Era wasn't shaken because they knew that as long as they kept on chasing, they would soon find the other side.

Fourth time!

Judging by the difference between our movement speeds, we definitely won't miss a fourth time. Xiao Shiqin had calculated it. However, this time, when they chased after their target, they still missed.

Xiao Shiqin obviously wasn't hoping for Happy to just sit there waiting. When he was certain that they wouldn't miss, he meant that they should see signs of Happy within their field of view.

However, when they gave chase for the fourth time, they still didn't see any signs of their target.　

Bang!

At this moment, a new gunshot rang, clearly from up ahead.　　

"Hurry up and give chase!" A God like Sun Xiang obviously had very good judgement. He also had a good idea of their movement speed advantage. He felt like their miss this time was probably because they slowed down a bit every time they reached their target location. If they hurried, they would certain catch the other side the next time.

"We won't be able to catch them." Xiao Shiqin suddenly typed.

"It's only one person here. His movement speed is above our team's." Xiao Shiqin said. Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle wore a full set of Orange equipment, so Xiao Shiqin naturally had a very strong grasp of Dawn Rifle's movement speed.

Why did Happy split up? Hints for why could finally be seen. It was a very precise tactical change. Xiao Shiqin had been certain that they would catch their target the fourth time. As a result, Happy split up before this. Happy couldn't compare to Excellent Era in terms of their overall team movement speed, but Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle on his own was faster than Excellent Era.

What had Happy gained from this minute change? Was it just to continue with their "childish annoyance?"

The crowd members could finally see glimmers of the thinking, but it came with new questions. Neither side had yet to fight yet. They were just running around, baffling everyone. Many people had already gotten impatient. The boos from the crowd had naturally become extremely loud. Excellent Era's fans were very unhappy with Happy's mysterious strategy.

At this moment, another gunshot rang out.

Wu CHen's Dawn Rifle once again reminded Excellent Era where he was located.

To give chase or to not give chase?

Xiao Shiqin finally hesitated. If they chased, they definitely wouldn't be able to catch him. If they didn't chase, they wouldn't lose anything, but then what should they do?

Xiao Shiqin felt his head hurt a bit. He suddenly realized that this was a rather unfamiliar situation because up until now, he had been leading the weaker team. Through tactics, they contended with stronger teams. Overwhelming strength? Team Thunderclap had never possessed that.

But now? Xiao Shiqin realized that if he had been in Ye Xiu's position, perhaps he would have had an easier time because beating the strong as the weak was his strength. The strong beating the weak? He had started experiencing that this season, but the opponents that they encountered were too weak. So weak that he couldn't get any experience from it. In the blink of an eye, it was the finals. Now, they had encountered a weak team, but not strong enough to pose a threat.

And his opponent was another Master Tactician, Ye Xiu. To Xiao Shiqin, his generation had been hugely affected by this God. Their Glory knowledge had more or less come from this God. Why else was he called the Glory Textbook?

Quite a few of Xiao Shiqin's tactics and strategies had been learned from Ye Xiu's matches. His tactical ability wasn't any better than the opposing God.

Xiao Shiqin suddenly became aware that the opponents he had to beat this match were similar... to the former Team Thunderclap that he had once led.

Chapter 1032: Attempted Exchange

The current situation made Xiao Shiqin feel somewhat embarrassed. Besides Xiao Shiqin, even his teammates might not notice this small detail.

Although Team Excellent Era's captain was Sun Xiang, the commanding position had been transferred to him when he joined the team as vice captain. At this moment Xiao Shiqin suddenly became silent. In a situation like this, which required the team to choose, they had come to a sudden halt, almost as if a fire had been extinguished.

　

Xiao Shiqin immediately recovered his senses. Coming to a stop like this could be fatal on stage. He needed to quickly adjust himself instead of getting distracted, so he could grasp their current situation. After Xiao Shiqin understood that Ye Xiu was trying to do what he had been doing the entire time throughout his career, his train of thought became incomparably smooth.

Simply put, Ye Xiu was Ye Xiu, Xiao Shiqin was Xiao Shiqin. Even if they were doing the same thing, they weren't the same people. Ye Xiu was someone Xiao Shiqin had studied, but this didn't mean that he completely grasped Ye Xiu's patterns. After thinking about things from Ye Xiu's perspective, Xiao Shiqin was suddenly at a loss.

From Ye Xiu, he had learned tactics to fight the strong with the weak, and for the most part, it involved deducing many things from what he already knew. During Ye Xiu's entire time at Excellent Era, the team hadn't been anywhere near as weak as Thunderclap was. At most they would be disadvantaged during a match, yet they never fought with the mentality of a weak team facing a stronger team. Even during the season when Excellent Era had been in danger of being relegated, no one had thought that they were a weak team. Excellent Era's relegation had been considered something of a miracle.

Even taking Happy's current position into consideration, Xiao Shiqin still couldn't determine what Happy's intentions were. At the very least, if he were the one playing the Happy card, he wouldn't have brought it to this kind of situation.

Should they keep chasing, or should they stop?

To be honest, in the current situation, Excellent Era really didn't need to be so vigorous in taking the initiative. Because they had won the group arena, they were currently in the lead. They could simply sit and wait for Happy to come knocking at their door.

But the problem was, they were Excellent Era. They were the team that held the clear advantage in this competition. The dignity of a powerhouse prevented them from acting in such a passive manner. This was why Excellent Era's actions in the past had always been proactive and aggressive. They vigorously searched for Team Happy's position, wanting to quickly decide victory or defeat, as if they were the ones falling behind.

Except now, they had a target right in front of them, yet they couldn't reach it.

Split up?

Xiao Shiqin shook his head. If they really divided their troops so that one group was fast enough to catch up, they might actually fall into Happy's trap.

"This way."

Xiao Shiqin once again sent this message in the public chat. Afterwards, he directed his character to lead Team Excellent Era in the opposite direction.

He gave up on chasing after Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle, instead charging in the direction of Ye Xiu and his Lord Grim's fake shot. However, his message in the public chat was intended to cause confusion. This way ... which way was this way?

Xiao Shiqin obviously didn't want Happy to easily deduce his intentions. However, this time, when Wu Chen fired a projectile, he didn't immediately leave. Xiao Shiqin's message of "this way" hadn't done anything to sway him. He waited for a short period of time, but he didn't discover any traces of Team Excellent Era. In Team Happy's chat, Wu Chen reported this occurrence. A moment later, Ye Xiu replied with his coordinates.

The members of the audience, who paid close attention, could see that these coordinates pointed to the place where Lord Grim had pretended to fire his shot. This was also in the direction that Team Excellent Era was currently headed.

Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle decisively altered his course, also heading towards this location.

From their omniscient view, the audience could see the whole situation very clearly. Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle increased his speed, gradually pressing closer to Team Excellent Era from behind. Yet, Team Happy's other four members moved in a wide arc, seeming to want to circle their way behind Dawn Rifle.

Everyone anxiously watched the scene unfold. Finally, Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle caught up to Team Excellent Era. All five members of the team were currently within his field of view.

However, at the same time, he was also discovered by Excellent Era. Even if they had clearly been focused on getting to their destination, how could an experienced pro team like Excellent Era forget to keep track of their surroundings while moving?

"Behind!" Zhang Jiaxing called out, discovering Dawn Rifle during one of his routine sweeps.

No one rushed to look back. In a flash, the other four members had already created a protective encirclement around Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric. The entire team turned around as one.

　　

Immediately afterwards, artillery fire rained down ...

Excellent Era's five members easily dodged, but they had no way of returning fire. At this distance, only Launcher's had the range to fight back. Tean Excellent Era's current team composition consisted of two Battle Mages, a Striker, a Mechanic, and a Cleric.

Mechanic Life Extinguisher was without a doubt their number one long range attacker. However, compared to Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle, his range was insufficient. After releasing his first attack, Dawn Rifle had already begun charging up a second attack, then a third ...

Everyone was struck dumb. Dawn Rifle seemed inclined to challenge Excellent Era's entire team alone. Was this really Team Happy's secret weapon?

Team Excellent Era obviously wouldn't sit passively or be thrown into disorder by Wu Chen's long-ranged attacks. The team rapidly flew towards Wu Chen, quickly closing the distance.

However, Wu Chen wasn't greedy at all. As soon as he saw Team Excellent Era charging towards him, he immediately retreated. He moved even faster than he had previously, even utilizing Aerial Fire.

Team Excellent Era could only watch helplessly. Dawn Rifle's movement speed was indeed above their team's. This had already been previously confirmed.

However, as soon as they stopped, Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle once again happily rained skills down onto them.

Was this ... kiting?

Once again, everyone stared blankly. Wu Chen, a completely unknown player, was actually single-handedly kiting Excellent Era?

In reality, this kind of max range offensive couldn't effectively hurt Excellent Era's players because their characters were simply too strong. However, this kind of endless harassment made them unable to just sit still and let it happen.

In fact, the reason the team's speed was slower than Dawn Rifle was because they were being held back by the slowest member.** If we were only considering each individuals, any member of Excellent Era outside of Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric could surpass Dawn Rifle in terms of speed.

Leave the Cleric behind and kill Dawn Rifle first?

Just as Xiao Shiqin had this thought, his entire body suddenly broke out in a cold sweat.

If they really did this, they would be abandoning their Cleric. Wouldn't this be just the opportunity Team Happy was looking for? Even if Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle was caught and killed this way, to trade his life for Excellent Era's Cleric would definitely be worth it.

So treacherous, so despicable!

Was the initial wild goose chase a ploy to make Excellent Era drop their guard?

So they could quickly pick off our Cleric?

Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher looked around, sweeping the surrounding terrain. As a Master Tactician, he had an experienced eye, quickly locating a location extremely suited to this kind of sneak attack.

"Go!" This time, the order was only sent in the team chat. Team Excellent Era suddenly changed directions, charging towards the optimal attack location that Xiao Shiqin had calculated.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

** TL Note: 木桶理论 literally means that a barrel’s capacity is limited by the length of the shortest plank. In economics, this is known as Liebig's law of the minimum (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liebig%27s_law_of_the_minimum#Liebig's_barrel). It essentially states that maximum potential is limited by the resource is scarecest, instead of by the sum of all resources. The concept itself is pretty straightforward, although it can be applied to a lot of situations outside of economics, as seen here. -- Veriquity

Chapter 1033: Heading for Tiger-Borne Mountains

Xiao Shiqin gave the signal to attack and the team immediately obeyed. One Autumn Leaf, who had been at the back of their formation, charged to the front and dashed in the direction Xiao Shiqin had pointed out to them along with Qiu Fei's Combat Form.

Now knowing that all that was behind them was a far off Dawn Rifle, there was no need for Excellent Era to be so cautious about their backs. The two Battle Mages advanced together, swiftly arriving at the place Xiao Shiqin had pointed out to them.

A miss!

They had missed again.

The place Xiao Shiqin had predicted would be the best spot for Happy to ambush them was devoid of people.

　

"Could it be that Ye Xiu had predicted I would realize this and didn't choose this position on purpose?" Xiao Shiqin unavoidably began to do another mental multiple choice with himself.

That's how Team Excellent Era was sent into uncertainty once more. Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle courageously moved forward a few steps and fired wildly at them. Though it wasn't any serious threat, Excellent Era's players still had to dodge it, so it still caused them trouble, no?

Xiao Shiqin might have been considering their strategy, he also managed to react swiftly. In the current Team Excellent Era, the one who could get Dawn Rifle in range first was Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher.

Who would've thought that Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle would immediately and resolutely go into a full retreat the moment he began to act.

Xiao Shiqin felt helpless.

For this player, he had only done research on him just in case. Although Wu Chen had barely appeared in the Challenger League, he had still fought in the pro league prior to that, so Xiao Shiqin had found some resources. Dawn Rifle was a player with a good grasp of the foundations, but no other particularly striking abilities. Xiao Shiqin hadn't gone in-depth with how they should deal with him.

　

Yet now, it was this player that was causing them the most trouble.

He didn't need or want to do anything fantastic, he just wanted to complete his mission without mistakes. Wu Chen carefully maneuvered his Dawn Rifle. He was clear on his own skill level. Against Excellent Era, he didn't have the ability to deal any significant damage to them, but he could still accomplish this sort of harassment.

This was because this wasn't a task with any true difficulty. Other pro players probably wouldn't be willing to accept such a simple task, but not Wu Chen. He knew he was a player with no talent to shoulder such important tasks. This sort of simple task was a chance for him to do what he could, and he took it very seriously.

It was easy to imagine the result of him taking a simple task so seriously.

Excellent Era really had gotten frustrated with Wu Chen's harassment.

The entire team wouldn't be able to catch up to him, so they could only split up if they wanted to hit him.

Xiao Shiqin had realized Ye Xiu's intentions, but… he had no choice but to comply.

This was because he wasn't in command of Thunderclap anymore, where he could lower his position. He was in command of Excellent Era, the strongest team, the only team to ever erect a dynasty. Even being relegated couldn't kill the pride this team had. They thought of themselves as that team that had created a dynasty, and their fans saw them as a powerhouse team that was second to none. Being relegated was nothing more than an accident.

A team like this couldn't perform as if they were disadvantaged. When relegated, they were even more sensitive, and even more repulsed by such an idea. They would let Dawn Rifle buzz around them like a fly. Xiao Shiqin thought it wouldn't matter in the larger scheme; everyone just had to dodge a little more.

However, because they were Team Excellent Era, their fans and the audience wouldn't accept it if they couldn't even deal with a bother like this. Excellent Era couldn't just win. They had to crush their opponents and win with conviction.

They had to attack...

Team Excellent Era adjusted their direction, chasing after Dawn Rifle. Except, this time, they didn't move as a unit. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher and Qiu Fei's Combat Form brought out their fastest movement speed. They swiftly began to close in on Dawn Rifle while, behind them, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf and Shen Jian's Striker stuck close to and protected their Cleric, Woven Shadow.

　

Xiao Shiqin actually felt very insecure. He knew that the situation Ye Xiu had been waiting for had appeared. Team Happy definitely would've made arrangements for such a situation. However, he couldn't do anything about it. He had finally been given a clear experience of how a powerhouse had to act even when they knew they shouldn't. Throughout the Challenger League, they could still steamroll their opponents like that, but this time, they were facing an enemy that worried them.

Seeing Life Extinguisher and Combat Form in pursuit so suddenly, Dawn Rifle fled without a care for harassing them any more.

"Slow down," Xiao Shiqin typed into the channel, directing this mostly towards Qiu Fei.

If they went at full speed, they would be able to catch up to Dawn Rifle faster, but they would also widen the distance between them and the other three. Knowing that Happy would capitalize on this, Xiao Shiqin would naturally do the best he could to weaken what advantage they could gain. He wouldn't use his all to chase after Dawn Rifle, but just choose a speed that could catch up to Dawn Rifle. This way, they wouldn't draw away from One Autumn Leaf and the other two so quickly.

Xiao Shiqin hoped that Happy would strike sooner than later, yet Happy didn't act.

The audience could clearly see that Happy's Lord Grim and co were following Dawn Rifle a small ways away and were prepared to coordinate. However, when Dawn Rifle began to retreat, the four darted away from their positions and got into positions for an ambush. Yet, not long after, the four began to move again, leaving their original positions.

Now that the arrangements of each team were crystal clear, the commentators Li Yibo and Pan Lin could finally begin to commentate confidently.

"Happy wants to use the harassment from Dawn Rifle to force Excellent Era to split their forces," Pan Lin said.

"Yes… In reality, Dawn Rifle can't do very much to harass them, at least not to the point of forcing them. However, it seems like Excellent Era is very confident in their ability to deal with this," Li Yibo added.

"Uh… It doesn't seem like Life Extinguisher and Combat Form are running in pursuit at full speed?" Pan Lin questioned.

"Yeah… they're trying to preserve the team formation as much as possible. They don't want to split up too much. It seems like Xiao Shiqin has a clear understanding of Happy's strategy," Li Yibo said.

"So that's why Happy hasn't struck yet. Their offensive formation has yet again been shifted," Pan Lin noted.

"Why isn't Team Excellent Era being more resolute? If they use One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form to lead the charge and have Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher in the middle with his long-range capabilities, they can split the team into three parts and better deal with the situation." That was when Li Yibo voiced an uncertainty and it really did seem like a more secure arrangement than Xiao Shiqin's.

This, naturally, wasn't a question Pan Lin could answer. The audience, too, could only be puzzled, feeling that Li Yibo was very correct. Why didn't a Master Tactician like Xiao Shiqin choose a better strategy?

Yet, it was Chen Guo on Team Happy's bench, the Chen Guo that usually worried over not being able to understand anything that was going on in the match grinned smugly at the commentary.

"For the team competition against Excellent Era, this is our breakthrough point!"

When Ye Xiu had said this in Team Happy's strategy meeting and pointed at Xiao Shiqin's name on their strategy board, Chen Guo had found it extremely strange. Even though she wasn't very skilled, she was also relentlessly thinking of a method on how to beat Excellent Era. When fighting stronger opponents, you had to find your opponent's weak point. This was something Chen Guo understood. However, she had never imagined that Xiao Shiqin would be Excellent Era's weak point.

"Why?" Though Chen Guo wouldn't take part in the matches, she was still the first person to question this out of curiosity.

Because Xiao Shiqin still hadn't synced up with Excellent Era's rhythm yet.

This was the answer Chen Guo had received.

Xiao Shiqin's background had influenced a lot of his tactical style and playstyle. For a powerhouse like Excellent Era, Xiao Shiqin's tactical style held them back. His detailed, calculated and nitpicking style wasn't noble enough for Team Excellent Era.

That was something that Xiao Shiqin had been acutely aware of since joining Excellent Era.

He had made adjustments and the two sides synced up cheerfully. Unfortunately, they had never met an opponent that could truly test them, because for Excellent Era, the Challenger League was too low a level. Any sort of adjustment would seem seamless at this sort of level.

Only strong opponents would be true tests of their success.

Happy might not be a powerful opponent, but they were the only true test Excellent Era had been pitted up against since their relegation.

Any dissonance that existed between Xiao Shiqin and Excellent Era would be tested for here. If there was a problem, they would have to resolve it on the field. If they couldn't resolve it well, more problems might become apparent.

Happy's tactics were so simple that they seemed almost childish. However, they had managed to accurately strike at the disharmony between Xiao Shiqin and Excellent Era.

Xiao Shiqin, with his original style, wouldn't have bothered about this sort of childish harassment. However, after taking on Excellent Era, he had to find a way to deal with it.

Knowing that a mountain hid tigers, yet heading for those tiger-borne mountains anyways. This wasn't Xiao Shiqin's preferred style at all, but he had to deal with these problems in such a way. He could only face this with care, but the arrangements he made weren't nearly as proactive and daring as Li Yibo's ideas.

This was because Xiao Shiqin still subconsciously displayed the style he as most comfortable with in uncertain situations.

He didn't want Excellent Era to seem cautious and nervous like a mid to low tier team.

Thus, he had used a different method to avoid executing his original cautious method...

Team Excellent Era, having split into two, continued to pursue Dawn Rifle, but Dawn Rifle was running for his life and Happy's other members were retreating for their lives. Xiao Shiqin might've suppressed his speed, but Happy drew out the duration. In the end, the two groups still managed to pull apart to a distance that Xiao Shiqin was reluctant to have.

Even Pan Lin couldn't help but sigh in disappointment for Excellent Era, "If they had known sooner, Life Extinguisher and Combat Form might as well have sped up. That way, they would at least be able to attack Dawn Rifle a couple times."

"Isn't Excellent Era being a little too cautious? They're so much stronger than Happy, after all. They can totally afford to be a little more headstrong," Li Yibo commented. This time, he really hadn't gotten anything wrong. Xiao Shiqin, struggling to make a decision, had reverted to what he was most comfortable with.

Team Excellent Era was forced to exercise excessive caution under this style.

Chapter 1034: 1v2

Xiao Shiqin and Qiu Fei accelerated in pursuit of Dawn Rifle, but they weren't thorough enough.. In the end,, they still pulled a certain amount of distance away from Sun Xiang's group. Even worse, not only were they not getting closer to Dawn Rifle, the two saw signs of the other Happy members.

Not good!!

When Xiao Shiqin saw the other members of Happy in that direction, his heart skipped a beat. He thought Happy would disengage and then regroup to ambush their Cleric, but judging from their current position, it was obvious that they didn't have such intentions. Their true targets were the players pursuing Dawn Rifle.

"Stop!"

After realising that they had fallen into a trap, Xiao Shiqin subconsciously made adjustments, gesturing to Qiu Fei to stop his pursuit. He then spun his view to look at the distance between them and the three characters behind him.

"Retreat!" The distance caused Xiao Shiqin to feel a lack of security, so he had Life Extinguisher retreat.

Qiu Fei's Combat Form visibly hesitated for a moment, but obeyed the order nonetheless.

However, the members of Happy had already appeared. How could they let them escape so easily? Dawn Rifle stopped retreating while the other silhouettes quickly grew clearer. They carried out a fan formation and moved to encircle Life Extinguisher and Combat Form.

This was indeed a trap!

Xiao Shiqin felt fortunate for being able to react quickly, so he could retreat in time. The loss shouldn't be too great, right?

The loss was indeed insignificant. Even though Happy pressed them fiercely, the other three members of Excellent Era weren't so far behind that they couldn't be seen. Reinforcements arrived in the blink of an eye. Happy only advanced on them, attacking only for a moment, and then retreated before the members of Excellent Era finished grouping up.

Xiao Shiqin let out a long sigh of relief. He was pretty satisfied with his response towards the situation. However, it was unknown if the commentators, viewers, and other pro players understood his reasoning... Everyone apart from him felt that his choice of action meant an opportunity wasted.

"Why did he retreat?" Pan Lin was very puzzled.

"Excellent Era is fighting very hesitantly! Since they've already given chase, why did they choose to retreat? Even though Excellent Era had been outnumbered, from the strengths of their pro players and characters, they shouldn't need to escape. Reinforcements would have arrived if they held out a bit longer, so Happy wouldn't have attacked too rashly. By retreating, Happy could attack fiercely without needing to heed the consequences! Excellent Era is currently retreating very quickly. They have no continuity in their attacks at all!" Li Yibo spoke.

"Excellent Era's performance is quite abnormal today." Pan Lin said.

"Is it because the group arena didn't meet their expectations? Or is it because they've never met a troublesome opponent like Happy in the Challenger League? No matter what the reason may be, Excellent Era shouldn't fight with such a lack of confidence..." Li Yibo only mentioned the problem, but was still thinking about the specific reason. Even though he roughly knew what it was, what was it specifically?

"Xiao Shiqin... is treating Excellent Era like Thunderclap." In the end, it was a pro player from Tiny Herb who discovered the exact problem.

"He lacked comprehensive and high-level practice this season, so he wasn't able to judge thoroughly enough. In stressful situations, he subconsciously responds with the play style he used to lead Team Thunderclap." Xu Bin said.

Xu Bin had the right to talk about Xiao Shiqin. This is because his former team, 301 Degrees, was a mid-tier one along with Xiao Shiqin's Thunderclap. The two were direct rivals, so they always fought to the death with each other in order to vie for the spot in the finals. Their matches would greatly impact their final rankings, so they always had to thoroughly investigate each other.

"Yes. He is now leading Team Excellent Era! With fierce players like Sun Xiang, there's no need for him to fight like that. I'd say, if he let Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf rush to the front, he might have been able to neutralize Happy's ambush." Liu Xiaobie said.

Whatever was said could only remain as words; the match didn't progress like they thought. At this time, Xiao Shiqin started to realize that something was wrong. This was thanks to their Cleric, Zhang Jiaxing, one of the three members who had caught up to him.

"Aren't we fighting a bit too passively? I think we can be more proactive." Zhang Jiaxing expressed his opinion. There was only one shot caller, but other players had the right to give advice and speak their thoughts. Among Excellent Era's roster, Zhang Jiaxing was the only player who had been a core member of the team the entire time. Coincidently, the Cleric was a character who needed to be able to observe the general situation, so he could acutely discover what was off today.

Xiao Shiqin woke up with these words. He immediately became aware that he mistook Excellent Era for Thunderclap when he was commanding. In fact, he had been reminding himself to change his character for the entire season. However, he was still unable to take on his new role with familiarity during crucial moments in the match. The tactical habits he had developed from Thunderclap were still deeply rooted in him. He needed time and matches to erase it. Although he had ample time this year, he didn't have enough matches. The level of the opponents in the Challenger League weren't adequate enough.

"You're right, we need to be more proactive!" Xiao Shiqin was not the type to save his face when the problem was found. Saving face was mostly found in powerhouses, so players from medium to small teams wouldn't have this shortcoming even for an All Star.

Xiao Shiqin immediately made adjustments after noticing the problem. Excellent Era's ace, One Autumn Leaf, finally pushed towards the peak of the formation. Combat Form and One Autumn Leaf immediately accelerated in pursuit, while Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher acted as a support in the middle. Shen Jian's Striker took the responsibility of protecting the team's Cleric.

"Yes, it seems like Excellent Era has finally discovered the problem and is quickly making adjustments." Li Yibo spoke happily. It was not because he felt happy for Excellent Era, but because their adjustments followed the format he thought was best before. He was able to show his skills as a commentator through the comments today, so Li Yibo was rather pleased with himself.

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf and Qiu Fei's Combat Form no longer held any reservations. They attacked with full power while moving swiftly. Soon, the retreating characters of Team Happy appeared in the two's field of view.

Lord Grim!

The one they were able to catch up to was coincidentally Ye Xiu, who had defeated Qiu Fei and Sun Xiang in the group arena. They were able to meet in the team competition again.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

The two Battle Mages of Excellent Era, One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form, suddenly used this high-level move. The two characters raced out in sync. Yet after dashing out, they immediately pulled a distance between them. It wasn't a coincidence. This was obviously a combination that the Battle Mage duo were trained to do. The opponent they teamed up in challenging was the person, who had brought Battle Mages to the pinnacle.

Boom boom boom!

Lord Grim swept the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella, and three artillery shells were sent towards the two challengers from the umbrella's tip.

This attack couldn't stop Dragon Breaks the Rank's momentum at all, but Lord Grim was able to fly a great distance backwards using Anti-Tank Missiles' recoil. He then swung the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella up over his head his head and a Rotor Wing twirled above his head as he flew up into the sky. The moment his feet left the ground, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf arrived. When he saw Lord Grim flying up, he readjusted Evil Annihilation's trajectory, but he was too late. One Autumn Leaf speedily swept across, but hit nothing. Combat Form, who was a step slower, naturally ended up in a similar situation. However, the two Dragon Breaks the Ranks still came out from below, causing him to sway to and fro due to the strong winds from the attacks. The force from their attacks could clearly be seen.

While rocking in midair, Lord Grim retracted the Rotor Wing and unsheathed his tachi. He tilted his body in mid air and used a Sword Draw towards the two, who had just used a high-level skill.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks could be quickly cancelled with no ending lag, and Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei's reactions were very quick. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form jumped to the left and right respectively. ,dodging the sword slash from Sword Draw.

Falling Light Blade!

Lord Grim used this skill afterwards, aiming for the space between the two characters. The skill had a small attack range, but it was just enough to reach the two.

But because it was only just enough to reach them, One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form only had to take a step back in order to escape from the attack range. Two spears glinted as they crossed at an angle towards Lord Grim.

Slide Kick!

Lord Grim didn't pause after Falling Light Blade and slipped away with a Slide Kick. By matching skills across different classes, he used the most prominent feature of an unspecialized. When Excellent Era learned they were going against Ye Xiu's unspecialized, they trained specifically for him. The players in Team Excellent Era were all familiar with what skills an unspecialized could use. This was done by interpreting the unspecialized as the 25th class.

Even though they were familiar with the possible skills available to an unspecialized, Excellent Era, the team who was most familiar with Ye Xiu, was unable to predict how Ye Xiu would use the skills. When Ye Xiu was in the team, he focused his efforts on Battle Mages. However, this was only 1/24 of his battle capabilities when applying their prior knowledge to his unspecialized. By changing his class, Excellent Era's familiarity towards Ye Xiu became extremely limited.

A Slide Kick after Falling Light Blade?

Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei's reactions were relatively quick, but still a beat too slow. The spears the two characters held weren't able to catch Lord Grim.

After Lord Grim dashed away with the Slide Kick, he threw a grenade behind him. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form leapt aside once again, and the explosion's flames flashed between the two characters. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form turned around to chase him, but a purple fog rose up after they took two steps. They happened to step onto a Poison Gas Trap. The two were completely unaware when Lord Grim had planted this trap.

The stadium bubbled with excitement. Everyone thought Ye Xiu's Lord Grim would immediately find a chance to break away and leave, but from what they were seeing, this guy was carrying out a 1v2!

The audience had an omniscient view, so they also knew that the other members of Happy were pushing towards Excellent Era to ambush their Cleric.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

There'll be two more chapters tonight

Chapter 1035: Cut Off From the Team

The team competition between Happy and Excellent Era had completely unfolded. In the beginning, Excellent Era nipped at Happy's heels, refusing to let up until they finally caught up and started attacking, but the crowd could see that Team Happy's Ye Xiu was performing a 1v2, while the other four were preparing to ambush Excellent Era from the rear.

Team Excellent Era was clearly unaware of it. Xiao Shiqin had just realized that he wasn't being daring enough, so he adopted a more proactive attitude. On the other hand, Team Happy had already changed their strategy.　　

The commentators Pan Lin and Li Yibo saw these changes, but restrained themselves from making any early conclusions. It was only when the movements of Team Happy's Soft Mist, Dawn Rifle, One Inch Ash, and Little Cold Hands became very obvious did they dare to comment on it.

"How unexpected.... It's simply too unexpected." Li Yibo sighed, "We were just talking about how Team Excellent Era was playing a bit too conservatively, unlike a strong team. In the blink of an eye, it's Happy that's moving out in an imposing manner. Happy's ace player is pinning down Excellent Era's main force, while the others are preparing for a sneak attack from the rear. This is a standard strategy for a powerhouse team with a top-tier ace player!!"

Li Yibo's statement woke up many people.　　

Indeed, Happy's current strategy was a standard powerhouse strategy. By using a top player, a character to pin down as many opponents as possible, would allow for more openings to attack. This principle was applicable to many sports. For example, in basketball, a skilled player might have two or three defenders on him, giving his other teammates more openings and opportunities to score.

But the problem was that the powerhouse should be Team Excellent Era! But in this match, it was Happy employing this strategy. Wasn't that kind of weird?

"For this strategy to work, the ace player's performance is crucial! Ye Xiu probably isn't a stranger towards this strategy, but the problem is that the current him is no longer the Battle God Ye Qiu from before. Right now, he's facing a pincer attack from Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei. One Autumn Leaf doesn't need to be mentioned. Even Qiu Fei's Combat Form is a formidable character. Can Ye Xiu hold on?" Pan Lin spoke swiftly.

Can he hold on?

The answer didn't matter. Team Excellent Era's rear had already caught on fire. Team Happy's timing had been perfectly executed; they didn't let Ye Xiu take too pressure alone. His main purpose was to draw the attention of Team Excellent Era and have them pull away from each other.

Now, Happy's group of four got into position and charged forward without any hesitation.　

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

By the time Shen Jian noticed the ambush, Soft Mist's spear had already arrived. Excellent Era thought that Dawn Rifle and One Inch Ash were ahead of them, but those two had now suddenly appeared at their flank within attack range.

Shen Jian's responsibility was to defend their healer, so he naturally stepped forward and acted as a meat shield. He had his Striker step forward and shield Zhang Jiaxin's Cleric with his body.

Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks hit him square in the stomach, but it failed to send him flying. The instant that Shen Jian stepped forward, he immediately activated Reinforced Iron Bones. Under this skill's effect, his Striker wouldn't be pushed back by the knockback. Immediately afterwards, he made his counterattack towards Soft Mist. Suddenly, a Satellite Beam descended from the sky, completely enveloping him. Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle had shot out a high-level skill in coordination with Soft Mist's attack.　

Tang Rou didn't fight with Shen Jian. She had Soft Mist circle around and attack Zhang Jiaxin's Cleric, Woven Shadow.

Zhang Jiaxin deserved to be the healer for a powerhouse like Team Excellent Era. he didn't panic. In the team competition, the healer was often a priority target. Staying calm in these situations was a fundamental trait that every healer needed. As someone qualified to be part of a powerhouse's starting line up, he obviously wouldn't be lacking in this regard.

The instant Shen Jian did his job, Zhang Jiaxin had his Cleric retreat. In these situations, the healer needed to win as much time as possible because no team would let their healer die so easily. When a healer was attacked, the team would immediately come to save him, so the healer needed to minimize the losses they would take during this period of time and coordinate with his teammates coming to the rescue.

As Zhang Jiaxin had Woven Shadow retreat, he grasped his current situation. Excellent Era's formation was still intact. As soon as Happy launched their ambush, Life Extinguisher changed directions and went back to assist his team's Cleric. This was already enough to make Zhang Jiaxin feel at peace.

3v4. With Excellent Era's strength, Zhang Jiaxin felt like there shouldn't be any problem.

With this support, Zhang Jiaxin became even more calm. When he saw Soft Mist charge directly towards him, he had his Woven Shadow retreat even faster. Kiting Tang Rou for some time was doable for Zhang Jiaxin, but doing that wasn't smart. Zhang Jiaxin grasped Happy's formation. Tang Rou's Soft Mist was at the very front and, from what he understood, despite this player being very pretty, her aggressiveness on stage didn't lose out to any male player. Zhang Jiaxin had his Woven Shadow continue to retreat. He wanted to lure Soft Mist in further to pull her away from her team. That way, when Excellent Era counterattacked, she would become Happy's burden.

In this short instant, being able to come up with this kind of plan was enough to show his worth as an experienced player, but when he saw the way Soft Mist was holding her spear, Zhang Jiaxin suddenly felt like something wasn't right.

"Behind you!" Before Zhang Jiaxin could yell out his warning, Soft Mist already turned around 180 degrees and thrust forward with her spear. Magic waves surged forth. It was a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. At this distance, it would be a back attack.

Hit!

Shen Jian had been struggling due to the combo from Dawn Rifle's Satellite Beam. At the same time, he had to pay attention to all of the other members of Happy. Soft Mist didn't attack him and instead circled around, so he naturally thought that she was going for their Cleric. As a result, he didn't even think that Soft Mist would be circling around to attack him from behind. It was an extremely powerful attack too.　

After being hit, he was sent flying away. By activating Reinforced Iron Bones, he could resist the effects of most attacks, but a high-level skill like Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had grab priority, the one flaw of Reinforced Iron Bones.

He was sent flying. As a result, it wasn't Soft Mist splitting apart from the team, but him. He landed in a location, where Qiao Yifan had set up numerous ghost boundaries. From this, it could be seen that Happy had been plotting a one-wave offense the entire time.

Chapter 1036: Bypass

Poor Zhang Jiaxing played a Cleric. In this situation, he could only support Shen Jian and help him endure, but couldn't turn the tides. If he wasn't careful, he might even get caught up in it himself.

The hesitant Zhang Jiaxing didn't dare have his Cleric, Woven Shadow, get any closer. Right now, all he wanted was for Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher to hurry back over. However, considering Happy's detailed strategic arrangements, there was little chance that they would've neglected to think of such a situation. Although Ye Xiu wasn't here, Tang Rou and the other three still fought methodically. After Shen Jian's Striker was sent into one of One Inch Ash's ghost boundaries, Qiao Yifan didn't hesitate to sent a relentless barrage of attacks. In an instant, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash shot up on the DPS charts to first place. Somehow, the one who headed Happy's offensive as the main DPS was a Phantom Demon. This was something that was completely unforeseen to most people.

No matter if it was Zhang Jiaxing or Shen Jian, the two were more focused on Soft Mist, who had led the charge when ambushing. They had neglected the Phantom Demon, which was usually a supporting role, and now they were paying the price. After falling into One Inch Ash's ghost boundaries, Successive Strike's health had immediately plummeted. When One Inch Ash then triggered Ghost Feast, Happy's Cleric, Little Cold Hands, had even given Successive Strike a Holy Commandment. Tang Rou's Soft Mist and Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle took this instant to strike with their strongest skills as well.

Boom!

The explosions created by Launchers had the most impressive sound effects, and spirits wrecked havoc amongst the flashing light. Soft Mist's valiant figure was blurred and engulfed by smoke, and Shen Jian was at a loss as to where to strike, only able to clearly see his character's health falling rapidly.

As for Woven Shadows?

In that moment, Shen Jian had even forgotten that Woven Shadow was someone he should protect. Instead, he was just hoping that Woven Shadow could hurry up and save him.

Clerics were rather helpless to prevent this sort of offense, but they could help hold the situation steady. To Zhang Jiaxing, it looked like Happy was pulling Shen Jian's Successive Strike to one side while attacking. It looked a little like a street brawl, where you first pulled your victim into an alleyway to beat up.

The reason for pulling a victim into an alleyway was to avoid witnesses. Happy's current actions were, naturally, to get for as much time as possible before Life Extinguisher came to support.

Taking a careful look, Zhang Jiaxing realized that if he just let Shen Jian endure on his own, he'd probably get killed. There was no room for further consideration; he hurriedly had Woven Shadows step up to heal Shen Jian.

Yet the healing spell hadn't been finished before a missile exploded in front of him. Having seen Woven Shadow's actions, Wu Chen immediately swung his canon around to interrupt the healing Zhang Jiaxing had been trying to give.

Interrupting healing was basic knowledge in team competitions. As a player, Wu Chen didn't have any striking talents, but he had great foundations. Since he knew that his natural talent was limited and he wouldn't make any high-end breakthroughs, he made sure he had a solid of a grasp on these basics as possible. His current healing interruption was giving even Excellent Era's healer a hard time. After all, Zhang Jiaxing had no cover right now and was casting heals while completely exposed to the other's canonfire.

Again and again, Woven Shadow's casts for healing were interrupted rhythmically by Dawn Rifle. In the blink of an eye, four casts had already failed.

Zhang Jiaxing felt a deep-seated helplessness and, in the end, could only send out the instant cast Cures. Cures didn't need casting and healed for quite a lot, but consumed a lot of mana and also had long cooldowns. Usually, healers would save them as a last resort, leaving them for when they were truly and direly needed during the match. However, Zhang Jiaxing was helpless in the current situation. If he didn't help Shen Jian hold on, this might become a critical point that would lose them the match. Though, originally, with Zhang Jiaxing's belief that they would have no problem fighting three on four, losing a person first wasn't a problem, he wasn't so optimistic after seeing how much damage Happy could and did deal with their tactics.

Wu Chen had little ability to interrupt the Cures that came down. Though you could focus fire a single target in team competitions, it was hard to take down a character in a single wave of attacks because of healers.

Tang Rou and the others had done their best, but in the end, they didn't manage to wipe out Shen Jian's Successive Strike with this wave of attacks. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher arrived as support with a hail of Air Drops.

Even so, Team Happy was still fighting four against three with an advantage in numbers. However, they didn't loiter and hurriedly fled before Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher got too close.

Team Happy had launched an offensive worthy of a powerhouse team. Their ace player had stalled the main force of their opponents while the others fought fewer with more. Yet in the end, they had retreated in a very un-powerhouse-like manner. In a situation where they had the advantage in numbers, they chose to retreat.

"Ah…" Commentator Pan Lin thought that this was quite the missed chance, "Successive Strike doesn't have much health left…"

"However, Xiao Shiqin has already come back. Under the cover he can provide, Zhang Jiaxing can heal better. The situation will be pulled back to a head on fight. While Happy has the advantage in numbers, what about in skill and character strength? Especially since healing is a huge factor in team competitions. Happy's healer isn't all that skilled!" Li Yibo commented.

"That's true," Pan Lin agreed with a nod, "If this was a powerhouse team of a similar strength to Excellent Era, this tactical ambush might've became a decisive point to the match!"

"Not necessarily," Li Yibo said, smiling, "If this really was a team that matched Excellent Era in strength, they probably wouldn't handle things the same way. Look, after the ambush, only Xiao Shiqin ran to support, but Qiu Fei and Sun Xiang are still there sticking to Ye Xiu!"

"Seems like Excellent Era feels that the three of them are enough to deal with the four of Happy!"

"That's one of the reasons. Another is that Excellent Era doesn't want to waste this chance where Ye Xiu is alone and without support! Who is the largest threat in Happy to Excellent Era? It's, of course, Ye Xiu. If they can send him out of the match early, then the ending of this match would be set. I think Happy has neglected to consider this aspect. All they thought of was how Ye Xiu could be a diversion, but forgot that this was also giving their opponent a chance!" Li Yibo said.

"Alright, let's have a look at the situation over there…" Pan Lin said.

For the broadcast, this sort of situation was rather troublesome. This was because the battle had split into two. They might have cut to Happy's ambush, but Ye Xiu's exchange with Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had never stopped!

"Seems like Ye Xiu's situation isn't looking good!" Pan Lin said when the shot switched back to the battle over there.

　

This was originally a very interesting one versus two. Weren't Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei both Ye Xiu's successors? It was rare that there would be a chance for them to brawl undisturbed like this in a team competition. However, when the shot switched over, they saw Ye Xiu's Lord Grim curled up into a ball shooting out from between One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form with an Aerial Fire. The sight of such an incredibly precise technique made Pan Lin's scalp tingle. He didn't even have the time to play up this face-off. They had already fought for so long. The climax might've already gone by.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

　

Right after Lord Grim darted out through the gap, Combat Form followed with a powerful technique, his spear heading directly for Lord Grim's chest. The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella immediately changed forms and Lord Grim used a Guard in midair, accurately blocking the attack. Then his umbrella swiftly returned to gun form and fired to add momentum to what Dragon Breaks the Ranks had given him. Lord Grim flew backwards lightning fast and the stab One Autumn Leaf had tried to give after Combat Form's attack hit air.

After landing, Lord Grim didn't bother engaging the two any longer, turning and fleeing. Everyone could see that in Happy's team chat, the four had informed Ye Xiu that their offensive was over. Thus, Ye Xiu naturally wouldn't continue playing with the two. He had never thought of dealing with these two alone.

"Lord Grim has retreated and now on both sides it's Happy retreating while Excellent Era is in pursuit. It was Happy that was on the offensive just now, yet it seems like Excellent Era has the initiative now," Pan Lin noted.

"It can't be helped. If Happy's attack just now had managed to wipe out one of Excellent Era's players then it might not be like this. However, they had managed to do so, letting Excellent Era turn the tides," Li Yibo explained.

"Then that means… the attack by Happy was a failure?"

"Having not achieve what they planned, it should count as a failure. I believe that Happy didn't just aim to deal some damage to Successive Strike and have Woven Shadow expend some mana, right? Such a grandiose set up, even putting Ye Xiu in danger, it wouldn't be worth it."

"Ok, so now Happy is trying to throw their pursuers off on both sides," Pan Lin said as the shot switched between the two sides.

　

"At the moment, the four over here aren't doing so well! They have the advantage in numbers, meaning that their movement is more restricted, and their movement speed as a whole has dropped."

"In this situation, Happy probably won't be able to throw off their pursuers. I'm afraid that they'll probably have to go all-out to hold on," Li Yibo said.

"Now let's check on Ye Xiu… Ah, he threw them off! Lord Grim's movement speed shouldn't have such a big advantage against One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form… How did he do it?" The switching of the shot somehow managed to miss out on Lord Grim escaping from the two Battle Mages, surprising Pan Lin greatly. It was a good thing that there wasn't anything substantial happening currently, so they had the time to playback. Thus, the process of Ye Xiu throwing off his pursuers was replayed.

　

"Seems like it's still old ginger that's more spicy*..." After watching, Li Yibo sighed.

Ye Xiu hadn't raced with the two, but instead used the environment to his advantage. He had clearly known where to go when first retreating. As expected, after running into an area with a lot of cover, Lord Grim vanished from the two's view with a few turns. And now, Lord Grim had already skipped town while One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form were still running in circles back there!

Even at hide-and-seek, God Ye Xiu's skill was at the top of the top, making people awestruck. Sun Xiang might also be a God at the top, but in this situation, he stood no chance.

"Ye Xiu's escaped." Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had to inform the others through the team chat.

Hearing this, Xiao Shiqin's heart stuttered.

Could it be… Xiao Shiqin hoped that his guess was incorrect.

"Stop the pursuit! Coordinates, regroup," Xiao Shiqin hurriedly ordered in the team chat.

Chapter 1037: Unrescuable

They say that team competitions are ever changing with all sorts of playstyles, but these differences never deviated from a set of standards. In the end, all these changing elements were geared towards creating the eventual situation of many against few, strong against weak.

Seeing the coordinates given by Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, Xiao Shiqin wasn't just anxious anymore, he was shocked.

The distance between them had been drawn out so far, and how did that happen? Xiao Shiqin's three person group had chased the four members of Happy while Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei pursued Ye Xiu.

That's right. This happened through their chase of Happy.

This was the finals of the Challenger League, not ten random players going five on five in the in-game arena. When retreating from being chased, you had to be tactical, too, and not just run around like a headless chicken. If Happy's path of retreat was planned out, then that meant that Excellent Era's split was intentionally caused by Happy. Then, Ye Xiu easily threw Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei off his tail. If he didn't realize something was wrong by now, then Xiao Shiqin's tactical sense would be terrible and he wouldn't deserve to be known as one of the Four Master Tacticians.

"Regroup!" After Xiao Shiqin sent some coordinates in the team chat, he and his two teammates didn't bother with Happy's four anymore and quickly turned to leave. Yet they had just turned when Happy's four person team that had been fleeing clumsily suddenly turned to launch an energetic counterattack, chasing after the three and taking advantage of their situations. Their attacks in pursuit were smooth and well-versed; it was clear that they had practiced specifically for such a situation. Xiao Shiqin's heart fell further.

Yet the three of them hadn't gotten very far before a figure flashed in front of them.

There were only so many characters on the field, so who other than Lord Grim could appear at this time?

　

As expected!

Xiao Shiqin now knew that his guess was completely correct. They had, once again, fallen into Happy's trap. It seemed like the wave of attacks that they had launched was more than satisfactory, but Happy's scheme didn't end there. They had long since prepared for the next step. After pulling Excellent Era's two groups far apart enough to be out of support range, Ye Xiu would throw his opponents off his tail to regroup with them first, once again turning this into many against few.

After giving their exact coordinates, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei would also run over as fast as possible. However, before then, Xiao Shiqin's three person group had to deal with an offensive from these five. It might seem like five people was just one more person than four, but the problem was that this time, Ye Xiu was there. The Ye Xiu that was even more of a threat than the rest of Happy put together.

A pincer attack.

"Charge through!" Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher was the first to attack. Shen Jian's Striker, Successive Strike, followed, fists swinging. Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Woven Shadow, wasn't idle either, using the skills that Clerics had to harass the character blocking their way.

Ye Xiu was scary, but if he was just blocking the way on his own, he can't block us all, right?

There might be people in pursuit behind them, but Excellent Era's three were still very confident against Ye Xiu's blockade and the three charged forwards together.

As expected, Ye Xiu alone couldn't block all three of them. They were all pro players, not normal players in the online game. Not only did he fail to block them, Lord Grim also received significant damage against the three's charge.

Breakthrough, regroup with Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, then turn back and crush Happy. That's what Xiao Shiqin had planned, but then he looked left and right. Shen Jian's Striker, Successive Strike, had charged through, but where was Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Woven Shadow?

　

Xiao Shiqin hurriedly looked back with Life Extinguisher and immediately felt like crying.

As expected, Ye Xiu didn't have the power to block all three of them, so he hadn't bothered trying. He only wanted to block one of them. Life Extinguisher and Successive Strike had broken through, but Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow had been blocked by Lord Grim. It was totally worth the damage that he had taken.

Dragon Tooth, Sky Strike, Falling Flower Palm.

　

Turning his view, Xiao Shiqin saw Lord Grim smoothly execute the simple three-hit Battle Mage combo. After Woven Shadow was hit by Falling Flower Palm, he was immediately blown far away. Happy's other four had managed to catch up by then. Soft Mist jumped, spear in hand and used a Circle Swing to catch the airborne Woven Shadow, swinging him in a circle before smashing him to the ground.

On the ground, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash had already managed to lay down several ghost boundaries. They were like several large pots, emitting the aroma of the Phantom Ghost's power and awaiting ingredients to complete this dish!

Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow was, without a doubt, the long-awaited ingredients. After being thrown into the pot by Soft Mist's Circle Swing, they immediately began cooking. Little Cold Hand's Sacred Fire came down as the spices, then Dawn Rifle blasted attacks at him. The flames were rising!

Woven Shadow was cooked immediately. In such a situation, Clerics had a very hard time saving themselves. As a magic class, most of his skills had to be casted. Thus, when he was being attacked continuously like this, he couldn't use any of those casts. He could only hope for outside help.

Xiao Shiqin was extremely frustrated with his own carelessness. Though it would be hard with their disadvantage in numbers, but they couldn't just leave their healer to die. Life Extinguisher and Successive Strike simultaneously turned to charge back into the fray, but found their way blocked by Lord Grim again.

Xiao Shiqin didn't have time to deal with Ye Xiu. Life Extinguisher sent all his long-ranged skills towards Woven Shadow, but Happy's team ignored them, fighting through Life Extinguisher's attacks.

As for Shen Jian's Successive Strike, he had to get close to deal damage. Being blocked by Lord Grim, he couldn't charge over to help for now. However, in this exchange, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher had managed to get closer. However, for him, getting closer was no different than staying away. Most of his attacks didn't require for him to close in. Even if he used them, no one would pay any heed to it. Even if they had to take more damage, they were determined to kill Woven Shadow.

　

Xiao Shiqin knew very well that this exchange was definitely worth it. It went without saying that he alone wouldn't be able to kill a target when the opponent had a Cleric. Even if he could, it would still be more worth it for their opponents to take out their healer.

Firepower coverage was ignored. Go up to wreck havoc? No matter how bad their opponents were, they still had four people, and Mechanics weren't a class that could charge bodily into an opponent's formation. With Xiao Shiqin's tactical knowledge, he obviously wouldn't do something so mindless.

With a turn of view, Life Extinguisher launched another round of attacks, but this time he focused his firepower on Little Cold Hands, Happy's healer.

As expected of a Master Tactician. In this helpless situation, he decided to surround Wei to save Zhao*. How could Happy just leave their healer to be attacked?

Team Happy really did just ignore their healer being attacked, speeding up their attacks on Woven Shadow. Xiao Shiqin felt like crying. Was Woven Shadow really unrescuable? Kill the opponent's healer as an exchange? The problem was, there were three people surrounding and attacking Woven Shadow who was helpless. As for his side? It was just his Life Extinguisher attacking Little Cold Hands alone. Even though his technique was good enough to make Little Cold Hands helpless, his DPS couldn't compare to the combined DPS of three characters. Plus, he had been late in striking. If his opponents killed Woven Shadow first and then went over to support Little Cold Hands, then wouldn't all his hard work be for nothing?

In these crucial times, Xiao Shiqin was quick and decisive. Life Extinguisher abruptly turned his fire towards Lord Grim.

This action was very confusing to everyone. The commentators, Pan Lin and Li Yibo analyzed this as trying to kill off Lord Grim, exchanging a Cleric for Team Happy's ace.

The two used a very questioning and uncertain tone when saying this. Was Ye Xiu the type that could be killed so easily? Under Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei's combined offense, Ye Xiu had managed to play a graceful game of hide and seek and threw them off his tail. Even when hopelessly outnumbered, he still had very strong self-preservation skills. Trying to take out Lord Grim wasn't even as feasible as trying to take out Little Cold Hands.

Yet, Xiao Shiqin's intentions soon became very clear. Turning his fire on Lord Grim and attacking wildly had given Shen Jian a chance to slip away. Successive Strike charged past Lord Grim, ignoring all else, and towards the enemy's formation.

Xiao Shiqin also took this chance to change focus again, showering Soft Mist and the others. This time, it provided cover for Shen Jian's Striker's charge and Tang Rou and co's encirclement was finally broken open.

Zhang Jiaxing was an experienced pro as well, not a weakling that needed to be constantly protected in the online game. He took the chance to dart out of the opening. Xiao Shiqin was delighted and hurried to provide suppressing fire. Woven Shadow was like a little lamb that had finally found its way home, stumbling and tripping as he shot towards Life Extinguisher.

The two regrouped and immediately turned to flee. They hadn't taken two steps when Xiao Shiqin suddenly realized something was missing. Turning his view to look, he was close to bursting into tears. They might have pulled Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow out, but Shen Jian's Striker, Successive Strike had been trapped in.

The audience was stunned.

This was Xiao Shiqin! Because of him and him alone, an ordinary team like Thunderclap had become a regular visitor of the playoffs. This team had managed to continuously cause trouble for the powerhouses. They could cause a headache for any team.

Yet now they were so careless when playing now. They had lost their Cleric a moment ago. Now that they had picked their Cleric back up, they lost their Striker.

Normal characters weren't as valuable as healers, but they couldn't just leave him there either, right? There was a total headcount of six on each side. Losing one meant losing a portion of their strength. Many team competitions had ended with one team losing one member and then spiralling downhill, unable to hold on.

Xiao Shiqin helplessly had Life Extinguisher turn back and Zhang Jiaxing couldn't ignore this either. He wasn't a helpless rescued princess; he was here to help out on the field.

Rescuing Shen Jian's Striker would be easier than rescuing a healer. After all, Strikers had great offensive capabilities and could easily find an opening with assistance from outside.

With Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Woven Shadow, helping out with Sacred Fire and similar skills, Successive Strike finally broke out. Like Woven Shadow before, he hurried towards the warm embrace of his team.

"Careful!!" Xiao Shiqin hurriedly type out that message, but didn't manage to help Shen Jian. Lord Grim suddenly came in from an angle and used a Circle Swing with his Myriad Manifestations Umbrella to impale Successive Strike and, running and swinging him about, threw Successive Strike back into the encirclement.

After going in this massive circle, would the first to die in the team competition still be Successive Strike?

"Keep up his health!!" Xiao Shiqin was like a commander in a dungeon, yelling at the healer to keep his health stable.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

TN: Surrounding Wei to save Zhao comes from an event in the warring states where the army laid siege to Wei to force their troops to retreat from Zhao, thus saving Zhao. - Jouissance

Chapter 1038: Emergency Substitution

Everyone was struck dumb.

In the group arena, Excellent Era had only won one point. This was already inconsistent with the expectations of many people, but what about now? Unexpectedly, Team Happy continuously held the initiative, dominating the whole way, whereas Excellent Era was forced to constantly run for their lives. Just looking at the current situation, just who was the powerhouse here? Who was the grassroots team?

Many in the audience had wanted to see Happy emerge victorious, because it would be an exciting upset. However, seeing the scene before them, it really did seem inconceivable. Yet, this was something they were looking forward to, so obviously it would be something that made them excited. The stadium wasn't only made up of Excellent Era fans; this wasn't Team Excellent Era's home ground.

Only, these audience members, who wanted to see Happy succeed, couldn't really be called Happy's fans. Truthfully, they only wanted to see a major upset. Thus, they wouldn't act like Happy's true fans and recklessly cheer for the team. Since Happy's chances really weren't optimistic, this kind of cheering could easily end with them getting their faces slapped. False fans would obviously be willing to risk this.

Except now, Happy had actually grasped an advantage during the team competition. These spectators, who were only looking for an upset, were also beginning to stir. Those who were more hot-blooded had already started cheering. Gradually, the others followed suit, expressing what they truly wished in their hearts. They too began loudly shouting encouragement. On the flip side, Excellent Era's fans, seeing their team's passive movements, could only sit stupidly.

Originally, they had been prepared to cheer to add to Excellent Era's beautiful performance. Now, with the team acting so passively, it would be more like sending help at the darkest hour.** They weren't mentally prepared for this! Thus, in that instant, the stadium was suddenly filled with loud voices cheering for Happy, drowning out the voices of Excellent Era fans who had been distracted. It seemed like ages before they reacted, desperately raising their voices to cheer for Excellent Era.

Often, cheers from fans in the stadium would be a sort of catalyst for the players on stage. However, Glory was an exception to this, because the players would be completely sealed within their player booths. They weren't able to hear anything going on in the stadium. Although the reasoning behind this was simple, the fans' wishful thinking still caused them to believe that their cheers would somehow transfer strength to their players. At the same time, the pro players didn't do anything to deny this. Even if they couldn't hear any of this support, it wouldn't do them any good to betray their fans good intentions.

At this very moment, the stadium echoed with two equally powerful cheers, yet on stage the situation didn't really change.

"Heal! Heal!"

Truthfully, Xiao Shiqin's directions were a bit redundant. At times like this, it wasn't as if Zhang Jiaxing could still just sit and watch! He had long since controlled his Cleric Woven Shadow to heal Successive Strike. Unfortunately, he was a bit late, because Happy's side also wasn't just sitting back and doing nothing. Besides Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was also harassing him non-stop. Zhang Jiaxing had already expended the cooldowns of all of his instantaneous skills. While his chanting skills were off cooldown, the problem was he couldn't find any opportunities to use them. He was constantly interrupted, as if he was dancing from excitement.

"Protect! Protect!"

Zhang Jiaxing also yelled out in the chat.

However, this reminder was just like Xiao Shiqin's earlier reminder to heal. How could Xiao Shiqin not know to shield the Cleric? Of course he knew, but he couldn't do anything. This was because they were currently faced with the existence of an uncontrollable factor ... Team Happy had more people.

Yes, more people. This advantage had been personally cultivated by Ye Xiu from the start, until it reached an utterly heartless degree. Zhang Jiaxing's heals weren't enough. Xiao Shiqin's cover fire wasn't enough. And these two definitely weren't any ordinary players! Zhang Jiaxing was the main healer of Excellent Era, a powerhouse team, and Xiao Shiqin was an All-Star! He had just showed off his military might during the group arena, gracefully retreating off stage when he knew he was finished. Except now, when facing against all of Team Happy, these two seemed to be completely stuck.

But even in a situation like this, as long the two persevered, it wouldn't all be for nothing. Every so often one of Woven Shadow's skills would find an opening and heal a little. Furthermore, Shen Jian was still doing his best to struggle and break free. Although everyone was on edge, at least they still had hope. Yet Xiao Shiqin and Zhang Jiaxing were constantly sending each other warnings in the team channel. The true use of the channel was seen here.

With this kind of shouting, it could be seen that Excellent Era was truly in a dire position. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei began accelerating without any regard for future consequences. For example, even a Dragon Breaks the Ranks was brought out and used as a movement skill. The broadcast switched to a close-up view of the map, showing the two characters moving at a breakneck pace. The audience could see that the time it would take for these two to reach the battlefield could be measured in seconds.

Missing just one final step?

At this moment, this sentence appeared in everyone's minds.*** If these two Battle Mages reached the battlefield in time, they could definitely reverse the situation. Team Happy's characters were really a bit disappointing; at a crucial moment like this, their damage output was really too low. If these characters could stand shoulder to shoulder with the ones from a powerhouse like Excellent Era, perhaps Shen Jian would have been killed already.

Beautiful tactics. Beautiful execution. But in the end, would they lose it all because of useless characters?

At this moment, the silhouettes of One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form could be seen on the horizon. Looking at Successive Strike's health and doing a few quick calculations, Xiao Shiqin quietly let out the breath he had been holding. At the same time, he felt ashamed. Just a while ago, when he was still in Team Thunderclap, he had lost many matches because of this kind disparity in character strength. Back then, he had often fantasized about having a powerhouse character within his grasp. But now, he finally achieved that dream, and he was instead relying on the brute force of the characters. It looked like Happy's beautiful display would soon be thwarted, but right now Xiao Shiqin felt disgusted. This kind of brute force was what he had admired for so long before. But now that he was truly winning only because of this, he couldn't feel any joy.

Happy's characters ...

As Xiao Shiqin wistfully looked at these characters, he was suddenly startled.

What's going on? How come there were only four characters on Happy's side?

Where's the Cleric? Where was Little Cold Hands?

In his haste to protect Woven Shadow and save Shen Jian's Successive Strike, Xiao Shiqin had neglected such a huge change! Now that he suddenly discovered it, his heartbeat quickened, and his mind quickly mapped out this entire region.

Not good!

Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher suddenly rushed forward like a melee character. This move caused Zhang Jiaxing to jump with fright.

Was this the beginning of a counterattack?

But Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei still hadn't reached the battlefield! And even if they had, as a Mechanic, there was no reason for him to jump to the front lines like this!

In the end, Zhang Jiaxing was also stupefied.

A shadow of a person flew into the attackers' encirclement. Yet this character originally shouldn't have appeared.

Steamed Bun Invasion!

Unexpectedly, it was Steamed Bun Invasion!

"When did he appear?" It wasn't just the harried and preoccupied Xiao Shiqin and Zhang Jiaxing who had failed to notice. Even the spectators, with their omniscient view, had been so focused on the fight that they hadn't paid attention to the fact that Happy had actually switched out a player.

At this moment, there was no time for a replay. Steamed Bun Invasion had suddenly joined joined the fight, immediately using Strangle. However, in a crucial moment like this, Happy had actually managed to complete a character substitution?

Cleric Little Cold Hands had withdrawn. Brawler Steamed Bun Invasion had joined the fight.

Happy no longer had the damage output of four characters. They now had five!

It was only after realizing this that Xiao Shiqin had recklessly charged forward. He knew that against the damage output of five characters, Successive Strike wouldn't be able to last until One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrived. He needed to charge in at this moment in order to disrupt the setup.

At this very moment, Happy didn't have a healer either. If they took this opportunity to focus their attacks on one character and managed to take out a lot of health, with the support incoming from Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, perhaps they would be able to swap again.

Just as Xiao Shiqin made this decision, he saw the Myriad Manifestations Umbrella in Lord Grim hand shake ...

Tears streamed down Xiao Shiqin's face ... In his moment of desperation, he had once again forgotten this unspecialized character. An unspecialized's healing capabilities were still weak, but ... no matter how small a mosquito was, it was still flesh. On a professional stage, even a tiny bit could mean the difference between victory and defeat. With him here to heal the team, Happy could likely sustain until they found the chance to switch their healer back in. After all, this position was quite close to a support zone. It was only after Xiao Shiqin become conscious of their current position, after he mapped out the area in his head just now, that he finally realized Happy's intent. However, his realization had arrived a bit late.

Steamed Bun Invasion had joined the fight, and Team Happy's damage output had immediately increased by a level. Every time Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher rushed over, he was blocked by Lord Grim. His ultimate decision to do everything he could to disrupt the situation had also fallen to pieces.

It wasn't possible for Ye Xiu to kill him in an instant, but blocking him and obstructing his disturbance wasn't a problem.

Boom!

Another round of explosions occurred. Shen Jian's Striker finally fell.

After an unbearably bad performance during the group arena, Shen Jian became the first to fall during the team competition. But from a fair point of view, this time, it wasn't really his fault. Facing this kind of trap, any player would find it hard to cope. It was regretful, but competition was just this cruel sometimes. This kind of situation had happened to him, ending his performance in this match here. He hadn't made any eye-catching plays and was even the first to be killed. As far as those who hadn't bothered to ask about the sequence of events were concerned, this was basically the worst performance of the match.

However, up until now, had anyone really performed poorly during this team competition? No, everyone had worked hard to bring out their individual skills, but in a fight, there would always be a winner and a loser. Shen Jian very much regretted being the first one out. He could definitely be called the most unlucky player tonight. WIth this being the most important match of the season for Excellent Era, his performance was really too terrible. Shen Jian sat paralyzed in his seat, as if he could see himself returning to the time when he had been a substitute player.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

TL Note: **The first idiom used, 锦上添花, means to add flowers to embroidery, or to decorate something that is already perfect. The second idiom, 雪中送炭, means to send charcoal in snowy weather, or to provide help in a time of great need.

***The "phrase" mentioned here is actually a chenyu, 功亏一篑. Literally translated, it means that in the process of piling up many hills (usually nine) of dirt, one bucket is missed. Basically it means to almost finish something, but end up missing by just a tiny bit, the last step. --Veriquity

Chapter 1039: Shadow Play

"Steamed Bun Invasion! Strangle! Happy is focusing their attacks! One wave rush! Beautiful!!!"　　

With a fierce battle ongoing, there was no time for the commentators to give any lengthy explanations or play-by-plays. Pan Lin ended up using short and hurried keywords, which helped make the intensity of the match even more clear.　

"Happy... The first kill goes to Happy!!!" He stumbled a bit on this result. Pan Lin wanted to shout that Happy had taken the first point, but he thought about it again and remembered that wasn't how the point system worked anymore! Killing the opponent didn't count as a point. The number of points won depended on how many of your players were left standing at the end of the match. The two methods of calculating points didn't have any impact on the end result, but for the experienced Pan Lin, he felt like calculating points through kills would be more exciting and fun.

I'll give them my recommendation later.

Pan Lin quietly thought to himself. The new tournament format was being tested in the Challenger League. The Alliance was currently taking feedback. As part of the broadcast team, he had quite a lot of authority in this matter. Much of the competitive format was established for the convenience of the broadcast. For this season's potential change, the broadcast had put a good amount of effort into pushing for it.

These thoughts flashed through Pan Lin's head. There was still a match going on. He couldn't spend his time thinking about his recommendation at the moment.

Shen Jian's Successive Strike was killed. Even though the sixth player Wang Ze immediately loaded in, he would appear in the support zone. He would be in the same situation as Sun Xiang and Shen Jian; he needed time to arrive.

For now, Excellent Era was at a one player disadvantage, but if the situation was calmly looked at, not many would think that Happy was at an advantage.

Excellent Era had one fewer player, but One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form had finally arrived. As for Happy, to make up for their insufficient DPS, they did a character switch. While they had killed Successive Strike, they left behind a hidden danger: Happy didn't have a healer right now.

Admittedly, Lord Grim had healing capabilities, but for a team competition, his healing would be like trying to extinguish a burning cart with a cup of water; it barely counted as support.

Even though Excellent Era lost a player, it was a good time for them to make a strong counterattack.　　

Xiao Shiqin obviously wouldn't miss this opportunity. He had already made preparations for this situation. He couldn't do anything about Lord Grim's healing, but this was their opportunity to give Happy a heavy blow. If Ye Xiu wasn't able to control the situation well enough, it was very possible that Happy would be swept away by Excellent Era in one swoop because Excellent Era's ace player Sun Xiang and his One Autumn Leaf had arrived.

Shattering the Lands!　　

Sun Xiang possessed the spirit of an ace player. One of his teammates had been killed. It didn't matter how strong or confident Excellent Era was, this irrefutable reality was a blow to their morale. The ace player needed to stand out at times like this to turn the tides through a brilliant performance to win back their morale.

As a result, Sun Xiang started off immediately with a high-level skill. One Autumn Leaf leapt high in the air with Evil Annihilation raised up and jumped directly into the middle of Team Happy.

"Scatter!"

Ye Xiu shouted in the team chat.　　

The oppressiveness of Battle God One Autumn Leaf wasn't something any of Team Happy's characters could contend against. The ghost boundaries set up by One Inch Ash wouldn't be effective. Shattering the Lands was an AoE attack. In addition to the possible Landslide effect from Evil Annihilation, he would turn the sky and earth upside down despite being trapped within the ghost boundaries.

Just this single move was enough to force Team Happy to scatter. This was the might of the number one character in the Alliance, Battle God One Autumn Leaf.

The other members of Excellent Era had already started coordinating their attacks with One Autumn Leaf. Qiu Fei's Combat Form followed One Autumn Leaf like a shadow. Excellent Era had never played with dual Battle Mages before. The previous matches hadn't showed anything particularly special about it. It was only until this match did hints of it appear. Qiu Fei's Combat Form was like wingman for One Autumn Leaf. His attacks were a guide for One Autumn Leaf, filling in any holes. This was a very famous playstyle called Shadow Play. However, in the era of stars, it was rarely seen nowadays. Of the 24 All Stars, not one of them were shadows.

It could be said that shadows did the dirty work. They were oftentimes the ones that covered up the mistakes made by ace players. With them, the ace players would perform more brilliantly, but the existence of the shadow was likely to be ignored. Who would be willing to be that type of player? As it turned out, being an invisible shadow also required a very high level of skill. Not just anyone was qualified to take on that role, so very few teams used it because there was no one appropriate for the role.

But Qiu Fei? His skill was solid. A year and a half after Ye Xiu's departure from Excellent Era, he could already contend with Ye Xiu 1v1. He was also a new rookie with no name, so no one was surprised that he was pushed into this position.

But then again, this decision also depended on the team's needs and style.

Tiny Herb and Blue Rain also had incredible rookies with the same class as their team's ace players. However, neither Gao Yingjie nor Lu Hanwen were appointed as shadows for their Gods. They had their own place on the stage. They worked hard to demonstrate their skill and continued to shine brightly.

Neither choice was right or wrong. Objectively speaking, Excellent Era's ace player Sun Xiang was younger. Sun Xiang wasn't like Tiny Herb's Wang Jiexi or Blue Rain's Huang Shaotian who needed to train a successor soon. Sun Xiang was still rising, so a shadow by his side was a very good push forward. The advantages of having a better ace player didn't need to be mentioned. Compared to Tiny Herb and Blue Rain, Excellent Era was very suitable for a Shadow Play. It was just that using Qiu Fei as a stepping stone for Sun Xiang was a bit regrettable.

Then again, gold always shines. Shadows were easily ignored by the general crowd, but they wouldn't escape the eyes of professionals. This was also why the Shadow Play was difficult to maintain. Outstanding shadows were too easily recruited. Just the promise of no longer having to be a shadow was more than enough. If they could have their own stage to shine, who would be willing to remain as a stepping stone?

Qiu Fei was a diligent and steadfast player, so he didn't reject the team's choice. He took on the burden willingly. However, through the Challenger League, Sun Xiang didn't need a shadow to crush his opponents. For Excellent Era, this was their first formidable opponent for their newly formed duo.

But just before, under everyone's watch, the two of them had failed to catch a single player. The two of them had targeted Lord Grim, yet Lord Grim was able to escape from their grasp so easily. Then, Lord Grim ran over to help his teammates kill one of Excellent Era's players.

From how long it took for Lord Grim and how long it took for the two of them to reach the battlefield, it could be seen just how cleanly Ye Xiu was able to escape from them. If not for Xiao Shiqin noticing the change in tactics early on, the two of them might have still been searching for Lord Grim!

It easy to think of what Sun Xiang was feeling like after being played around like that. He had been preparing to show his superiority over Ye Xiu in this team competition. Not yelling at Qiu Fei to move to the side was already a huge improvement for him.

After losing to Ye Xiu in the group arena, Sun Xiang underwent a huge transformation. For the sake of victory, he started to reach a compromise. He abandoned his previous attitude towards his reputation. Victory. Right now, the only desire in his heart was victory.　

The team competition had only just started and Excellent Era was losing. If this was the previous Sun Xiang, he would have become irritated long ago. But now, he was able to maintain his calm and follow Xiao Shiqin's arrangements.

Shattering the Land scattered Team Happy's formation. Qiu Fei's Combat Form seized the opportunity to charge forward. Shattering the Land didn't have that aspect to it, so it was up to him to make up for it.

With this duo joining the battle, Team Excellent Era exploded with fighting strength. Team Happy scattered, but didn't show any plans to counterattack. They clearly didn't want to clash directly with Excellent Era here, even if they had the numbers advantage.

"Focus Dawn Rifle!" Xiao Shiqin gave a new target.

Wu Chen was someone who had never appeared on stage before this point. Xiao Shiqin picked him not because he was underestimating Wu Chen or because Wu Chen was the most convenient target, it was because he recognized that this person was biggest hidden danger to Excellent Era.　

Launcher!

He had noticed it earlier. Was there any class more fitting to partner with Ye Xiu? His Battle Mage and Su Mucheng's Launcher were titled Best Partners every year in the Alliance before his retirement.

Wu Chen couldn't compare to Su Mucheng whether it was in individual skill or character strength, but with Ye Xiu by his side, his fighting strength was vastly improved. In the entire Glory scene, no one understood how to coordinate with Launchers better than Ye Xiu. Even though right now, Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle was mainly just being guided around, Xiao Shiqin didn't think his value stopped there. From Wu Chen's careful harassment to his solid fundamentals that he showed when interrupting their Cleric, Xiao Shiqin was certain that under Ye Xiu's lead, Wu Chen would show even greater potential. And this had never been seen before this match. This sort of unknown variable made Xiao Shiqin feel uneasy. He decided that it would be best to hurry up and get rid of him before his potential erupted.

Sun Xiang had originally planned on targeting Lord Grim, but then he saw Xiao Shiqin's orders…...

Victory! For the sake of victory!

Sun Xiang grinded his teeth as he went against his wishes. When Shattering the Lands ended, he immediately had One Autumn Leaf rush towards Dawn Rifle.

Xiao Shiqin wasn't just someone who ordered people around. All sorts of gadgets poured out from his Life Extinguisher and marched towards Dawn Rifle like an army.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

TKA's #2!!! If we can get to #1 this week or next week, I'll post a special video when the EE vs Happy match ends :)

Chapter 1040: This Again

How fast!

Seeing One Autumn Leaf suddenly turn around and then the famed spear Evil Annihilation flash in front of his eyes, Wu Chen only had this single thought in his mind.

He was just an average player. He didn't have crazy reaction speeds nor insane hand speed. This type of attack was truly hard for him to defend against. He had been carefully maintaining his distance the entire time, but at this moment, One Autumn Leaf was too close. He leaped back in panic while simultaneously preparing to use Aerial Fire, but he felt like it was already too late.

Ding!

A clinging noise sounded.　

The sounds of two weapons clashing felt so real. A scarlet spear stabbed forward and blocked the black Evil Annihilation.

So he's here!

The instant he blocked, Sun Xiang unconsciously thought that he was facing Ye Xiu. The only player in Team Happy that he had his eyes on was Ye Xiu. In his eyes, Ye Xiu was the only one qualified to block his attacks.

But unfortunately, in the next second, Sun Xiang saw his opponent clearly, Soft Mist.

Sun Xiang felt somewhat annoyed.

If it were Ye Xiu's Lord Grim, he might have stopped for a bit to fight him, but seeing that it was Soft Mist, he resolved himself to carry out Xiao Shiqin's orders and take Dawn Rifle out of the match.

At this moment, a stream of fire flowed out from Soft Mist's scarlet spear towards One Autumn Leaf.

Flowing Flame!

Sun Xiang recognized this effect and knew it was a special effect from a weapon. The probability of triggering the effect usually wasn't high, but it looked like the other side was lucky. To think she was able to trigger it with just a single block. But so what?

Sun Xiang ignored the flaming attack. It was just a weapon effect. Was it necessary for the Battle God One Autumn Leaf to dodge it?

One Autumn Leaf didn't retreat and instead advanced. Under Sun Xiang's control, One Autumn Leaf was going to force his way through Soft Mist's interception. Suddenly, Soft Mist's spear pierced through the flames?

Dragon Tooth?

No.

Double Stab?　

No.

Circle Swing?　

Definitely not.

Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart!

This spear aimed for One Autumn Leaf's heart. It was the Level 60 Battle Mage skill, Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart. It was best described as a simple stab, but its might was far greater than a Dragon Tooth.

How could a normal attack be enough to defend against a high-level skill? It definitely couldn't be blocked with just one's body. In the end, Sun Xiang was forced to retreat and leapt backwards twice to just barely dodge the attack. However, Soft Mist wasn't done yet. She was just about to execute her next attack. However, Qiu Fei's Combat Style attacked from the flank, stopping Soft Mist from continuing her assault.

From an outsider's point of view, it was a very normal assistance from a teammate, but in Sun Xiang's eyes, it was disgraceful! Just Soft Mist alone had forced him to require Qiu Fei's assistance?

Sun Xiang was angry. One Autumn Leaf stepped forward one step. Tooth for tooth. He unleashed his own Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart, except compared to Soft Mist's, it was more crafty and fast.

Qiu Fei's Combat Form had been at the front, but when he saw Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf return to attack, he immediately opened up space for him. He followed Xiao Shiqin's orders and thrust his spear at Dawn Rifle.

But with Tang Rou's interception, Wu Chen had seized the opportunity to use Aerial Fire to escape. The army of machines created by Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher rushed forward, but they were stopped by Qiao Yifan's ghost boundaries. The gadgets from Mechanics were far weaker than the summons from Summoners. Many of them were one-time use tools. In addition, ghost boundaries could injure Mechanic gadgets and Summoner summons. As soon as the weak gadgets entered the boundary, there was almost no chance of them leaving. Xiao Shiqin hastily made adjustments. He couldn't let all of these skills go to waste. In the end, he also lost his opportunity to catch Dawn Rifle.

Xiao Shiqin was extremely annoyed. He knew that Ye Xiu had once again been one step ahead of him. Soft Mist's interception, One Inch Ash's trap. Both of them were to protect Dawn Rifle. Happy had guessed that Excellent Era would target him.

He really is…. So troublesome…..

Xiao Shiqin sighed. He wasn't as single-minded as Sun Xiang, but Ye Xiu was undoubtedly the biggest threat in Happy. He didn't lack experience fighting with Ye Xiu. In short, he had lost more times than he won, but back then, Ye Xiu's Excellent Era was much more powerful than his Thunderclap. Xiao Shiqin had been at a clear disadvantage in all of those matches, so even though he lost more times, he was still confident in his ability. But now, the two had switched positions. He was the one with Excellent Era, as for Ye Xiu? His team was a grassroots team even weaker than Thunderclap, but how was the match going? It was beyond anyone's expectations.

God of Glory…

Thinking of Ye Xiu's most spectacular title, Xiao Shiqin didn't need to ascertain Ye Xiu's skill. Ye Xiu had always been a part of a powerhouse like Excellent Era. A powerful team would often cover up how much an individual shined. For example, when Xiao Shiqin lost to Ye Xiu before, he didn't think that it was because he was worse than Ye Xiu. The difference lay in the team's overall strength!

But now, the positions had switched. Why was Excellent Era in such dire straits? This time, there was no excuse!

Dawn Rifle had already escaped. What next?

Xiao Shiqin observed their situation. Mindlessly attacking wasn't a thing. He needed to find a breakthrough point and deal a damaging blow towards Happy.

Bang!

The noise from Falling Flower Palm got Xiao Shiqin's attention. Sun Xiang versus Soft Mist. Sun Xiang was more skilled and had the stronger character, so after a few exchanges, One Autumn Leaf's Falling Flower Palm sent Soft Mist flying. He and Combat Form rushed forward after her.

Dawn Rifle had escaped outside of their attack range, so Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei switched targets to Soft Mist. Listening to the shotcaller was very important in a match, but players weren't wooden dolls who could only do as they were told. Oftentimes, players needed to make decisions based on their circumstances.

Xiao Shiqin noticed the two switch targets already and saw that the situation looked good, so he immediately started attacking Soft Mist as well. Right now, he was the only other attacker on Excellent Era. When those two switched targets, it was easy for him to switch targets too. He didn't need to give anyone instructions. As for Zhang Jiang, he had been healing when needed.

"Go die!" Sun Xiang typed in the public chat. He was clearly not happy about Soft Mist disrupting his plans. He was even angrier that it wasn't Ye Xiu who had blocked him, but this little character.

Sun Xiang and the shadow Qiu Fei, along with Xiao Shiqin's support. This trio wasn't something any one person could defend against, but Tang Rou didn't back down from the fight. She raised her spear and actually stood in an attacking stance.　　

"What a noob…" Sun Xiang remarked disdainfully. She didn't know her own strength and she was going to die for it.　

But this remark caught Xiao Shiqin's eyes. He was startled by it.

Were there noobs among Happy? Perhaps in the past, but right now, how could Ye Xiu let a noob participate in the finals?

Everyone in Happy should be able to see the difference in strength between the two sides, yet no one helped Soft Mist. Was she sacrificing herself to give others time or?

Xiao Shiqin looked around wildly. The others in Happy didn't disperse after Soft Mist became the focus of Excellent Era. They were still in a battle stance.

But what about Lord Grim?

Xiao Shiqin swept the field and discovered that Lord Grim was nowhere to be found!

Lord Grim had been the character that he had been paying close attention to the entire time. His attention had shifted when he switched his target to Soft Mist. During those few seconds, where could he have gone?

He turned 720 degrees and finally found Lord Grim. That guy had stealthily hid behind a tree trunk. Xiao Shiqin had noticed his head sticking out. Then, he saw Lord Grim open his hands. Xiao Shiqin was greatly alarmed and he looked towards where Lord Grim's palms were facing. Woven Shadow! Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow!

"!!!" Xiao Shiqin wasn't able to type out any words. He only had time to warn everyone in this way. Unfortunately, it was too late. Zhang Jiaxing's attention had been focused on One Autumn Leaf's and Combat Form's health. He hadn't noticed that there was an ambush set up for him. The instant that Xiao Shiqin typed out the warning, Woven Shadow flew out.

Cloud Grasping Fist!

The Myriad Manifestations Umbrella opened up. It was a low-level Grappler skill. Ye Xiu had used this method in the match against Team Jade Dynasty to grab the opponent from afar and his target had been Team Jade Dynasty's Cleric.

And this time, Team Excellent Era had actually fallen for this move too.

It was the same technique, but used differently.

With Jade Dynasty, no one had expected that an unspecialized could do this, so Lord Grim had been very brazen. His teammates just needed to get the opposing side's attention for him to use it.

Facing Excellent Era, Ye Xiu had thought about what the opposing side might do and waited patiently until an opportunity arose. Tang Rou's Soft Mist do a 1v3? This wasn't a noob acting rashily. This was bait to attract Excellent Era's attention. With such an advantage, who wouldn't want to take it? Just when they thought that they had an opportunity to kill Soft Mist, their healer was snatched away.　

Was this a trade?

No!

Soft Mist's tenaciousness exceeded their expectations. Three Battle Mages fought. She was in a 1v2 and even though she was losing, her spear danced like flowing water.

What type of hand speed is this?

Seeing Soft Mist's insanely fast rhythm, everyone was dumbfounded.

"How is she… compared to you?" In the crowd, Tiny Herb's Xu Bin suddenly asked his teammate Liu Xiaobie. Hand speed had always been Liu Xiaobie's greatest weapon.

Liu Xiaobie didn't respond. Was it because he didn't feel like responding, or because he felt too embarrassed to admit that his hand speed wasn't as high?

Chapter 1041: A Familiar Scene

Along with Lord Grim's strategic ambush, Soft Mist's performance attracted quite a bit of attention too.　　

Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, and Qiu Fei. Let alone whether she could contend against the three allied together, just daring to block them on her own showed her courage. Besides blocking, she also showed a bit more, letting others know that she wasn't just being sent to her death. How could this type of performance not attract any attention?

Even the three Team Tiny Herb players were focused on Soft Mist. In Team Happy's coordinated ambush, Soft Mist's performance was the cause, while Lord Grim's ambush was the effect. Without Soft Mist restricting the other side's main attackers, how could Lord Grim have escaped Xiao Shiqin's eyes and find an opportunity to set up an ambush?

Therefore, for Team Happy's tactic to work, the key component was actually Soft Mist. By standing out alone, she made Excellent Era think that she was their breakthrough point, but when Excellent Era attacked her, they realized that she wasn't that easy of a target. A short while later, Excellent Era's Cleric was snatched away.

Those paying attention to Happy had placed far too much focus onto Ye Xiu, including Team Excellent Era. Then, for this tactic, the real ace player appeared to be Soft Mist, that lost Soft Mist who had been completely crushed by Xiao Shiqin in the group arena.

When the Cleric Woven Shadow was snatched away, the 1v3 danger that Soft Mist had been in was instantly gone. This was relieving a besieged ally by attacking the besieger's home base. Excellent Era was already behind. They definitely couldn't let this trade happen. They needed to go rescue their Cleric.

Life Extinguisher's attacks were the first to arrive. He was their long-ranged character after all. He didn't need to move. He just turned around and started attacking. But then Lord Grim followed up with a Toss and flung Woven Shadow, making Life Extinguisher's attacks look like fireworks raining down on Woven Shadow. When Woven Shadow landed, One Inch Ash's ghost boundaries had already been set…..

Happy executed this team combo very smoothly. It looked as if they had practiced this thousands of times. This combo had been used for fighting for wild bosses in the game.

Pro matches were high-level matches, but in terms of chaos, wild boss fights were on a whole new level. Team Happy's players had coordinated with each other, created opportunities for their allies, and found opportunities to attack in these wild boss fights. An important part of killing wild bosses was keeping the boss's aggro under control. Where did this aggro come from? From continuous attacks. It was only by maintaining continuous attacks could the boss's aggro be stabilized.　

These types of combos were what Team Happy was best at. Today, their targets had been changed from bosses to pro players, but it didn't seem like it was any different. After sending Shen Jian's Successive Strike away, Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow was next.

But this time, Excellent Era wasn't as weak. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher quickly turned and switched targets. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei weren't slow either. The two characters wanted to rescue from a different direction, but Tang Rou was still there. She immediately had her Soft Mist intercept them.

Sun Xiang naturally knew that drawing their focus towards Soft Mist had been a trap. Seeing that she still refused to let go, his heart blazed with anger!

"Get out of here!" The angry Sun Xiang's explosiveness was quite frightening. Numerous Chasers on One Autumn Leaf exploded, instantly creating an eleven hit combo. Qiu Fei's Combat Form followed up with a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky, comboing it with Sun Xiang's burst.

Soft Mist took heavy damage from this combo, but the Rising Dragon Soars the Sky also pushed her to the side.　　

Sun Xiang had originally planned on continuing to attack Soft Mist, but then saw Combat Form force her back. Annoyance flickered in his heart as he had One Autumn Leaf chase after her, but after the first step, he suddenly remembered that rescuing their healer should be their priority. He immediately turned around and headed towards Woven Shadow. As for Qiu Fei's Combat Form? He just quietly followed alongside One Autumn Leaf. Only a professional's eyes would have been able to see the significance of that Rising Dragon Soars the Sky.

That Rising Dragon Soars the Sky had interrupted One Autumn Leaf's combo. If this was a fight against Soft Mist, it would have definitely been a mistake. It would be a good point to review after the match, but in this situation, the interrupt reminded Sun Xiang of what was more important. Sun Xiang clearly reacted to it. If not, he might really have chased after Soft Mist and delayed the rescue of their Cleric.

Those who weren't skilled enough might not have noticed the significance of this move. They might have just thought of it as Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei working together to get rid of the obstacle in their way. Li Yibo saw One Autumn Leaf make that step though and sighed: "Sun Xiang appears to be a bit hesitant! For such a crucial moment, he really should be more decisive, even if it ends with attacking Soft Mist. Wavering like this probably isn't a good sign."

It was hard to say if Li Yibo saw through Qiu Fei's move, but the point he made on his hesitation was a good point. Hesitation would affect the players and waste time. When they started rescuing their healer, if they thought "if we had gotten rid of Soft Mist before", it would just be a distraction. If a player wasn't fully focused, a player might only be able to perform at 70-80%. The player might miss small details and openings. They might make more mistakes too. Li Yibo's words were frightening to hear.

Luckily, Excellent Era was using a shadow. Sun Xiang would always have a Qiu Fei alongside him. In terms of age, Sun Xiang wasn't actually much older than Qiu Fei. But in terms of stability, the young Qiu Fei was much more steady than Sun Xiang. This was also why Excellent Era chose to employ a Shadow Style. From a tactical perspective, making up for each other's weaknesses was very powerful.

Lord Grim snatched Woven Shadow with Cloud Grasping Fist and then tossed him. Although he was able to fling Woven Shadow a certain distance away, there was a limit to what he could do. In the match against Team Jade Dynasty, this move had allowed them to kill off their opponent's healer. But today, the opponent was Team Excellent Era. Once their healer was grabbed, they immediately switched targets. Previously, Happy had stopped Jade Dynasty's rescue attempts, but they had no way of stopping Excellent Era. After sending Soft Mist flying away, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei reached Happy's cooking pot. Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun's Steamed Bun Invasion were currently beating up Woven Shadow. Bullying a healer was something every Glory player was good at.

When One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrived, One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun Invasion completely ignored them.

You want to kill him before you die? It won't be that easy!

Sun Xiang glanced at Woven Shadow's health. It wasn't that low! Zhang Jiaxing wasn't an ordinary healer. Even without any protection, he wouldn't be bullied so easily. If he had been against two normal players in the game, it would be hard to say who would be bullying who! Zhang Jiaxing was doing his best dodging and attacking, keeping up his health. When he saw One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrive, he immediately started moving to regroup with them. Suddenly, he was grabbed from behind and tossed back with a Back Throw.

Zhang Jiaxing turned and saw Lord Grim. His mix and match equipment was always funny to look at. But in this instant, he saw this figure rush towards One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form. When he saw him fighting with his two allies, he went into a bit of a daze.

It wasn't until Steamed Bun Invasion punched him did he wake up.

Not anymore...

This figure was no longer the one helping defend him.　

Zhang Jiaxing was Excellent Era's healer. When Ye Xiu was in the team, how could there not have been many times when Ye Xiu had come to rescue him. Even though the character was different and the equipment was different, Lord Grim charging forward bravely reminded Zhang Jiaxing of when Ye Xiu had been on the team and led them in battle. He had been protected by this very person.

But now, this person, who he had once hoped would never fall, had become the sign of his death.

Die or not die?　　

For a moment, Zhang Jiaxing truly was in a daze. Then, he saw a field of light engulf Lord Grim.　

Life Extinguisher?

It clearly wasn't. Excellent Era's goal was to rescue the Cleric. If Life Extinguisher was going to attack, the attacks would be focused on covering up Woven Shadow. From where the light came from, it was long-ranged support from Dawn Rifle. At the same time, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash laid down a ghost boundary, not for Woven Shadow, but to help Lord Grim.

Can I escape? Seeing One Inch Ash split his attention over there, Zhang Jiaxing looked for an opening. But then Steamed Bun Invasion came out of nowhere and pinned him to the ground with a Tyrannical Chain Punch.

It looks like One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form aren't going to be able to get here. What about Life Extinguisher?

Zhang Jiaxing struggled as he looked over. Life Extinguisher was on his way, but he was blocked midway. It was Soft Mist! After being sent flying away by One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form, she quickly got up. Instead of looking for revenge, she switched targets to Life Extinguisher.

When Xiao Shiqin saw that it was Soft Mist, his head started hurting. In the group arena, he had easily beaten Tang Rou, but he couldn't use the same strategy in the team competition. If he took Soft Mist away and kited around her, by the time he got back, there would only be a corpse left!

Life Extinguisher wasn't able to reach Woven Shadow. Dawn Rifle would sometimes assist Lord Grim, sometimes take care of Life Extinguisher, and even help out Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadow.

This strategy...

Zhang Jiaxing stared blankly. This is too familiar…..　

Screen Cannon!

The Screen Cannon was Team Excellent Era's most used tactic. It revolved around the Launcher, who provided large-scale support. To break this tactic, restricting the Launcher was crucial. However, the Launcher attacked from afar. It was difficult for melee classes to go over and suppress him. And with Excellent Era's situation? Woven Shadow wouldn't be able to hold on much longer. There was no time to break through the Screen Cannon through traditionally methods.

Breakthrough! Hurry up... Zhang Jiaxing started to panic.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

If we get first, Jouissance will be able to do ~12 chaps per week for the following week, but only if we are still first at the end of the week (for the next few months)! Unfortunately, I can only contribute ~5 chaps per week, and I won't be able to do anymore than that unless I can find something to do over the upcoming summer. TLDR; TKA #1 -> 17 chapters the next week

Chapter 1042: Box Tactics

"They're actually using Screen Cannon..." Li Yibo's words rushed out in a breath of surprise upon realizing what Team Happy was doing, but then wasn't sure what else to say. He had a strange feeling. From the performance the two teams had displayed today, overall, Happy was more like Excellent Era while Excellent Era… Excellent Era didn't really seem like much of anything.

That's right. The current Excellent Era wasn't the same Excellent Era that it used to be anymore. In the current team, only the ace character One Autumn Leaf and Cleric Woven Shadows were from the original roster. The rest of the characters had all been switched out.

Originally, everyone saw Excellent Era as a team with three All-Star players. However, from the current team build, it was clear that Su Mucheng's Launcher had lost her place on the team.

Was this a tactical decision? It didn't seem certain.

Though the Shadow Play was a very good way to make up for Sun Xiang's shortcomings while utilizing his ability to the fullest, in the Screen Cannon strategy that Excellent Era once employed, Launchers gave the best coordination and support, and that was Su Mucheng's most striking characteristic as a player.

Was it that they didn't know how to coordinate after switching aces? Pro players weren't dumb. They had to determine if that strategy would still be employed and if the team still needed her support and coordination.

Starting from the latter half of the last season, it was clear that Su Mucheng and Dancing Rain's role in the team had clearly changed. She and Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf never gained the title of Best Partner that they had always received before. She had become an independent offensive player. As for this season, since there were no pro matches to play, what little that made up the Challenger League wasn't enough to make Excellent Era's new methods apparent.

With Xiao Shiqin's Mechanic and Shen Jian's Striker, the Excellent Era of today held no trace of the original Team Excellent Era.

On the contrary, it was Happy, despite having completely different classes from the original Excellent Era, whose performance elicited a warm familiarity in the hearts of many Excellent Era fans with this strategy they were using.

Li Yibo had no words. Excellent Era's fans were at a loss, too.

A team rebuilding their style from scratch wasn't enough to scare their fans away. However, when they realized that their opponent was so similar to the original team they were loyal to, the fans couldn't help but feel quite uncertain.

Now, the two were personally strangling each other to death. Seeing the tactics that were most familiar to them suppressing the very team that they supported, the feelings Excellent Era's fans were in turmoil.

They were watching helplessly as their Team Excellent Era was torn apart while Happy was throwing around all of their most familiar tactics.

"Screen Cannon… and Ye Xiu stalling Qiu Fei and Sun Xiang. This ace player oriented style that belongs to powerhouses…" Pan Lin was detailing the tactics and strategies used by Happy.

"You've missed one: Tang Rou is stalling Xiao Shiqin," Li Yibo brought up.

　

"Ah… This is…" Pan Lin hesitated for a moment. "Box-1?"

"That's right, it's Box-1," Li Yibo confirmed with confidence.

The so-called "Box-1" was when a member of the team was sent to stall and harass a key member of the opposing team. That member would no longer be responsible for coordinating with the rest of the team. They only had one task, which was to prevent the target player from coordinating with the rest of their team. So long as this was accomplished, then this "Box-1" would be considered successful. It didn't matter if the player couldn't kill the opponent because "Box-1" targeted a player crucial to the opposing team. Through isolating that player from the opposing team, that team's formation would take a tremendous hit. That was the true tactical intent of "Box-1".

Using "Box-1" against a Master Tactician like Xiao Shiqin was extremely difficult. However, it was a good thing that Team Happy's goal wasn't to remove or isolate Xiao Shiqin, but to stall for time. Just like how Ye Xiu was fighting one on two. In reality, he stood very little chance against the combination of Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei and could only keep being pushed back. However, what he gained was time. This was what caused Zhang Jiaxing, head raised in hope, to despair. At this rate, he'd be killed!

Xiao Shiqin was desperate, but he couldn't find any breakthrough points. All his hope was placed on Excellent Era's sixth member, Wang Ze.

The sixth player would automatically be switched in upon a player's death. They could choose which support zone to switch in from. The reason Happy could switch out Little Cold Hands for Steamed Bun Invasion to maximize DPS was because this area was close to a support zone. Wang Ze's Sharpshooter should be here any time now.

Gunshot!

Wang Ze's Sharpshooter came just as Xiao Shiqin predicted. He appeared where Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle was, so his first attack was aimed at Dawn Rifle. This caused a great disturbance in Happy's Screen Cannon. Plus, Wang Ze's class was coincidentally a Sharpshooter. His attack range wasn't as good as Launchers, but he didn't have as much trouble as the melee classes. Due to the gunfire aimed at him, Dawn Rifle's tempo was messed up. His talent was average, so using a Screen Cannon under this focused fire was hard for him to maintain.

"Rescue the Cleric!" Xiao Shiqin hurriedly sent out the order.

Even without the Screen Cannon in the way, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei couldn't get past Ye Xiu so easily, and nor could Shao Xiqin throw Tang Rou off. After so long, the healing skills Zhang Jiaxing's Woven Shadows could use were all on cooldown, and he couldn't really do anything. He was too busy dodging attacks. All he could do was await support. Out of the three sides on Excellent Era, if any one side could break through, then the situation could be salvaged. Right now, it seemed that the newcomer Wang Ze was their best chance.

The sixth member couldn't watch the match from an omniscient point of view, so in reality, he was the most confused person. His only knowledge of the situation came from what he could glean from the messages in the chat. The players on the field didn't really have any time to communicate the situation to the sixth player, who would appear on the field at an uncertain time. Usually, the first order given to the sixth player was to tell them which support zone they should switch in from upon a player's death.

Entering the match then rushing over from the support zone, the first of Happy's characters Wang Ze saw was Dawn Rifle, so he quickly began to attack as he looked over the situation.

Without looking he would have no idea, but now that he saw what was going on, he was shocked. His own team was scattered and their Cleric was being beaten up, unprotected, and in a dire situation.

Wang Ze was just thinking he should probably go rescue Woven Shadows first when Xiao Shiqin gave the order. Naturally, he unhesitantly threw Dawn Rifle to the side to charge into the fray.

Yet that was when Wu Chen decided he wasn't having that and Dawn Rifle began to attack Wang Ze's Sharpshooter wildly, even closing in to block him with his body.

Launchers didn't have that many melee skills like Sharpshooters did, so closing in on a Sharpshooter meant nothing good for them. However, was he at a disadvantage now? Of course not. Wang Ze just wanted to get him off his tail as fast as possible, but Wu Chen didn't care, clinging to the Sharpshooter with all his might.

That's right. He was a very ordinary, even closer to a below-average pro player. After his own team had disbanded, he had lost his source of bread and butter. He wasn't young anymore and he wasn't very skilled. Which real team would take him? The only teams that would were grassroots teams that couldn't even attract pro players!

Yet a grassroots team really had came.

Happy had eliminated them from the Challenger League and was the perpetrator of their disbandment. This team that he should hate was the one that had sent him an invite.

Wu Chen accepted. He couldn't bear leaving Glory so soon. It was just that, after joining to Happy, his main job was no longer to be a player that competed in matches. That, for him, was somewhat disappointing. Though his skill wasn't at the cream of the crop level, the eagerness pros held towards competing wasn't measured by skill level.

It was a good thing that Happy had registered him in the Challenger League, which made him hopeful for another chance. He hoped to compete onstage more, but he had never thought that Happy would leave the grandest stage of the Challenger League to him. When Ye Xiu had told him he was going up for the finals of the Challenger League, he could barely believe his ears. After confirming things, he naturally had a few doubts. Because even though Happy might've been a grassroots team, Wu Chen knew that his skill wasn't anything special among the members of this grassroots team. Even disregarding God Ye Qiu, the other newbies had potential that was better relied on.

　　

Why me?

Wu Chen had questioned and Ye Xiu had replied honestly: because you're a Launcher.

So it was because of his class.

This sort of reason would disappoint most people. Everyone hoped that others would notice their talent, but not Wu Chen. Talent? After being a part of the Glory circle for so long, he knew how much talent he had. With his talent alone, he wouldn't be given the chance to appear on this sort of stage at all.

Because of his class. This reason wasn't anything wonderful, but it was satisfactory enough for him. Wu Chen thanked the class he had stuck with and loved for giving him such a chance in the end. Wu Chen knew with clarity that this match would probably be the last time he ever appeared in an official match and this stage was probably the largest he could ever get.

The finals of the Challenger League opponent? Excellent Era!

Wu Chen had been excited and nervous. For this match, he had went and trained with all his might, doing everything he could to accomplish what was required of him. Ye Xiu had already clearly informed him of what the team needed him to do, and he had trained according to these needs. Finally, the matchday had arrived.

His had performed… alright, right?

Until today, the careful and precise Wu Chen had been satisfied with his performance. Now, all they had to do was kill Excellent Era's Cleric and then they would've completely tilted the scales of victory for this match. Yet, it was at such a crucial moment that Excellent Era's sixth player had arrived and tried to break through the area he was in to save their Cleric.

　

No! I won't allow this to happen!

　　

Wu Chen, who had been careful the entire match, seemed to completely lose all rationality in that moment. He used a fighting style that should never appear on a Launcher and stuck to this Sharpshooter like gum. His mind had mostly blanked. All he knew was that he had to stop this person to assure victory in this match.

"Wu Chen… this… this…" Wu Chen, a player who should've been easy to see through for Li Yibo, was now someone whose actions had made Li Yibo speechless. His current actions weren't something that was for show; it was ugly; it had no skill to it.

"Is this… Box-2?" Pan Lin suddenly asked.

"Box-2?" Li Yibo was stunned. Ok… from some perspectives, this could be counted as a Box-2, but Wu Chen's performance really was rather "two"*. Yet Wang Ze's Sharpshooter really had been stalled by him.

"It's over," Li Yibo sighed, shaking his head. Team Excellent Era, Zhang Jiaxing's Cleric, Woven Shadows, had been eliminated from the match.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

TN: *Two, in Chinese, is a way of saying stupidly incomprehensible. - Jouissance

Chapter 1043: Regarded as Helpless Grass

In the audience, Seven Field and his group were clapping until their palms were swollen.

"Do you see that? That's our Happy!!!" Seven Fields strained his throat, yelling at the Excellent Era fans surrounding him. Seven Field was usually a rather calm person, but in this moment he could no longer control his excitement. Was Excellent Era strong? Yes, they were, but in this match, it was Happy that was suppressing Excellent Era. From the beginning, they had been leading Excellent Era around by the nose.

Seven Field's voice was already rather raspy. Not just him, but all 53 Happy guild members that lived in City B, who came to cheer Happy on, were all losing their voices from yelling. This was because compared to the thousands of Excellent Era fans here, their fifty three was negligible.

Yet in this moment, they had the upper hand because their team was supporting them. The Cleric had even been killed. Anyone who knew Glory would know that in this situation, there was no optimism left to be had. Faced with Seven Field's open taunting, the Excellent Era fans had nothing they could use as a response. And Seven Fields only had one disappointment in that moment, which was… the name Happy really was too ordinary. It didn't feel special, being yelled out.

"The healer, wiped out! Team Excellent Era's Cleric Woven Shadow has been killed and player Zhang Jiaxing has left the match. In the finals of the Challenger League, Excellent Era is in a dire situation!" Pan Lin was also yelling in the live broadcast. As the commentator of the broadcast, he wasn't biased to either side. What he hoped to see was a spectacular performance. The biggest point of drama about this match, apart from Ye Xiu versus Excellent Era, was to see if a dark horse would appear.

And now, the situation of the match was obviously tilting in Happy's favor. This caused the commentators, who were looking for drama, to become excited. According to the TV Audience Rating Department, the view count for this match suddenly skyrocketed. This was evidently because Happy had killed the Cleric Woven Shadow. Without a healer, the scales of victory had tilted sharply. The Glory players that heard of this would probably all turn on a TV or switch channels to watch this match that originally held no suspense.

Excellent Era's competition booth.

Zhang Jiaxing, having left the match, seemed to lose all strength, slumping in his seat. Now, he was able to watch the match from an omniscient view, but how would this match go? He found himself almost afraid to watch. He couldn't help but think, what would it be like if Excellent Era was stopped here and couldn't return to the Alliance, forced to participate in this Challenger League for another year?

It definitely wasn't just him that was worrying about this.

Just as Woven Shadow's health fell to zero, like a bolt of lightning, this thought surfaced in the minds of almost all of Excellent Era's players, the players off stage and the players onstage alike. Many people had already glanced discreetly at boss Tao Xuan and they found that the boss' eyebrow kept twitching. He, too, had long since lost the calm he usually had.

　

In the field, Excellent Era only had four people left in total and no healer.

"Focus fire on the Launcher!" In the moment Woven Shadow fell, Xiao Shiqin gave a new order. He knew that he couldn't save Woven Shadow anymore. The only one that had hope of breaking through was Wang Ze and he had been blocked by Wu Chen reckless and wild actions. However, this desperate recklessness meant that he was more or less using Dawn Rifle's life to block Wang Ze. He used Dawn Rifle's body to block shot after shot of Wang Ze's Sharpshooter.

No matter how strong a character was, they couldn't afford to be a meat shield like that. In that moment, Wu Chen had evidently hardened his heart and prepared to sacrifice his own character. Someone who no longer cared about their own life was always the scariest. Wang Ze had been stalled by Wu Chen in that state and the shots and blows he had made had all mercilessly struck Dawn Rifle. Wu Chen didn't make any movements to dodge, afraid that Wang Ze might manage to grasp an opening. Just like that, he managed to stall Wang Ze's Sharpshooter by brute force, but also sentence Dawn Rifle to his death.

Xiao Shiqin had a clear view. They might not have a healer right now, but Happy currently didn't have one either. They needed to take this chance to barrage the other side with attacks and kill off as many of their characters as possible. The longer they stalled, the worse off they would be, with their lack of a healer.

In this situation, it wasn't a good idea to stall the opponent's ace, so Xiao Shiqin swiftly gave an order, getting Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei to switch targets and wipe out Dawn Rifle, who only had 30 percent of his health left after the beating he received from Wang Ze. This was because he saw One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun Invasion rushing to support Dawn Rifle after finishing Woven Shadow off. He couldn't let their plans come through again.

Both sides were fighting to get there first!

However, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei's charge against Ye Xiu and Xiao Shiqin's attempts to throw off Tang Rou had been happening for a while already. It wasn't that they couldn't. It was just that they didn't have enough time to save Woven Shadow. Now, both sides broke through and immediately focused their attacks on Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle. Their sudden change in rhythm finally displayed the airs a powerhouse team like theirs should have. Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash weren't slow either, but they weren't healers and could only attack to try and suppress their opponent's offense. Excellent Era, without their healer, aimed to finish things as fast as possible and didn't methodically exchange blows with Happy. When they needed to storm their opponents, they would be willing to trade some blood even without their healer!

　　

One wave rush!

Excellent Era's four characters ignored everything else and focused on unleashing a torrent of attacks, crushing Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle and instantly managing to close in on Happy by a player.

Happy's Cleric Little Cold Hands was automatically switched in, but needed time to arrive from the support zones. During this time, the two sides were fighting four on four, equal in numbers. The audience suddenly realized that Excellent Era didn't seem to be at a disadvantage!

On Happy's side, only Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash were in a relatively good state.

Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had already fought Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei while alone twice. His one versus two fight had a cost. The damage he had dealt to One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form was nothing compared to the damage he had taken from the two. The current Lord Grim only had 70 percent of his health left.

Tang Rou's Soft Mist was in a far worse condition though. Before, she had courageously taken on Sun Xiang, Qiu Fei and Xiao Shiqin's charge alone and had already lost a lot of health. Then, she had gone to block Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei before being sent flying and switching to stall Life Extinguisher. Through all of this, the damage she had taken far exceeded the damage she had dealt. Currently, Soft Mist only had 20 percent of her health left, not even as much as Dawn Rifle. It was just that Xiao Shiqin had placed heavy importance on getting rid of the tactical advantage Dawn Rifle had provided for Happy and named him to be the first target. After their success, the four Excellent Era membered charged for Soft Mist at once.

Fast!

That was what everyone thought.

　

After their Cleric was killed, Team Excellent Era didn't dawdle and instead immediately increased their rhythm, swiftly focusing their fire on and wiping Dawn Rifle off the field, then charged at Soft Mist hoping for another One Wave Rush.

"I never expected that Team Excellent Era would fight more wildly after their Cleric was killed…" Pan Lin said, stunned.

"Happy's tactics haven't been laid out very smoothly, it seems! Excellent Era storming Dawn Rifle, Steamed Bun Invasion, and One Inch Ash running to support, this sort of natural instinct lost them the initiative they had for the majority of the match. Seems like they really are still too young. Look at Xiao Shiqin. When Woven Shadows was about to be killed, he had already given the order to focus their fire on Dawn Rifle instead. This sort of rhythm is something Happy can learn from."

"Then how do you think Happy should deal with this?" Pan Lin asked.

"Support Lord Grim or Soft Mist, continuing to draw out the situation where they outnumber Excellent Era and trading with them. When at an advantage in numbers, this sort of trade would put a great amount of pressure on Excellent Era and Happy could continue to keep hold of the initiative. Yet now, the match is in Excellent Era's control again… I think Ye Xiu is probably regretting things now. He should've done the same thing as Xiao Shiqin and gave his team members orders beforehand. Happy's members are younger, more inexperienced, they need his guidance more!" Li Yibo said.

"He might not have had the time to do so, when facing Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei alone," Pan Lin suggested.

"That's true. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei have been very aggressive in these fights." Li Yibo nodded.

In any case, this was a completely unexpected situation.

　

Excellent Era's fans, who had wilted a little, sprung back to life then. Having been taunted by Seven Fields, they immediately retorted. Excellent Era's fans had far more people. This counterattack almost drowned Happy's small cheerleading squad in yells.

"See that? That's Excellent Era for you! So what if they lost their healer? Can you endure our one wave rush?" The Excellent Era fans, who sat close and had thus almost been hit in the head by Seven Field's excited gesturing, jumped up to shout as revenge, shoving their heads towards Seven Field.

As for Seven Fields and the others? They were too nervous to care about arguing with Excellent Era's fans.

Hold on!

The 53 Happy guild members clenched their fists as one, almost seeming to hear the inner voices of their comrades.

Hold on!

How would Happy deal with this?

Those who wondered all looked to Lord Grim. Ye Xiu should take command by now, right? If he just let these rookies do whatever they wanted, they would only get led around by the nose by the experienced Xiao Shiqin. Out of all of Happy's players, only he had the ability to match Xiao Shiqin in tactics.

Yet he said nothing. In this crucial moment, he didn't give any orders, letting the members of Happy act according their their own judgements.

Excellent Era's four players advanced, but Soft Mist, with only 20 percent of her health left, had no intentions of backing down.

"Attack!!" At Xiao Shiqin's command, the two Battle Mages charged forward and the two gunners provided firepower coverage from afar.

Missed!

Xiao Shiqin was stunned. They had to wipe their target off the field in a single wave of attacks so everyone had to be careful to not only deal damage, but also entrap their target, cutting off all of Soft Mist's paths of retreat and not letting her escape.

Yet now, their entrapment seemed miles away from Soft Mist.

This was because neither Xiao Shiqin nor Wang Ze, nor Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had thought Tang Rou, when faced with this situation, wouldn't choose to dodge or back down, but… to charge forward!!!

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

Soft Mist unhesitantly charged forward with her 20 percent of health.

Xiao Shiqin cried internally: we bloody know you're an aggressive player already, but there's got to be a limit! You're charging forward in a situation like this? Do you take us for helpless grass?

Chapter 1044: The Last Drop of Blood

Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks stirred up the entire stadium. The commentator, Pan Lin, could only give a long "Oh..." before becoming silent.

Despite facing four members from Excellent Era all by herself, Soft Mist dared to rush ahead with more vigor and initiative than before. This girl... does she even understand the situation she's in?

Many people wanted to make fun of Tang Rou's suicidal action. However, everyone was stunned the very next second when they saw Soft Mist's Dragon Breaks the Ranks get past the suppression of the two Battle Mages, One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form, and arrive in front of the two long-ranged gunners.

This seemed like a situation where Tang Rou was walking right into a trap. If anyone in Excellent Era had been prepared, they could have gotten rid of Soft Mist right away. The problem was that they hadn't been. Whether it was the Master Tactician Xiao Shiqin, the new generation's God Sun Xiang, or the talented rookie Qiu Fei, none of them expected Tang Rou to be so fearless. .

At the time, no one could determine whether her courage was deserving of praise or extremely foolish.

Soft Mist's spear swept around in a circle, and the two long-ranged gunners were forced to retreat. As they dodged, they lifted their guns and started to shoot. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form spun around to pincer Soft Mist.

The four from Excellent Era adjusted extremely quickly. However, Tang Rou's unexpected move still managed to disrupt their rhythm. They surrounded her again, but it wasn't as perfect as the previous wave, regardless of whether it was their positioning or rhythm.

Their encirclement might have been enough for normal players. Unfortunately, for Happy's Ye Xiu, such a disorderly encirclement couldn't just be politely described as "imperfect", it was filled with flaws.

"Matchstick!"

A message suddenly popped out from Lord Grim in Happy's team chat.

This wasn't a code word; Matchstick was the name of Wang Ze's Sharpshooter. Although he had only arrived in the map not long ago and failed to save Excellent Era's Cleric, he was able to set up a good foundation for Excellent Era's comeback by dealing a lot of damage to Dawn Rifle. However, he had now become Happy's breakthrough target.

This was probably the first direct confrontation between the two teams in this Matchstick. The four characters from both sides were gathered in the same area and each attacked their respective tactical targets.

"Happy is putting on a tough front facing Excellent Era's counterattack!!" Pan Lin cried with surprise. Happy had been deliberately avoiding direct confrontations the entire time. However, now their approach suddenly changed. When the four from Excellent Era surrounded Soft Mist, the other three characters from Happy valiantly charged forward to save her.

At the same time, Tang Rou, who was surrounded, also carried out Ye Xiu's instruction.

1v4. There was nothing that could make Tang Rou more excited. Her hand speed exploded as Soft Mist charged towards Matchstick. She swayed left and right at high speeds, dodging the incoming gunner attacks. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form chased closely behind her. The two had nothing harassing them, so their movement speeds werewas faster and the distance between them continued to decrease.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

At this moment, time was the most important. It was a matter of speed. No one would save their high-level skills for later. One Autumn Leaf unleashed a Dragon Breaks the Ranks towards Soft Mist's back.

But Soft Mist leaped up into the air.

Shattering the Lands!

Excellent Era wasn't the only one who knew how to use this Level 75 skill.

One Autumn Leaf's Dragon Breaks the Ranks brushed past her, missing by just a hair. Combat Form had originally been planning on following up with an attack, but seeing Soft Mist use Shattering the Lands, he immediately made adjustments.

The attacks from Xiao Shiqin and Wang Ze didn't stop. Soft Mist was in the air now, so dodging was more difficult. She was struck repeatedly by bullets, and her health slid down.

Her Shattering the Lands still came out though!

Soft Mist descended from the air along with streaks of blood and fire. Her spear stabbed into the ground and magic waves lifted up the earth. Dirt and stone swirled in the air. A blaze of fire flowed out from the center, her spear's Flowing Fire effect.

This type of high-level skill couldn't be taken directly. Qiu Fei's Combat Form was unable to advance. Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf immediately dodged to the side. On the other hand, Xiao Shiqin and Wang Ze escaped from its attack range, while continuing to attack.

"Kill her!!!" Xiao Shiqin roared. Soft Mist's ferociousness would fire up the spirits of anyone who crossed her path.

Just when Soft Mist's health was about to hit 0, a white light surrounded her body.

Small Heal!

"Wha... what..." Pan Lin was about to explode. He was just about to announce Soft Mist's death, but he hadn't expected Lord Grim to cast a heal to save Soft Mist at the last second.

"Brilliant!" This was Li Yibo's evaluation of it. Small Heal had a cast time, so being able to time it so perfectly required extremely accurate predictions. It wasn't just a matter of hand speed.

However, the heal was a low-level skill. Lord Grim wasn't a healer and he didn't have healer equipment either. This Small Heal only allowed Soft Mist to not die in the last moment. Truly saving her from death was still far away.

However, by prolonging her inevitable death, Tang Rou was able to attack once more.

Soft Mist attacked Matchstick with a Falling Flower Palm.

Wang Ze didn't dodge. Soft Mist's hitpoints were at single digits. Instead of dodging, he might as well just finish her off.

That's what everyone thought, so they all attacked.

Suddenly, another white light flashed onto Soft Mist.

Small Cure!

Soft Mist once again survived with a last second save. Just from Soft Mist's remaining health, it could be seen how prompt the heal had been. After the heal, her health dropped to near zero. Soft Mist was hanging on with just one last drop of health left.

But that didn't affect Soft Mist from carrying out her attack.

Falling Flower Palm sent Matchstick flying away towards One Inch Ash's five overlapping ghost boundaries. Steamed Bun Invasion pounced forward and grabbed Matchstick in midair. Wang Ze couldn't even Quick Recover.

Matchstick was sent flying. A huge gap appeared in Excellent Era's encirclement. Soft Mist immediately tried to rush through it, but Xiao Shiqin wasn't going to give her that chance. Bullets rained down on her. However, a figure flashed and Lord Grim appeared with his umbrella propped up, protecting Soft Mist completely.

Soft Mist actually didn't die?

No one wanted to believe it. Li Yibo was just about to talk about Ye Xiu's two miraculous saves and their effects on the Matchstick. He hadn't expected that Soft Mist would be saved once again.

Just one more attack yet Excellent Era wasn't able to do it?

That was just... too unlucky.

Yes, something so outrageous couldn't be from skill. It could only be luck.

But this was just temporary, no?

One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form had charged forward. Their two spears crossed each other at 120 degree angles, attacking Lord Grim from the left and right. As for Soft Mist, who was hiding behind Lord Grim, she was within their attack range too. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher used a Rotor Wings to fly up and get around Lord Grim's umbrella shield by attacking from above.

They just needed one attack. How could they not do it? The three players from Excellent Era were confident, even if Ye Xiu was protecting her. They didn't think that Ye Xiu could protect her so thoroughly.

Ye Xiu couldn't protect her, but he also didn't bother trying. Life Extinguisher flew into the air with Rotor Wings and saw what Soft Mist was doing. He suddenly cried out in alarm.

"Careful!"

The warning was too late though. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form had reached them. Lord Grim's Myriad Manifestations Umbrella retracted and a powerful magic wave surged forth, Rising Dragon Soars the Sky!

Soft Mist only had just a drop of health left, yet she actually attacked. Under the cover of Lord Grim's shield, this was a two-player Blind Shield Play. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei hadn't expected it at all. By the time Xiao Shiqin became aware of it, it was too late.

Dancing Fire Flowing Flame turned into an angry dragon and flew out from behind Lord Grim's umbrella towards Combat Form. Combat Form had already let out his attack, but its priority couldn't compete with Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. He was chomped by the magic dragon. The magic waves coiled around his body and then exploded. Combat Form took a full blow from this high-level skill.

Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf didn't get hit by the sneak attack. Lord Grim's umbrella greeted him instead. The umbrella strike looked like it was more to drive him away than to damage him, but Sun Xiang could only get hit by it. He couldn't dodge Ye Xiu's strike. If he did, he would be in the path of Soft Mist's Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Wouldn't dodging over there be letting them hit two birds with one stone?

Rising Dragon Soars the Sky wasn't just a sneak attack. Ye Xiu used it to limit the opponent's space, allowing him to put in two strikes and knock One Autumn Leaf to the side. Life Extinguisher's gunfire rained down from above, but Lord Grim simply opened up the umbrella put it above his head. Using the umbrella shield in this way was the easiest. After all, wasn't that the original purpose of an umbrella?

After taking care of those two, he convened with Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash under the gunfire above from Life Extinguisher. It was like he was taking a stroll in the rain. Ye Xiu had already casted a Recover onto Soft Mist. Her health was slowly recovering. Even though it wasn't much, but to those in Excellent Era, it was like a stab to their hearts.

How long is it going to take to get rid of that last drop of health?

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

Heals have a cast time but no cooldown. Cures have no cast time but a long cooldown.

Chapter 1045: Interlinked

Recover healed over time in bursts. The amount of heal per burst wasn't much to begin with. Lord Grim was a poor healer too, so each burst was even more dismal. In fact, even with these bursts, Excellent Era could still kill off their target in one strike. However, every burst was like torture to them.

What's worse, Happy's Cleric was most likely about to arrive. Even though that Cleric's skill wasn't amazing, in this situation, it was more than enough to be the deciding factor. Xiao Shiqin suddenly felt a bit upset. After killing Dawn Rifle, they should have headed towards the support zone to cut off and maybe even kill the enemy Cleric. Instead, they got into a tangle with Soft Mist. Even if she would die in the end, it was still embarrassing!

The fight had already reached this point. Regretting now was useless. Soft Mist must die before the healer arrived.

Xiao Shiqin made arrangements for the team formation using just a few concise words in the chat. The Battle Mage duo, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, headed directly towards Happy's four player group. Previously, they had surrounded Tang Rou's Soft Mist, but ended up being attacked by Happy from the inside and outside. This time, Happy had surrounded Wang Ze's Matchstick. It should be their turn to attack from the inside and outside.

Wang Ze had just joined the battle. His Matchstick was at full health. He wasn't panicked despite being surrounded by Happy. This time, Excellent Era's rescue operation came quickly. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form charged forward ferociously. They weren't in a hurry to rescue Matchstick. Their target was still Soft Mist. Soft Mist only had a sliver of health left. It was already a miracle that she was alive. Without a healer, focusing their attention onto protecting her was actually a huge burden for Happy. However, Happy didn't protect her. Soft Mist charged at them with just 20% of her health left. Later, she only had a drop of health left, yet she and Lord Grim coordinated together to strike Combat Form with a Rising Dragon Soars the Sky. Soft Mist's existence had become a huge hindrance to Excellent Era's plans. She was like bait, controlling Excellent Era's goals. Not only did she not become a burden to her team. She was using every second of her time on the field very effectively.

Xiao Shiqin was clearly aware of this issue. Excellent Era made adjustments. They didn't put all of their efforts into killing Soft Mist. While Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei charged into Happy's formation, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher circled around from a different direction.

What is he trying to do?　

Pan Lin and Li Yibo glanced at each other. For a moment, they didn't understand, so they didn't dare say anything. The orders that Xiao Shiqin gave in chat didn't really convey what he was planning on doing.

Life Extinguisher was making every second count. As he sprinted, he observed Happy's movements. When he realized that no one was paying attention to him, there seemed to be some hesitation to Life Extinguisher's movements.

At this moment, everyone finally understood Xiao Shiqin's intentions. They couldn't help but think of a popular verse from many years back: as the last to know the truth, my tears fall.

Yes, Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher had been planning on intercepting Happy's Cleric, but the problem was that he had gone in the wrong direction…..

The spectators had an omniscient view, so from the beginning, they knew which support zone Little Cold Hands had swapped in from. It wasn't the closest support zone. At that time, everyone felt confused, but now everyone understood that swapping in from the closest support zone was too easy to guess. Happy had made preparations for it. They were very careful about maintaining their healer advantage.

Xiao Shiqin had Life Extinguisher run towards this direction for awhile, but having not seen any signs of Little Cold Hands, he felt like something wasn't right. From his calculations, he should already be able to see the Cleric. However, he didn't. That at least meant that the other side had been ready for his interception, whether that was taking a roundabout route or coming from a different support zone.

Another judgement error made Xiao Shiqin feel exhausted. He realized that he was unable to grasp Happy's thinking.

He understood Ye Xiu, but the Ye Xiu that he understood was the Ye Xiu leading a powerhouse. But the Ye Xiu he was facing now was a Ye Xiu leading a grassroots team displaying more complex strategies. From time to time, Ye Xiu would show the craftiness of small teams, while showing the oppressiveness of top teams.

Just take this choice of support zones. From Xiao Shiqin's experience of leading a weak team, entering from the closest support zone was a necessary choice because a weak team needed a healer to hurry and help them maintain their advantage. However, Happy just had to be bold and actually had their Cleric take a longer path. Xiao Shiqin had never had this type of confidence when he led Thunderclap.

In the end, is it because I'm not confident enough?

When I was on Thunderclap, had I ever thought of leading the team to win the championship?

No. Never.

The outside world had always believed Thunderclap to be a weak team. Just being able to make into the playoffs every years was a huge success. As a result, Thunderclap and even Xiao Shiqin had always thought so as well. Their goal every year was to make into the playoffs. As for the playoffs itself, they didn't have any high ambitions. They clearly thirsted to be champions, but they never believed in themselves nor aspired to be number one.

In the end, Xiao Shiqin left Thunderclap to be a champion. Even though no one criticized him for it and even thought it was something he should have done earlier, Xiao Shiqin finally understood that he himself was weak. He hadn't believed in his teammates or himself. There was too big of a difference between himself and his opponent. Ye Xiu was leading a team scraped together from an Internet cafe, yet he dared to join the Challenger League and challenge a powerhouse like Excellent Era. How many had a laughed at him? But now? This joke was turning into a reality step by step.

But him? Although Team Thunderclap repeatedly beat the stronger opponent, he had never been confident in himself. Why had he never been confident? Thunderclap was able to win over strong teams in the regular season, so why couldn't they repeat that same performance in the playoffs? If they just repeated it three times, then wouldn't Thunderclap become the champions?

In the end, he had only been confident in the matches he should have won. However, Ye Xiu had the confidence and courage to create miracles!

Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher swiftly returned to the battle. The situation had already changed.

Soft Mist was finally killed.

Tang Rou wouldn't let herself become a burden that the entire team needed to put all of their efforts into protecting her. Even if she only had just a drop of health left, she would still fight and contribute to the team. After one last final struggle, she fell. In that instant, the stadium erupted into applause. Even Excellent Era's fans chose to remain silent. In this life and death situation, they were unable to give any applause to the enemy team, but they at least stayed silent to show their respect. In the group arena, Tang Rou lost miserably. But in this team competition, she finally left a deep impression on everyone. Although it was hard to tell at times whether her performance was bravery or stupidity, her brave or stupid performance was a crucial factor in Happy reaching this point.

During the period of time it took Xiao Shiqin to run over in an attempt to block the healer, Excellent Era's three players were able to successfully kill Soft Mist, but they also suffered a blow, especially Wang Ze's Matchstick. He had been pincered by Steamed Bun and Qiao Yifan from the start. Later, Lord Grim came over to join in while protecting Soft Mist. Team Happy's focus wasn't to protect Soft Mist, but to continue targeting Matchstick.

One Inch Ash's ghost boundaries were extremely effective defenses. If One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form wanted to attack Happy, they had to go into the ghost boundaries. If they didn't, they could only just wait and watch as the other side besieged Matchstick.

There were ways to break through the restrictions from ghost boundaries, but in general, Ghostblades were difficult for One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form to deal with. Wang Ze's Matchstick only had limited support. He himself wasn't able to break out of the encirclement either. When Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher arrived, Soft Mist was already gone, but Matchstick was facing imminent danger.　　

When Xiao Shiqin returned and saw the negative debuffs on the two Battle Mages, he felt helpless. Ghostblades generally had a hard time affecting long-ranged classes, but he just had to be a Mechanic. Many of his gadgets had no way of breaking through ghost boundaries, so for a Mechanic, breaking through a ghost boundary was very difficult. If not, Xiao Shiqin would have had someone else block the Cleric, while he stayed. It wasn't like the two Battle Mages couldn't separate from time to time.

And now because of the existence of the ghost boundaries, they had no way of displaying their full strength. Their Sharpshooter, which wouldn't have been affected much by the ghost boundaries, had been snatched away by the other side long ago.

Xiao Shiqin didn't believe this to be a coincidence. This match gave him a completely knew understanding of how terrifying Ye Xiu's strategies were. All of his tactics were interlinked, each step taken was a step closer to victory. Every one of Team Happy's members were utilized to the limit. From Wu Chen's Dawn Rifle to Tang Rou's Soft Mist and now Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash.

I have to find a way to get rid of this Phantom Demon!

No... wait…..

Xiao Shiqin was thinking of a countermeasure, when a light suddenly lit up in his head.

Phantom Demon. Their next target should be this Phantom Demon, but if they did that, wouldn't they fall into Happy's trap again?

From the very start of this match, Happy's members revealed their talents one after the other, which Excellent Era locked onto. Then, they were put into a difficult spots because of these targets…...

Yes, so it's like that. The key to Happy's strategies lies here!

Chapter 1046: Steamed Bun’s Tempo

The crucial characters that dictated Happy's tactics were always traps. Every time Excellent Era attacked those characters, they would always fall into an unfavorable position and had to pay a considerable price for it. As a result, not only did they fail to break Happy's tactics, they suffered in the attempt.

Xiao Shiqin quickly deleted the "focus ghostblade" that he had typed into the team chat. Excellent Era couldn't afford to fall into any more traps. The current situation was a 4v3. Although Happy had captured one of their players, Happy was in a completely defensive position. Happy's three players were confined inside the ghost boundary, not daring to leave its range.

Excellent Era was at a disadvantage because of the protection from the ghost boundary. For now, they had no way of routing Happy. Without a healer, they couldn't play the long game. They needed to quickly find an opening.　　

Focus Ye Xiu!

A new order jumped into Excellent Era's team chat. Xiao Shiqin had pressed the Enter key quite forcefully. He was a bit annoyed, not discovering this issue earlier. He shouldn't have thought so much. After finding Lord Grim, he should have had Excellent Era focus all of their efforts and disregard all else to eliminate Ye Xiu from the beginning.

Yes, disregard all else.

After giving this order, Xiao Shiqin typed another four words: get rid of him.　　

Even if they had to sacrifice one, two, three, even four including their healer, as long as they got rid of Ye Xiu, Excellent Era may be at a numbers disadvantage, with their superior strength, how could they not be able to take care of Happy's green rookies?

This reasoning was so simple, simple to the point that Xiao Shiqin had completely disregarded it. He had thought very highly of Ye Xiu and analyzed all sorts of possibilities. He had spent all his time thinking about what Ye Xiu might do, so he hadn't thought about forcefully eliminating Ye Xiu.

In the end, it was because Xiao Shiqin was unable to get rid of his mid-tier team thinking. His tactics were unable to completely utilize Excellent Era's battle power. Their vastly superior strength in the Challenger League covered up this point, so when the finals came and the opponent's tactics and players managed to keep up, Excellent Era was suddenly overwhelmed.

This was completely inconsistent with what people had anticipated this match would go. In their eyes, even if Excellent Era lost, it must have been because, despite being at an advantage the vast majority of the time, they made a huge mistake that was seized by Happy. Who would have thought that Excellent Era would be the one at a disadvantage and be nibbled away by Happy.

It was only now did Xiao Shiqin realize where the problem lay. Even though he was unable to completely identify the problems with him and Excellent Era, he at least found where the crux of the issue lay.

Focus Ye Xiu and disregard all else.

No healer?

No healer was no healer. As long as they could get rid of Ye Xiu, any price was worth it. Excellent Era still had a numbers advantage at the moment. This might be their last opportunity. They needed to eliminate Lord Grim by whatever means possible, whether that meant eating the damage and debuffs from the ghost boundaries and taking the attacks from the other members of Happy. They could not back down.　　

The new order didn't just show their strategy.

Disregarding everything else showed their determination.

Everyone saw the order given by Excellent Era. Their hearts leaped up. They had a premonition that the biggest storm in the match was about to arrive.

Xiao Shiqin took the lead. His Life Extinguisher showed the same vigor as Dawn Rifle and rushed forward. He abandoned all of the gadgets restricted by ghost boundaries and released all of the heavy gadgets that could withstand the ghost boundaries. Under the cover of Air Drop, Life Extinguisher charged directly into the ghost boundaries.

What he meant by "disregard all else" was very clear. The other three Excellent Era players became spirited. Wang Ze's Matchstick turned his body. Ignoring the attacks taken, he headed straight for Lord Grim. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei ignored the debuffs and damage from the ghost boundaries and put a target on Lord Grim. They would kill him in the most efficient way possible.

Excellent Era's abrupt offensive was something felt not just by Ye Xiu, but Qiao Yifan. The ghost boundaries placed down by him were being completely ignored. These ghost boundaries debuffed and damaged the enemies, yet they were still focusing their attacks onto Lord Grim.

Lord Grim wasn't at full health. He had been through several fierce battles and withstood numerous attacks as well. He had protected Soft Mist with his umbrella shield. He looked like he was taking a stroll through the rain of bullets, but in reality, he had taken a lot of damage.

The shield form reduced a percentage of damage and also increased his defenses. To a certain extent, he couldn't completely nullify the damage like a block, but he didn't need to calculate attack priority with a shield unlike with a block. Facing attacks, as long as he met those attacks with his shield, he would be able to reduce the damage that he took.

Soft Mist hid behind Lord Grim's umbrella, so she didn't take any damage. However, Lord Grim would still take damage. If everything was added up, Lord Grim actually had the least amount of health in the team. He only had 50% of his health left.

Why didn't I think of prioritizing him earlier?

Xiao Shiqin's mind churned. The more he looked at the situation, the more he felt like prioritizing Lord Grim was the correct decision.　

After his Life Extinguisher entered the ghost boundary, he also ignored the existence of the ghost boundaries and only thought about killing Lord Grim.　　

Qiao Yifan immediately strengthened their defenses and threw down more ghost boundaries. However, these ghost boundaries were still being ignored by Excellent Era, who had surrounded and were crazily attacking Ye Xiu's Lord Grim. Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash seemed to be invisible. Excellent Era completely ignored their attacks.

"CC them!" Qiao Yifan hastily reminded Steamed Bun.

Readily following orders was one of Steamed Bun's features. It didn't matter who said it. He didn't consider if the reasoning made sense or not, he would follow it regardless. Steamed Bun Invasion pounced forward and used Tyrannical Chain Punch to pin down a target, but reality proved that even though Excellent Era disregard the two of them, they would still be on guard for these types of attacks. Steamed Bun had targeted One Autumn Leaf, who made a nimble turn and easily dodged it. Steamed Bun wasn't clingy. He turned and used Strangle on Combat Form.

Strangle had to be dodged. Even though Strangle wouldn't stop the target from attacking, it restricted the target's movements, which meant that he would be unable to reach Lord Grim.

Steamed Bun Invasion's attack was once again evaded, but he followed up with a Sand Toss, Brick... Brawler's had quite a lot of CC skills. Steamed Bun was throwing them out brainlessly. He didn't have a single target or any clear-cut thinking. Whichever target was the most convenient would be the target to attack. In an instant, his skills were all on cooldown. Steamed Bun's hand speed was quite outstanding. However, at this point, his low-level skills had refreshed, so he started chaining them again.　　

"Too reckless….." Li Yibo sighed.

However, this recklessness actually made a big impact on the situation. Excellent Era still put all their efforts into killing Lord Grim. They didn't care about the damage from these attacks, but they were afraid of these CC skills delaying them. They needed to pay attention to Steamed Bun Invasion's skills. However, Steamed Bun's attacks didn't have any thinking behind them. It was completely random. Xiao Shiqin had tried predicting Steamed Bun's attacks and ended up being hit by a Brick.　　

Yes, a Brick hit Life Extinguisher in the back of his head, putting him to enter a Dizzy state. Unfortunately, due to Life Extinguisher being inside the ghost boundaries, the constant damage from the ghost boundaries instantly got rid of his Dizzy state. Qiao Yifan felt regretful. This Steamed Bun didn't coordinate with him. If he had known that Brick would hit, he wouldn't have placed down a ghost boundary that dealt damage!

But Steamed Bun didn't care. He had already switched targets. For a moment, Steamed Bun Invasion was actually singlehandedly flustering Excellent Era. They didn't want to waste their time on Steamed Bun Invasion, but they needed to put quite a bit of effort into defending against Steamed Bun Invasion's attacks.

Neither the heavens nor the earth knew where his attacks were coming from, whether that was a Brick or another skill. Every time Steamed Bun lifted his hands, everyone in Excellent Era dodged out of fright. And in the end? Steamed Bun Invasion could only target one person, so the other two were just wasting their time, no?

"This this... how messy..." Pan Lin was dumbstruck. Due to Steamed Bun's wave of attacks, the match was incomprehensibly chaotic. It could no longer be deciphered through their knowledge of Glory. Li Yibo was silent for a long time before finally saying: "He disrupted Excellent Era's tempo."

Yes. Anyone could see that. Excellent Era's tempo was in a mess, but the problem was what about Happy's tempo? They didn't have any at all. Excellent Era couldn't grasp Steamed Bun's attacks, but neither could the rest of Happy.

"F*ck off!!"

Sun Xiang was finally unable to endure it anymore. That clown was actually slowing down their assault on Lord Grim. One Autumn Leaf temporarily let Lord Grim off the hook. His Evil Annihilation headed straight for Steamed Bun Invasion. He was determined to send this clown flying far away.　

"Careful!"

The moment One Autumn Leaf turned around, a spear suddenly shot towards him. Ye Xiu wasn't dead yet. In this type of chaotic battle, there were opportunities everywhere. One Autumn Leaf suddenly switched targets without paying attention to anyone else. Ye Xiu's attack was almost out of instinct. If he didn't attack, he would be wasting his many years of practice.

Circle Swing!

Lord Grim sent One Autumn Leaf flying towards Matchstick.

"Good job, Steamed Bun."

"As if you need to say that!" Steamed Bun said incomparably confident, but did he even know what exactly what he had done? Team Happy expressed their doubts. They felt like Qiao Yifan telling Steamed Bun to abuse his CC skills deserved the most credit.

Chapter 1047: Disregard All Else

Had Steamed Bun Invasion's barrage of chaotic attacks happened at any other time, it probably wouldn't have brought him any form of praise from any expert. However, it had coincidentally coincided with this moment, when Excellent Era was trying to bring Lord Grim down while disregarding all else. His actions were extremely disruptive to Excellent Era's tempo.

It wasn't that Excellent Era had no way of dealing with his chaotic attacks, but that they didn't want to waste time on Steamed Bun Invasion. They had just set their target as Lord Grim. If they suddenly focus fired a different target, then their determination just now would be nothing but a joke.

Excellent Era's players never would have thought that Steamed Bun's playstyle would give them so much trouble. Those unpredictable attacks had somehow managed to constrain them.

They couldn't just do nothing about it, but what if this was another of Happy's traps?

Before Xiao Shiqin made a decision, Sun Xiang had already struck first.

It wasn't hard to deal with Steamed Bun, but what made things difficult was that Lord Grim hadn't been killed yet! Under such a chaotic rhythm, Sun Xiang's sudden target switch left an opening that Ye Xiu immediately took advantage of. Lord Grim had been faster and managed to capture One Autumn Leaf first.

Battle God One Autumn Leaf had become Ye Xiu's weapon...

　

Although this had been the case for the past ten years, but this time it was completely different.

One Autumn Leaf was roughly slammed down by Lord Grim and then hurled at Matchstick.

Wang Ze was completely caught off guard. Matchstick and One Autumn Leaf were thrown into a heap on the ground. Lord Grim then turned and threw a Sky Strike at Combat Form who was advancing on him from behind. Combat Form's spear trembled, his Double Stab parrying the first stab and striking with the second.

Double Stab's Cancel and Combo Technique!

The technique Qiu Fei had missed out on using a year ago. The technique that Ye Xiu had used to deal damage to him in the Group Arena a year later.

In reality, Qiu Fei had already mastered this technique and now used it to parry Lord Grim's Sky Strike. The second strike stabbed forward without any hesitation.

Following this strike up with a combo was enough to kill Lord Grim. Lord Grim didn't have that much health left, so this combo didn't need to be too complicated. Qiu Fei had confidence that he could do it.

　

It was just that since this technique was one that was deeply imprinted into his mind, Qiu Fei was rather moved.

"Thank you!"

After sending the two words into the global chat, Qiu Fei went to complete his next actions.

Yet that was when Lord Grim's character suddenly crouched. The second stab of Double Stab hit nothing but air and then Lord Grim's outstretched hands grabbed Combat Form's waist.

　

"You've still got a ways to go!"

Lord Grim straightened, arching backwards and throwing Combat Form head-over-heels into the ground.

Back Throw!

In that moment, One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form, Excellent Era's Battle Mage duo, had been successively smashed into the ground by Lord Grim. The one to disrupt Excellent Era's rhythm was Steamed Bun, but the one to truly turn the situation around was still Ye Xiu!

They really should have wiped him from the game earlier! Xiao Shiqin was vexed, but also knew that regrets would do nothing for them now, determinedly charging forth.

"Ghost Feast," Ye Xiu said in the chat.

"Roger," Qiao Yifan responded. One Inch Ash revealed the edge of his blade and the ghost boundaries that were scattered across the ground swelled up like rolling waves.

Ghost Feast!

The power of the Phantom Demon was released from all the boundaries, exploding and creating a blanket of flashing lights and silhouettes. Xiao Shiqin had charged forwards, but the lighting created by the explosions made it impossible for him to locate his targets. He could only make judgements according to the positions he had last seen of the characters. That was when Life Extinguisher's waist was grabbed.

　

Xiao Shiqin lowered his view and found Steamed Bun Invasion squatting in front of him.

Back Throw...

Life Extinguisher was also slammed to the ground, head-over-heels, by a Back

Throw. That was when the smoke from Ghost Feast's explosion dispersed. Another of Excellent Era's character names went grey. Wang Ze and his Matchstick had been eliminated.

Life Extinguisher swiftly rolled to his feet and saw Lord Grim, One Inch Ash, and Steamed Bun Invasion all advancing on him amidst the dispersing light.

Xiao Shiqin didn't retreat, his finger rapidly tapping. Life Extinguisher immediately summoned three gadgets, splitting up heading for a different character. With the ghost boundaries gone, his gadgets were finally able to shine.

　　

Bang bang bang!

　　

Lord Grim aimed, fired, and with three successive gunshots, caused three explosions with startling speed.

The gadgets that Life Extinguisher had only just sent out were instantly destroyed by Ye Xiu's precise shots.

One Inch Ash's Moonlight Slash swept over and Xiao Shiqin hurriedly had Life Extinguisher dodge. Then, the back of his head was hit by a Brick; Steamed Bun Invasion's Brick.

Xiao Shiqin felt like he was going to go crazy.

This Steamed Bun was sometimes utterly chaotic, not in sync with his teammates at all, but sometimes he somehow managed to get into a dead angle to deliver critical strikes.

Xiao Shiqin had researched every single one of Happy's opponents. For this Steamed Bun, he really didn't know how to describe him because he had never seen a player like this. You had no idea what he was doing. Looking at the previous matches, he seemed to flow with the tactical arrangements, but in the next match, his fluency with the very same tactical arrangements seemed to have vanished.

In Xiao Shiqin's tactic handbook, he had written and erased, erased and rewritten, written and edited the information on Steamed Bun. Every match, he would discover something new, and none of what he saw would repeat.

In the end, in Xiao Shiqin's notebook, only one sentence had remained unchanged in regards to Steamed Bun: an incredibly unstable player.

Yes, that was the final judgement Xiao Shiqin had made for Steamed Bun. As for this match, it adhered to Xiao Shiqin's judgement perfectly. After making this judgement, Xiao Shiqin couldn't think of any way to deal with this player tactically because there was no way of predicting this guy, so he could only deal with his actions as they came.

Yet at the crucial moment, Excellent Era had been sent into chaos by Steamed Bun and then dismantled by Ye Xiu.

Now, Xiao Shiqin himself had been CCed with a Brick from Steamed Bun.

Lord Grim and One Inch Ash's attacks came not a beat too late, knocking Life Extinguisher all over the place. If it wasn't for Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei running over to support, Xiao Shiqin would worry that he was about to be one wave rushed.

As soon as One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrived, Happy's three immediately ran.

"Don't let them get away!" Xiao Shiqin yelled.

After Ghost Feast, the field was completely clean and it was a great time to charge. Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher advanced while keeping an eye out and making sure to interrupt One Inch Ash's attacks. ghost boundaries were all chanted skills. If you managed to quickly notice and interrupt them, it would make a Phantom Demon's life very difficult.

Apart from that, there was also that Steamed Bun Invasion. Half of Xiao Shiqin's focus was on him. He couldn't let this guy throw the situation into chaos again.

Xiao Shiqin keeping an eye on the two by himself was naturally to give Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei a chance. During the Ghost Feast's explosion, he had healed himself a little and was now at 8 percent health. However, his health was still in the range of being wiped out in a single wave by the two members of Excellent Era.

Would there be a reason for Ye Xiu to face the two head on? Of course not. Lord Grim began to lead the two about in all sorts of tactical maneuverings.

Seeing this, Xiao Shiqin felt a headache come on.

Playing dirty...

Just went they had to finish things as quickly as possible, Ye Xiu began to play dirty. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form were melee classes and Lord Grim had ranged firepower. If he started to play dirty, the two would have little chance of catching up quickly.

Xiao Shiqin took a look at the time and contemplated for a moment… it should be about time, right?

A message popped up in Excellent Era's chat.

One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form had suddenly switched directions while chasing Lord Grim.

The viewers quickly understood. These two had gone off to catch the healer Little Cold Hands.

Xiao Shiqin clearly knew where the support zones on the map were. His error in judgement before had naturally been taken note of. That meant that this time he should be correct. Otherwise, if it were somewhere else, the support zone would be way too far.

This time, Xiao Shiqin hadn't guessed wrong. One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form's change in direction really did take them in Little Cold Hands' direction. The two hadn't gone far before they saw Little Cold Hands.

Yet, behind them, Team Happy's other three members lunged for Xiao Shiqin's Life Extinguisher like hungry wolves.

They weren't going to rescue their Cleric?

Xiao Shiqin was puzzled.

　

In reality, they didn't have any way to easily and quickly kill off their opponent's Cleric. However, this was the greatest threat to Excellent Era's victory. Happy would definitely protect their Cleric with their lives.

If that happened, then Excellent Era would have successfully caused a lot of trouble for Happy. With a target to protect, Happy would be a lot less flexible with their movements. And Xiao Shiqin's primary goal in this lure for Happy to support was to trap Ye Xiu and kill Lord Grim. However, he would have never thought that Happy would ignore their Cleric and instead focus their fire on his Life Extinguisher.

　

Trade?

Xiao Shiqin was confused. If this trade was successful, they might be in a three versus two situation, but Lord Grim only had so much health left. He wouldn't be able to turn that situation around with the pitiful amount of healing his unspecialized possessed. Three versus two had a high risk for them, no? What were they relying on? The CC from ghost boundaries? Phantom Demons were good at controlling, but the problem was that ghost boundaries still had their limits. After killing Happy's Cleric, Excellent Era would be much less pressed for time. In this sort of situation, two Battle Mages still had the ability to break through ghost boundaries.

Xiao Shiqin couldn't figure it out, but he wasn't going to stop there and let himself die. Life Extinguisher hurriedly went to retreat, but then realized that Ye Xiu playing dirty just now had "dirty played" his character into a perfect position. His current and only path of retreat was being blocked by Lord Grim.

They had planned this!

After realizing this, Xiao Shiqin felt uneasy. The opponent had planned this. That meant the current situation was still within their expectations.

That was when Xiao Shiqin suddenly saw Sun Xiang yell in the chat: "Holy shit, this Cleric is so fast!!"

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

Give your energy (power stones) to Happy!! If we're #1 at the end of the week, then you'll get your 17 chaps next week! Also, Butterfly Blue (TKA Author) has noticed us :D https://imgur.com/RDqcj5y

Chapter 1048: I’ll Leave it to You

Xiao Shiqin, having seen Ye Xiu's well prepared boxout, he began to feel nervous about the current situation. Seeing Sun Xiang's message in the chat, his heart thudded even louder.

The Cleric was fast? What did that mean? How fast could Happy's Little Cold Hands be?

　

Since Happy's characters had more Orange equipment than anything else, it was easy to see their stats. There was no reason for Little Cold Hands' movement speed to cause One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form surprise.

Unless… he was wearing a completely different set of equipment!

Little Cold Hands had two sets of equipment?

Xiao Shiqin was completely correct. In the broadcast, as well as the statistics given, Little Cold Hand's equipment page was displayed for all to see. As expected, his entire body was covered with equipment bearing movement speed buffs. It completely ignored the stats that Clerics usually needed and focused solely on movement speed alone.

Another set of equipment would definitely increase the weight of character. Clerics were a cloth armored class though. Cloth armor was the lightest of all types of armors so holding onto another set had minimal influence on weight. However, the speed this reckless movement speed buff gave Little Cold Hands really was something that even a God level account like One Autumn Leaf would find shocking.

Had such a strange Cleric ever appeared in the pro circle?

This Cleric had lost everything that made him valuable as a Cleric. His only ability was running. Yet that was exactly what Excellent Era hoped he lacked the most.

Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had already calculated Little Cold Hand's movement speed in comparison to One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form: neck and neck.

　

Under these circumstances, there were only two possibilities if they wanted to catch up. One was to use something that would buff their movement speed or debuff the opponent's movement speed. Battle Mages did, in fact, have such techniques. Among Magic Chasers, Ice Chasers could lower the target's speed and Neutral Chasers could buff one's own movement speed. The problem was that you couldn't just make Chasers whenever you wanted. You had to hit a target to create one, but the two of them couldn't even catch up to the target, so how were they to create any Chasers?

The other possibility relied on pacing. The fastest movement speed relied on Sprinting and Sprinting required stamina, and stamina could only be recovered under certain situations. This pacing would affect the resulting average movement speed. There was no need to worry about Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei. These pro player foundations were solid enough that they definitely had a solid grasp of pacing. What about their opponent? After chasing for a while, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei despaired. As experts, it was clear to them how good the other was once they had began chasing. Little Cold Hands' switching between the different movement speeds told the two immediately that this person had put a lot of effort into training this area. Wanting to catch up through mechanics wasn't going to be easy.

Faced with hopelessness in their mission to kill the Cleric, the two briefly informed Xiao Shiqin of the situation. In that moment, Xiao Shiqin's heart sunk to rock bottom.

The thought of dealing with the Cleric reminded him of a problem: in this match, had Team Happy's healer done anything that a healer was expected to do?

No! Not at all.

He had been part of the starting lineup and then given some insignificant healing in the exchange between the two sides. Since Team Happy didn't need much healing back then, Little Cold Hands had been more valuable in providing DPS buff support with his Holy Commandment than in healing. Then, he had silently left the match to let in Steamed Bun Invasion and maximize Happy's DPS.

.

What a transparent character.

Yet, he was also a character that couldn't be ignored. This was because he was the healer, the very healer that was a decisive factor in most Team Competitions. Especially after Excellent Era's healer had been killed, Little Cold Hands' absence was, in itself, a powerful presence that kept all of Excellent Era on their toes.

Xiao Shiqin naturally had tactics to deal with healers, especially since Happy's healer Little Cold Hands was, in his eyes, one of the biggest weaknesses in Happy. As a character that couldn't not be part of the team competition, his skill level wasn't good enough.

For this, Xiao Shiqin also had a set of tactics. However, he never got the chance to utilize them. Happy didn't give their Cleric very much to do before having him leave silently. Then he had suddenly become the player that would decide the victory of this match. Even knowing that this person wasn't all that skilled, Xiao Shiqin had to place a heavy focus on him at a time like this.

　

Even after realizing that they should place killing Lord Grim above all else, killing Little Cold Hands was still something that Xiao Shiqin placed equal tactical importance on. So, against a Ye Xiu playing dirty, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had received orders to switch targets and go to pincer Little Cold Hands.

Yet, what they found was a Cleric that knew nothing but running...

"Come back…" Xiao Shiqin said helplessly into the chat. If Happy dared to make such arrangements, he believed that this player would have been specially trained in this area. Even if it was Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, they would probably need a lot of time to deal with it. If they stalled for too long, then all that this would end with was these three going forth to support their healer after killing Life Extinguisher.

Another check.

Little Cold Hands had barely done anything a healer should, but managed to pin them with just his status as a healer.

In this moment, a well-known saying in Glory somehow came to Xiao Shiqin's mind: an unused skill is the most terrifying skill.

That's right. This saying had been put into practice as a tactic by Ye Xiu, using Little Cold Hands.

Xiao Shiqin could deeply feel that Happy's tactics for this match was a dense web. Every character, every stage, every detail entangled with one another. Even if you found a way to cut one string, another connection would immediately swarm forth, embedded within one another, uninterruptible and unfathomable.

It seems that… that's it for me...

Xiao Shiqin, in a one versus three, was doing his best to hold on, seeming to want to endure until Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei returned. However, it was unfortunate for him that Ye Xiu, having made so many tactical arrangements, knew how important it was to finish this as soon as possible. Apart from Lord Grim, who was a little more careful, the other two went all out in an effort to kill him.

Kill Lord Grim with disregard to all else?

A few minutes earlier, Xiao Shiqin had just given such an order. Yet, in the blink of an eye, it had switched to Happy killing his Life Extinguisher with disregard to all else.

"I'll leave it to you."

These were the last words Xiao Shiqin left to his teammates. Then, Life Extinguisher fell.

Xiao Shiqin was, without a doubt, a very important member of Team Excellent Era and left the most impact on this match. However, this wasn't any sort of good memory for him. In the tactical battle between him and Ye Xiu, he had been completely defeated. Then, when he had fallen, he had left a terrible situation for his teammates.

Two versus four and their opponents had a healer...

They were in this terrible situation yet he still said "I'll leave it to you"? Shouldn't these words be said when leaving his teammates a winning chance? But did Excellent Era have that now?

The Excellent Era fans were displeased by this. Their boos, for the first time, were aimed towards their own team, their own players. They were displeased and also afraid. Was Excellent Era really going to lose here?

One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrived, saw Life Extinguisher fall and the message Xiao Shiqin had left them in the chat, as well as the situation he had left for them.

Two versus three plus a healer?

In this sort of situation, some teams might have already typed GG, but would Excellent Era?

"Of course not." In the audience, Xu Bin of the Tiny Herb trio said this with confidence, seeing the situation, because Liu Xiaobie was guessing if Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei would GG.

"The situation Xiao Shiqin left them with is still possible to win." Xu Bin continued.

"Oh?"

"Don't you think that to kill Life Extinguisher, Happy's Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash lost a lot of health?" Xu Bin asked.

"So you mean…" Liu Xiaobie seemed to realize something.

"If Xiao Shiqin really wanted to, I think he could've held on until One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form arrived." Xu Bin explained.

"So you mean to say that while Happy was trying their best to crush him, he was also doing his best to deplete Happy's characters of their health. This accelerated Life Extinguisher's death, but he also managed to deal a lot more damage." Liu Xiaobie said.

"That's right, that's why he left such a message. It was because he used all he could to set the situation up for Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei." Xu Bin said.

"This situation is better than keeping his Life Extinguisher alive?" Liu Xiaobie questioned.

"That's what he thinks." Xu Bin said.

"He probably… felt that he couldn't beat Senior Ye Xiu in tactics so left a situation where pure combative strength would decide the victor, right?" Gao Yingjie suddenly cut in.

"Combative strength to decide the victor?" Liu Xiaobie repeated to himself. The current situation was a two versus four and Happy had a healer. This sort of absolute advantage didn't require any tactics anymore, right?

"I never expected that Xiao Shiqin would get a chance to use the tactic he's best at in this situation." Xu Bin said.

"The tactic… Xiao Shiqin is best at?" Liu Xiaobie was confused. He was someone who focused on mechanics. In regards to tactics, he didn't really pay much attention.

"Being underestimated." Xu Bin explained.

"Being underestimated?"

"That's right. He's making his opponent underestimate them." Xu Bin said.

Liu Xiaobie suddenly understood. Xiao Shiqin had come from Thunderclap, which wasn't very strong. If they intentionally had their opponent underestimate them, they would be able to find a lot of opportunities. Yet now, he had come to Excellent Era and they were in the Challenger League nonetheless, so the one tactic he was best at had never had a chance to be used. Just the name Excellent Era was enough to make some opposing teams surrender.

Yet now, Xiao Shiqin had used the death of his own Life Extinguisher to send Excellent Era to an absolute disadvantage. Two versus four and the opposing side had a healer. Even pros like Liu Xiaobie would feel like you could just type 'GG' in this situation. It was clear what Excellent Era's chances of victory were.

If they had an absolute grasp on victory, then they had the right to look down on their opponents, which naturally meant that there was the possibility that they would underestimate their opponents.

In this final moment, Xiao Shiqin had finally used the one method he was best at to set the scene for his teammates.

I'll leave it to you!

This wasn't something said lightly.

Chapter 1049: Worries of Being at Low Health

Being underestimated was the tactic that Xiao Shiqin was most familiar with when he had led Thunderclap. However, if even Xu Bin knew what Xiao Shiqin was good at, it meant that it wasn't a secret. This was Xiao Shiqin's tactical style.

To put it simply, it could be described with nine words: show weakness to the enemies, entice them to relax.

The theory was simple, but actually employing it wasn't easy, especially when everyone knew that was what you were good at. Whenever anyone faced Xiao Shiqin's team, they couldn't help but remind themselves to focus and not be careless.

However, emotions weren't always dictated by the mind. The tides constantly shifted in a match and after overcoming numerous difficulties, it was hard not to be excited when one had the upper hand. These were the places where Xiao Shiqin placed his traps. He used ample preparations to contend against a moment of lapse from the enemy due to excitement. He would bait the other side into becoming negligent.

In reality, Excellent Era hadn't prepared to do this in this match. There was something that Excellent Era had that was different than Thunderclap. They had stronger characters and better players.

2v4. Excellent Era was definitely in a disadvantageous situation, but with Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei, perhaps they had the ability to make a comeback?

Xiao Shiqin was gambling on the ability of these two. He had done his best to pave a path for them. In terms of numbers, Excellent Era was losing, but in Xiao Shiqin's final moments, he had traded his health away to deal massive damage to his opponents. Although he had been killed, he had greatly reduced Steamed Bun Invasion's and One Inch Ash's health.

Lord Grim had even less health than those two. With Little Cold Hands not there yet, it was hard to say what the outcome of the match would be!

While Tiny Herb's group analyzed the situation, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei didn't waste a second and immediately attacked.

Shattering the Land!

　

Qiu Fei's Combat Form opened with a high-level skill. The AoE attack was used to break the ghost boundaries. You don't want to leave your ghost boundaries? Then eat this move. Let's trade.

Happy's three characters were at low health. Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash had lost a lot of health because of Life Extinguisher. Sure enough, they didn't dare stay within the ghost boundaries and eat the high-level skill. The three characters avoided Shattering the Lands. One Autumn Leaf rushed forward, targeting Lord Grim.　

Ye Xiu didn't fight him. He dodged the attack and Aerial Fired away. Steamed Bun Invasion ran over from the side with a brick in his hand, preparing to smash it into One Autumn Leaf's head. Qiu Fei saw this and rushed over. Before Steamed Bun Invasion could throw his brick, a spear flashed in front of him, forcing him to jump out of the away of it.

Qiu Fei reacted swiftly. His spear nipped at Steamed Bun. A Dragon Tooth and then a Falling Flower Palm. Steamed Bun wasn't able to dodge it and was hit!

Before Steamed Bun Invasion could be sent flying away, he was blocked off by One Autumn Leaf. Sun Xiang actually ignored Lord Grim and switched to Steamed Bun Invasion.

Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash ran over hastily to rescue Steamed Bun, but Phantom Demons were good at controlling the field, not support. If he had to rescue a horse from a river, his class felt somewhat lacking. Laying down ghost boundaries could only restrict the enemies. It couldn't stop the enemies from attacking. Happy's characters didn't have much health left. Just restricting the enemies wouldn't be enough.

Steamed Bun and Qiao Yifan weren't able to stop the two Battle Mage's assault. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim was forced to turn back, attacking from long-range to close-range. Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei dodged, while continuing to attack Steamed Bun Invasion and One Inch Ash. When Lord Grim joined the fight, Combat Form suddenly turned around and thrust his spear fiercely with a Furious Dragon Strikes the Heart.

Sun Xiang remained focused and continued to attack Steamed Bun Invasion. One Inch Ash's attacks? Take them! One Autumn Leaf was the strongest character on this battlefield. He was also in the best condition. A ghostblade's attack could be completely ignored as long as it wasn't an Ice Boundary type of CC.

The Excellent Era duo clearly held the initiative, but had Xiao Shiqin's underestimate-us tactic been effective? It was hard to say because the emotional changes were subtle. Hoping the other side would completely underestimate them and stop concentrating on the match obviously wasn't realistic.

However, the value of Xiao Shiqin's final struggle could be seen. Facing One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form, Ye Xiu had the most pressure on him. His Lord Grim had the lowest health, but he had to face the dangers and help Steamed Bun and Qiao Yifan.

As for Happy's Cleric?

Happy needed their Cleric too urgently. The spectators could see that Little Cold Hands was almost there. Just a bit more and he could start healing.

But at this moment, Combat Form left the battle and headed towards Little Cold Hands. Ye Xiu, Steamed Bun, and Qiao Yifan had been left to Sun Xiang alone to fight.

It was a 1v3 by a Battle Mage. Tang Rou had done this previously.

But the difference was that Tang Rou had been the one initiated on. She baited the enemies to attack and then struggled to survive. Sun Xiang's situation was different. He faced Happy's three characters alone. He wasn't defending. He was attacking.

Kill!

It was a 1v3, but One Autumn Leaf put on an aggressive posture.　　

Everyone was shocked, but no one doubted Sun Xiang's actions.

He could back up his actions.

He was a top God in the Alliance. He held the strongest character in this battle. He might have three opponents, but they were at low health. If they just stood there like sandbags, One Autumn Leaf could kill them in an instant. He could probably kill the three of them faster than Combat Form could kill Little Cold Hands.

The three weren't sandbags though. However, they were feeling somewhat helpless against Sun Xiang's attacks.　　

They couldn't just eat these attacks. If they truly traded blow for blow with One Autumn Leaf, they might be the ones to fall, not One Autumn Leaf.

Clerics were the saving grace when a character was at low health. However, their saving grace was being blocked by Qiu Fei. When An Wenyi saw Combat Form charging towards his Little Cold Hands, he turned directions and ran. He didn't have confidence in healing his allies while fending off a pro player simultaneously.

Ye Xiu, Qiao Yifan, and Steamed Bun needed to fight with Sun Xiang, while figuring out a way to receive Little Cold Hands. Even though they held the numbers advantage, they were still in a difficult position.

　

"Happy should have received their healer sooner. They were a bit careless." Li Yibo remarked.　

"It's probably because Sun Xiang's and Qiu Fei's turnaround had been too quick. As soon as Life Extinguisher died, they arrived and started attacking. Happy didn't have any time to receive their healer." Pan Lin said.

"The problem is that Happy never showed any intentions of doing so. Ye Xiu's Lord Grim had originally been Aerial Firing away to escape from the battle, but he chose to come back." Li Yibo said.

"But if he didn't come back and left One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun Invasion to fight with the Excellent Era Battle Mage duo, by the time he received the Cleric, those two might already be dead. Those two had very little health left." Pan Lin said.　　

"Xiao Shiqin's final struggle like a fish in a net really dealt a huge blow to Happy." Li Yibo said.　

Pan Lin and Li Yibo talked back and forth during this intense battle until they ended up speechless. After discussing with each other, Happy's difficult position at that time was instantly made clear. Although Xiao Shiqin was no longer there, the final exchange before his death had truly given Happy a big blow. If he had tried to survive for as long as possible, he wouldn't have dealt as much damage. Even if Excellent Era had three players right now, Happy wouldn't be in as bad of a situation.

Right now, Sun Xiang was holding off three Happy players. Why? Because their health was low. With low health, they could not employ any forceful methods. Split up and run? That would result in one of their players dying. And then? One Autumn Leaf had four Neutral Chasers hovering around him. All of them had been formed by Sun Xiang intentionally. He was saving them specifically for that situation. He also had Dragon Breaks the Ranks, which was no longer on cooldown. He could use it any time to chase after a target.

Being amply prepared, Sun Xiang was even hoping that Happy would make such a move. That would give them an opportunity to turn the tides. He was confident that he could finish off two players before they reached their healer. Afterwards, it would be a 2v2. Once that happened, the healer wouldn't be as threatening, especially one at that skill level.

The Happy fans cheering for their victory were instantly stunned. On the other hand, the eyes of a few of the Excellent Era fans suddenly brightened. When they saw the current situation and then listened to the two commentators, they finally realized what Xiao Shiqin had done.

"Let's go, Excellent Era!!" The Excellent Era fans suddenly exploded into cheers. The final moments of the match were approaching. Their players were fighting, so they couldn't relax. Even if the players on stage couldn't hear them, they also needed to strive for victory alongside their players.

An Wenyi had Little Cold Hands run away from Combat Form. Seeing the opponent wasn't letting go of him, he hastily switched out his equipment. He had originally thought that he would be healing after getting there, so he had switched to his healing equipment. He hadn't expected that Happy's four players would be suppressed by Excellent Era's two players. As he ran, he searched for opportunities to get closer to the battle. It would be helpful if he could cast a few instant heals. Happy's three characters needed healing too urgently.

However, Qiu Fei wasn't going to let him do as he pleased. Combat Form clung onto Little Cold Hands, blocking the way over to the battle. Little Cold Hands could only turn around. There weren't any opportunities to heal. The only thing that he would meet would be Combat Form's painful attacks. In this situation, he could only run farther and farther away.

It hadn't been easy to get a healer advantage, yet because of this, the healer wouldn't be able to join the battle?

Happy's supporters felt unreconciled. They hoped that Happy had some way out.　

At this moment, an opening suddenly appeared in the 1v3 location. Lord Grim had just been fighting One Autumn Leaf, when he suddenly turned around and flipped his two hands.

"Cloud Grasping Fist!!"

Who knew how many people shouted at this moment. Lord Grim used Cloud Grasping Fist again, the move that had won them two miracles this match.

Was a third miracle going to appear?

No!

One Autumn Leaf's Evil Annihilation flew over. One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun Invasion tried to block it, but One Autumn Leaf suddenly switched moves. The spear suddenly slanted upwards into a Sky Strike.　　

The two were caught off guard by the Sky Strike and were knocked into the air. As Evil Annihilation fell, it switched directions and shot towards Lord Grim as if no one had ever tried to intercept it.

However, this slight delay allowed Lord Grim's Cloud Grasping First to come out and grab Combat Form. However, Lord Grim couldn't continue because One Autumn Leaf's attack had arrived. If he continued, he could hold onto Combat Form longer, but it would be quickly interrupted. What's worse, if the attack hit, Sun Xiang could very well combo him to his death.

Ye Xiu had no choice but to cancel his skill and retreat. Those with hopes for Cloud Grasping Fist were disappointed. Then, the two in the air let out attacks. Not waiting to land, Steamed Bun Invasion raised his left hand and threw with his right hand. A Brick concealed inside a Sand Toss was thrown out.

This trick didn't escape Sun Xiang's eyes. He was very focused right now. He quickly deduced the trajectory of the brick before turning his head to avoid Sand Toss's effect. But during that instant, Qiao Yifan's One Inch Ash immediately started casting. Frost started to form from the tip of his sword, Ice Boundary!

Ice Boundary was the most effective CC skill against One Autumn Leaf. Qiao Yifan hadn't usd it because he couldn't find an opportunity to. Sun Xiang was clearly wary of a Phantom Demon's threat and took him very seriously.

But because of the Cloud Grasping Fist mix-up, Qiao Yifan was finally able to find an opening. This opening might not mean a guaranteed hit, but it was worth a try.

Before he could finish casting, One Autumn Leaf turned his head back. Sun Xiang's actions were extremely precise. He only dodged the Sand Toss at the last moment. After turning his head, he had more than enough time to interrupt One Inch Ash's chant. But at the same time, Lord Grim strode over, using his body to block Sun Xiang's line of sight.

This block alone won enough time for One Inch Ash. When One Autumn Leaf pulled away to get a better view, he saw One Inch Ash's taichi drop down as ice spun around its tip.

Dragon Breaks the Rank!

Sun Xiang activated a high-level skill. A dragon rushed towards One Inch Ash.

The Ice Boundary fell, but One Autumn Leaf was able to escape from its range using the high-level skill. One Inch Ash wasn't sent flying from the attack. One Autumn Leaf pressed down on his Evil Annihilation, holding One Inch Ash still. Sun Xiang was clear that his suppression over the three Happy players had ended. He at least needed to kill off one opponent though.

However, he hadn't expected Lord Grim to suddenly appear beside him.

His appearance was too sudden. Dragon Breaks the Ranks had little ending lag, but Sun Xiang was unable to react in time. Lord Grim grabbed One Autumn Leaf and then threw him into One Inch Ash's Ice Boundary.

It was just a Toss.

Chapter 1050: The Race to Kill

One Autumn Leaf had high resistance, but not enough as that he could completely ignore the freezing effects of Ice Boundary. He wouldn't be completely frozen, but his movement speed being reduced was a reality that was already occurring.

No one bothered with him any longer. Lord Grim, One Inch Ash, Steamed Bun Invasion all darted towards Combat Form from their respective positions. Even people who hadn't played Glory, but only similar games would know what the key was to this current situation.

Seeing the situation here change abruptly, An Wenyi knew what he had to do next. He no longer focused on running, prepared to switch all his equipment at a moment's notice. The time for him to heal had finally come.

　

The situation of the field was ever changing and not something that anyone could be certain of.

　

But at this moment, the situation was clear.

The key to victory was if Happy could regroup with their healer or not. Their health had all fallen to a dangerous low. Lord Grim had 5 percent, One Inch Ash at 8 percent and Steamed Bun Invasion at 10 percent.

This sort of health was at the range where powerful character like those of Excellent Era's could take down in one wave. On the other hand, of Excellent Era's two characters, One Autumn Leaf still had 67 percent of his health and Combat Form had 55 percent. These two characters hadn't received any critical damage. The damage they had taken was accumulated through exchanges of attacks. With this sort of advantage in health, Happy wouldn't come out well even in a three versus two without some good healing.

Charge!

If they entered Little Cold Hands' healing range, then they could launch a full-on offensive without worrying. Then, what Excellent Era's duo would be facing was the same difficulty and awkwardness Ye Xiu and co had when they went up against Sun Xiang and One Autumn Leaf.

An Wenyi had begun to maneuver himself, trying to find a way to get support. However, Qiu fei was still locked onto him, chasing him further and further away.

Most people wouldn't understand the full situation, but they could still tell what their intentions were.

In terms of movement speed, Lord Grim and co didn't have any advantages over Combat Form. If Combat Form could continue to herd Little Cold Hands like this, then the distance between the three sides would remain constant. Then, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf would be able to charge back into the fray.

This sort of shocking occurrence was being realized under Qiu Fei's strict and efficient pathing. When Lord Grim and the other begun their chase, he had accelerated as well. Little Cold Hands was locked out of range by him, only able to run farther and farther away. He might not be able to keep this up forever, but it wouldn't be long before One Autumn Leaf managed to escape the Ice Boundary.

　

Were they going to lose this advantage they had fought so hard to gain?

Happy's supporters felt cold sweat in their fists. Everyone's gaze all focused on a single person.

Little Cold Hands.

That's right. The only one who could make a breakthrough in this sort of situation was him. With his skill level, he really couldn't face pro players properly, but just dodging like this wouldn't help the situation any, only bring it to a deadlock. No matter what, he had to take a risk.

　

It's on!

　

The calm and rational An Wenyi found that he had no other choice but to take this risk and hardened his heart.

　

Little Cold Hand abruptly switched out several pieces of equipment and his movement speed immediately plummeted. Then, he turned and charged.

　　

He had to charge into the fray.

However, he wasn't the only one who understood this. Qiu Fei had clearly realized, too, and had been waiting for An Wenyi to let go and charge. Little Cold Hands' current actions were within his expectations.

Dragon Rises from the Sea!

Cloud Whirling Windstorm!

　

In these desperate moments, no one would hold back anything. They would do everything they could, use everything they could. Qiu Fei's Combat Form successively used these two big skills, and this was something he had also done in the group arena. He used the chaotic magical energy from Cloud Whirling Windstorm to spread the vapor from Dragon Rises from the Sea across the area, creating a blanket of mist.

　　

Hide the characters, block the view!

This use of effects wasn't some sort of signature move. Zhang Jiale's Hundred Blossoms style was representative of using skill effects in this style. However, used now, Little Cold Hands and Happy's three attempts to find each other became like looking for needles in a haystack. Combat Form hid within the mist, no doubt aiming to strike at Little Cold Hands. When incapable of seeing where attacks were coming from, An Wenyi couldn't find a target even if he wanted to heal.

　

Angel Wings!

　

An Wenyi dealt with this with an Angel Wings. Snowy white wings made from holy light sprouted from his back and Little Cold Hands floated into the air. He wasn't very high up, but it helped him gain a better view.

An Wenyi was too rational. He didn't think for a second that his skill level was high enough to use pathing to evade a pro player's blockade so he didn't even try. What he wanted to do was grasp a chance to send out a heal. His goal was that simple.

　

The floating Little Cold Hands charged forwards, using his height to locate Lord Grim and the others once more. In the distance, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had also escaped the Ice Boundary and was dashing over. He had originally had four neutral Chasers prepared, but unfortunately, Chasers weren't food. You had to use them to attack in order to get the buffs. Currently, he had no attack targets nearby so even with the four Chasers, he couldn't buff his movement speed.

However, he wasn't the focus of the match right now.

Dragon Tooth!

　　

Combat Form, amidst the mist, had attacked, his spear stabbing upwards in a diagonal towards Little Cold Hands.

An Wenyi wasn't useless. He was naturally on his guard against Combat Form's attacks, hurriedly swerving to the side while sending a Sacred Fire in return.

Combat Form easily dodged, his attack rhythm not affected in the slightest. After the Dragon Tooth came a Double Stab, spear thrusting forwards twice. This time, An Wenyi had trouble dealing with it. When facing a mechanics expert, someone whose mechanics wasn't all that great would have trouble keeping up with their opponent's combo pace. After using his all to avoid these two strikes, An Wenyi knew he was at his limit. He wouldn't be able to dodge the following strike.

　

That was when three cannon blasts sounded.

　

Anti-Tank Missiles!

　　

The three successive booms of this skill's activation were too striking and the only one that could use this skill currently on the field was Lord Grim.

Combat Form hastily dodged to the side, but his attack didn't stop. A Circle Swing finally pulled Little Cold Hands down from midair. At the same time, he saw the cross in Little Cold Hands' hands flash with sacred light and a Holy Cure was clearly sent out.

　

How could this be!

Qiu Fei was stunned for an instant before realizing that while there were three blasts of a canon, no missiles had come. Yet soon enough, with a string of gunshots, a hail of bullets arrived.

Lord Grim had entered attacking range!

Qiu Fei realized he had been tricked.

The mist from the attack effect had cut the two sides out of each others line of sight, but also hindered his own awareness of the situation. He had thought Lord Grim, gleaning his position from his attacks at Little Cold Hands, had launched his own attack. Dodging had slowed his Circle Swing down just a little.

Though this was enough to catch Little Cold Hands, the Cleric had managed to rush out a heal in that time.

If Qiu Fei's calculations were correct, Lord Grim and the others should be just out of range.

However, the absence of the Anti-Tank Missiles alerted him to what had occurred.

Lord Grim's Anti-Tank Missiles weren't an attack, but an Aerial Cannon. Using Qiu Fei's limited awareness, he had tricked Qiu Fei with the sound of the Anti-Tank Missiles. His dodging had slowed down his attack pace while Lord Grim's skill had increased his movement speed. The combination of this had given An Wenyi a chance to heal in that instant and An Wenyi didn't waste it. His grasp of timing was his greatest talent.

　　

Holy Cure instantly pulled Lord Grim's health back up by 8 percent to 13 percent. The healing power of a proper healing was something a part-timer like Lord Grim could hope to achieve.

　

Following this, Lord Grim, having closed in, started to use firepower to suppress Combat Form. Since he had entered attacking range, he had also entered Little Cold Hands' healing range. No matter what, letting the healer fully regroup with Happy's three spelled defeat for them. He had to work harder on creating an opening.

Sky Strike, Dragon Tooth, Falling Flower Palm!

This was one of the most classic three-skill Battle Mage combo. After sending a target airborne, landing a Dragon Tooth and then a Falling Flower Palm, Little Cold Hands was thrown far off by this combo.

　

Qiu Fei didn't try to boxout Little Cold Hands any longer. Lord Grim had already reached his side, so how would he possibly get the chance to?

Whirling around, Combat Form launched a furious offense in disregard to everything else, forcing Lord Grim backwards, determined to not let him take another step forwards.

　

One Inch Ash and Steamed Bun Invasion quickly entered the fray and behind them, Sun Xiang's One Autumn Leaf had finally arrived as well. The value of Qiu Fei boxing out Little Cold Hands was apparent here. Sun Xiang hadn't left the battle for too long. After having to hold it in for so long, he was merciless with his attacks.

"Kill them quickly!"

　

Sun Xiang yelled into the channel.

Racing to kill them was, naturally, a race to kill them before Little Cold Hands returned. Having been thrown out by the Battle Mage, Little Cold Hands was rushing over as fast as he could.

Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei didn't think about blocking Little Cold Hands anymore because they knew that with Ye Xiu here, they wouldn't have another chance.

Race to kill them! They had to race to kill them no matter the cost; they had to kill them before Little Cold Hands arrived.

In that moment, there was no tactics, no dodging, no parrying, just attack after attack as if their characters had endless health. They bled continuously even as they forced their opponents to do the same. Everyone's hand speed had erupted to a peak state and the pacing of the battle was terrifyingly fast. All sorts of skills flew about and blood splattered everywhere.

　　

Had they lost all sanity?

No!

Excellent Era was at a state where they had to risk it all. The healer was fast approaching so all they could do was race to finish this. As for Happy? Low health was their problem. Even with a healer, if their health was too low and the opponent was brute forcing DPS, not even a healer would be able to save them. Sp all Happy could do was respond with equal mercilessness, competing with Excellent Era on DPS.

Chapter 1051: Never Meant to be Played Alone

What would the result of this clash be?

No one could predict it and no one had the time to predict it. This DPS competition really only lasted for a duration less than twenty seconds. Everyone used their most efficient methods of DPS. Those slow and powerful skills were all a waste of time in this situation.

　

The health bars of both sides were plummeting, but from this, it was evident that in the wild dash to kill the other, there was a method to their madness. Happy was evidently focusing their fire on Combat Form. Combat Form's original 55 percent of health was instantly forgotten. From when the fight erupted, this number had been dropping constantly, plummeting in free fall.

Considering character strength, Happy was nothing compared to Excellent Era, but Happy had an extra person. The three focused their fire and, in this battle where defense was neglected for more DPS, it would be easy to wipe a character out.

But for Happy? Their actual situation wasn't as good as things seemed. Even combined, the health of their characters were less than either of Excellent Era's. An extra person gave them more DPS. However, without a solid amount of health as a foundation, how could they make sure they would be able to keep up this DPS? The one with the most health among the three of them was Lord Grim's 13 percent. In this situation with everyone going all out, he'd be wiped out instantly if One Autumn Leaf and Combat Form focused their fire on him.

Happy was at a major disadvantage. The only thing that could turn this around for them was their Cleric, but what would happen during the time it took for their Cleric to arrive? Would Happy be able to hold on until then?

This period of time was a mere instant, but it was in this mere instant that the audience personally saw an advantage that was unique to the unspecialized class: the seamless transition between all of the low level skills.

No single class had so many short CD low level skills. With the battle where it was, no one would wait for all your skills to come off cooldown before unleashing them, so, for any class, after the battle began, there would never be a time where its skill tree would be wholesome because used skills would go on cooldown. The more intense the battle, the more skills were on cooldown.

Excellent Era versus Happy had already gotten to a point where the battle raged so intensely, that it couldn't get more intense. Under this situation, Lord Grim's skill options was still mostly complete.

You could only say mostly. After all, Lord Grim was also continuously using skills and low leveled skills also had cooldowns. However, this mostly complete was an absolute advantage over any other character in this fight.

　

The battle had reached its peak. Even the greatest player would feel like they didn't have enough skills.

Seamlessly cycling through a comboed set of skills? That was PvE. Only PvE would have something like that. This was PvP and it was a high-end PvP match. There was no time for anyone to cycle through skills without disruption like in PvE.

　

A fast-paced battle would soon make people feel like they had no skills to use and less and less choices to make.

Pro players were good at controlling their rhythm as to not fall into an awkward disadvantage. However, no matter what, they still had to use skills and there would always be cooldowns. As the pace went up, the room they had to maneuver would decrease.

But the unspecialized didn't have this problem!

Thus, when Happy was fighting with their backs to the wall and both sides felt like their skills weren't enough for the battle, Ye Xiu's Lord Grim still managed to fight at his fastest pace. While the offense of the others began to seem rather thinned out, Lord Grim still had sleeves full of tricks.

Not needing to worry about cooldowns and having skills to use anywhere anywhen was something that probably only occurred in the wet dreams of most players. Yet now, the unspecialized had turned this dream into a reality. Especially in this sort of crucial moment, the unspecialized's ability was magnified further as the opponent's skills diminished.

An unused skill was always the most terrifying skill.

And the unspecialized's skills were always at an unused state because he had more skills, because his skills had shorter cooldowns.

Happy managed to hold on in the few seconds it took Little Cold Hands to arrive, but no one fully understood what, exactly, happened in those few seconds. The advantage unspecialized had in this crucial moment wasn't something bystanders could glean, but those who were directly involved. Only Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei truly understood what sort of disadvantage they had when fighting against Lord Grim.

As for the commentators of the broadcast?

They were still lamenting over Little Cold Hands' arrival for Excellent Era!

"No, it's not over yet!" Li Yibo suddenly exclaimed.

Lord Grim's best efforts in restricting his opponents were just to help his own side endure this period. This was already an absurd result. However, Sun Xiang and QIu Fei's offense hadn't been truly interrupted. Happy's three had still taken quite a few hits, it was just that none of them had been fatal.

With Little Cold Hands' arrival, he saw the pitiful health bars of Happy's trio and didn't dare use chanted skills. He was afraid they might die in the time it took him to complete his chants.

Instantly, two instant cast Cures were sent over.

And then? There was no "then". After that, healing would require chanting. The three instant cast Cures had all been thrown out already.

Healers weren't gods. There was still a limit to their healing ability.

However, Happy's characters really had too little blood. At this point, they couldn't really hold on for much longer. There were situations that even a healer couldn't save.

Having used up all his instant casts, An Wenyi could only start to chant a heal. Yet right when he was about to do so, he suddenly saw a message from Ye Xiu in the chat: Holy Com.

Holy Commandment?

Not wanting healing at such a time but DPS support?

Everyone who saw Ye Xiu's command was completely stunned, all thinking they were hallucinating and wondering if this abbreviation had some other meaning. It couldn't possibly be that he wanted the healer to not heal, but support their offense?

The audience was hesitant, but the players on the field weren't. Seeing the order, An Wenyi didn't think twice before a Holy Commandment was immediately thrown out. The target was Combat Form who had less health and was obviously Happy's focus. If An Wenyi couldn't even make this sort of judgement, when he really had to apologize for all the effort Ye Xiu had gone through to dig him out of those players in Tyrannical Ambition.

The Holy Commandment enveloped Combat Form. It wasn't just the audience that was shocked by the Holy Commandment from little Cold Hands, even Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei felt puzzled.

However, they had no time to stop and consider. With the opponent's Cleric here, they were pressed for time. If they couldn't storm their opponents and Little Cold Hands managed to hold their health up, then the ending would be set.

　

Attack!

Continue the attack.

　

Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei had long since been prepared to mount their furious attack against this healing.

This was the scene Xiao Shiqin had set for them. After bringing down the health of two members of Happy, Sun Xiang and Qiu Fei would use the time it took for the Cleric to arrive to intensify their attacks. Being able to take down even one before the Cleric arrived would allow them to maintain a chance a victory. It wasn't easy.

We can do it!

Sun Xiang and QIu Fei were red eyed with bloodthirsty. Nothing else existed for them. They stared at the last scraps of blood that Happy's characters had, attacking, taking it down.

Success!

　

Steamed Bun Invasion's health was wiped, a situation even a healer couldn't save. Steamed Bun Invasion fell to Excellent Era's offense.

And then? One Inch Ash's health was already in the decimal range, could they take him down, too?

Another one fallen!

One Inch Ash fell, a second kill.

Success!

Two versus two, so what if there's a healer? The eventual victory will be ours! Sun Xiang's heart soared and there was finally only one opponent left in front of him. He had One Autumn Leaf lunge wildly. He could finally defeat this person.

Who would've expected that Lord Grim would suddenly jump up, sending out Anti-Tank Missiles at Combat Form, his characters flying backwards from the recoil.

Sun Xiang turned his view with this attack. What he saw caused him to charge over like he had gone crazy, trying to use his own body to block the three Anti-Tank Missiles.

But it was too late. Everything was too late. Lord Grim didn't just send out Anti-Tank Missiles. A grenade had also rolled over, across the ground.

　

Combat Form, Qiu Fei's Combat Form had run out of health.

The shadow that had been with him the whole way, helping him. In truth, Sun Xiang hadn't thought that he was very important, but in that moment, he truly wished to save Combat Form from death, willing, even, to use his own character, One Autumn Leaf, to shield his shadow from death.

But it was all too late. Engulfed by the light of the explosion, Combat Form could no longer escape and his health fell to zero. Combat Form, he had fallen.

AAAAAHHHHHH!

In the playor booth, no one could hear how Sun Xiang had screamed. One Autumn Leaf suddenly turned, a skill that had just come off of cooldown was flung forth.

Dragon Breaks the Ranks!

　

In pursuit of Lord Grim, who had flown out backwards, he caught up in the blink of an eye.

"Die!!" Sun Xiang bellowed out through gritted teeth, uncaring that the other couldn't hear this roars.

Lord Grim, airborne, was incapable of dodging this strike. He could only unsheath his sword to Guard, but he was still knocked out of the air from the force of the attack.

Yet before Lord Grim even hit the ground, a holy light washed over him.

Holy Heal.

This was the Heal that required the longest cast time, but also healed the largest amount of health and it accurately engulfed Lord Grim.

15%!

　

The high-end heal that needed an immense cast time instantly pulled Lord Grim's health up by that much.

　

Sun Xiang felt his despair return.

One versus two and the opponent had a healer, this situation...

　

"Didn't I tell you before, Glory was never meant to be played alone. Now, Sun Xiang… what do you say?" Lord Grim sent in the public chat as the Holy Heal descended.

Glory was never meant to be played alone?

Saying this when you were fighting two on one with a healer on your side? This made everyone speechless, but no one could retort it. This was an example of a situation going from hopeful to despair.

Sun Xiang hadn't wanted to give up yet and aimed to hurry and take out Little Cold Hands first. However, the moment he saw Ye Xiu's words, his fighting spirit extinguished. He knew that he wouldn't get a chance to do so.

"Yes… Glory... was never meant to be played alone…" After replying with the same words, Sun Xiang didn't type GG. He directly left the match.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

GG

Chapter 1052: We Are The Champions

It… it's over?

The system announced Team Happy's victory, and after that the system automatically gave a few close ups of the surviving characters. Shots of Lord Grim, with his colorful equipment, and Little Cold Hands at all sorts of angles were being displayed on the screen.

However, no one really reacted properly. Their hearts were still in their throats, waiting for a final explosion of attacks. This was because One Autumn Leaf still had over forty percent of his health left. Though he had to fight one on two, Excellent Era had a lead in the group arena. If he went all out, he might be able to at least take one person down even if he couldn't get them both. That way, it would at least end with a tie. Yet Sun Xiang had just the match left like that?

Did the system disconnect him?

No one dared to believe the reality before their eyes, and even the referee had to check the game's system to confirm that Sun Xiang really did surrender and it wasn't some sort of mistake.

After that, he finally announced that Happy had won the team competition, gaining two points. In the end of the Challenger League, Team Happy won 2 to 1 against Team Excellent Era.

"Fuck!!!"

An enraged bellow came from Excellent Era's bench. Their boss, Tao Xuan, suddenly seemed to have been possessed by the Battle God or something and jumped up, smashing the water bottle in his hand against the side of the stage.

They lost? They actually lost?

Tao Xuan didn't dare to believe his eyes. His Team Excellent Era, the powerhouse Team Excellent Era, with top players like Sun Xiang and Xiao Shiqin, and spectacular characters like One Autumn Leaf and Life Extinguisher had actually lost to the grassroots team Ye Xiu had led out from nowhere? How was that possible!?

"Hahaha, well played, well played." That was when someone from Team Happy's bench also stood up. Wei Chen extended his hands towards Excellent Era's bench, purposefully applauding for them to see and hear. His expression was one of nonchalance though, as if there was nothing much to their victory.

"Stop pretending, alright?" Chen Guo, who had almost began crying when their victory was announced, didn't know whether to laugh or cry at Wei Chen's actions. This guy had obviously been jumping for joy at this, but purposefully feigned nonchalance to anger Excellent Era. You might say that, but your tone is still trembling, man.

"We won!" Chen Guo turned her head around and said to Su Mucheng, who sat next to her. Su Mucheng was supposed to be an opponent in this competition, and she was even responsible for the point that Excellent Era had gained, but Chen Guo saw her as one of their own.

"Yes, we won…" Su Mucheng nodded.

"I'm glad I didn't waste my time coming out here." Sun Zheping let out a long breath, stretching out in his seat.

"We won, we won, we won!" Although Luo Ji hadn't gone up in this match, he was just as happy as everyone else was. He wanted to find someone to share this victory with, yet when he turned his head, he found that it was Mo Fan that sat closest to him, staring at the stage with his characteristic emotionless expression.

"We won!" Luo Ji hollered at him. Mo Fan turned his head, looking at him emotionlessly.

"Er…" Luo Ji decided to walk a few more steps so he could celebrate with the others. He charged forward and joined Chen Guo and the others. Yet, he hadn't noticed that, although Mo Fan hadn't spoken, though he was still stoic, his hand, in that moment, had clenched into a fist,

Happy's bench had exploded with celebration, while Excellent Era's bench was dead silent. Their boss's explosion of rage caused them to shrink back into their seats with their heads lowered, as if no one could see them that way.

That was when the audience there finally recovered.

They won. Happy actually won.

Seven Fields opened his mouth and stayed stunned for a full half minute until the person next to him nudged him.

"Fuck, fuck fuck fuck, fuck!!!" Seven Fields turned this way and that, cursing and spitting everywhere, but none of the people around him minded, grabbing him tightly. "We won."

"Yes, we won!"

"Holy fuck, we won!!!" Seven Fields gave the loudest cheer yet. Happy's group of loyal fans, surrounded by Excellent Era's fans, erupted as one. They threw everything in their hands that they could throw up into the air, cheering and yelling, singing and dancing about. The security guard in the stadium were poised, ready to take action just in case, but didn't go up to stop them. Happy's victory truly hadn't come easily. If they didn't allow them to celebrate, that would just be cruel.

As for Excellent Era's fans? They were all dumbstruck.

　

Contemplate if Sun Xiang's departure from the game was accidental or not? They weren't in the mood for that anymore. No matter what, the end was set and Happy was the final victor. As for their Team Excellent Era, would they have to stay in the Challenger League another year? They were a powerhouse team with God level players and God-level accounts, but they had to sink in the Challenger League for another year? Currently, all the Excellent Era fans could feel was sadness, disappointment, and discomfort.

"Happy… Happy won?" In the broadcast, when the system announced the victor, commentator Pan Lin had announced the result with a tone full of uncertainty. Even he was incredulous.

"Yes, Happy won. A miracle, they've truly created a real miracle." Li Yibo, on the other hand, had gotten back into character and couldn't help but sigh with deep emotion.

"This is completely unexpected! Happy has defeated Excellent Era, winning this year's Challenger League. They will become newcomers to the Pro Alliance next season. As for Excellent Era? This powerhouse team that created the only dynasty in Glory history is once again subject to another year of the Challenger League and the one to put them into this situation is, coincidentally, the ex-captain that built that very dynasty. For Excellent Era, is he an angel or a demon? I believe all of Excellent Era's people are feeling very conflicted right now. They must regret letting Ye Xiu enter retirement so easily."

After Pan Lin recovered from his shock, he leapt back into character. Happy's victory was truly unexpected, but there was much to say about it, too. Pan Lin swiftly formulated a response and began to commentate.

Now, the award ceremony began immediately after the match. All of Happy's players would have to go onstage to obtain their awards. Chen Guo was their boss, but she was also a registered member of Team Happy. Though she had barely played a single match, she still had the right to come onstage. Chen Guo was very proud of herself, walking on stage with the others. Onstage, the players had already stepped out of their booths.

Ye Xiu, Tang Rou, Steamed Bun, Wu Chen, Qiao Yifan, An Wenyi...

Everyone's gaze landed on them. Apart from Ye Xiu, the others were complete unknowns. Yet just now, they had created a miracle. They really defeated Excellent Era in the Challenger League, taking the only slot and entering the Alliance.

The present was no longer Excellent Era's world. In this moment, applause filled the venue. With the results out, those who had been hoping for this result, hoping for Happy to win no longer needed to hide. They could express their support and respect openly.

As for Excellent Era's competition booths?

Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, Zhang Jiaxing, Shen Jian, Wang Ze, Qiu Fei.

Apart from Qiu Fei, they were all people with at least some renown in the pro circle, and some were even Gods. Yet in that moment, they were failures. This stage was no longer theirs and they didn't have the heart to watch their opponent's crowning. They silently left the stage on one side.

Excellent Era's bench was still in complete silence. No one went up to comfort their returning teammates. It was their boss, Tao Xuan, who charged up to Sun Xiang like a Dragon Breaks the Ranks.

"The match wasn't over, why did you leave?!" Tao Xuan roared at Sun Xiang.

"I couldn't win," Sun Xiang shook his head.

"How would you know that without trying? Even if you couldn't win, you could still tie by defeating one of them and bring us into overtime," Tao Xuan bellowed.

"I wouldn't be able to, because Glory was never meant to be played alone," Sun Xiang said.

"You…" Tao Xuan was stunned. This was what Ye Xiu had said to Sun Xiang on the field. Yet at this time, Sun Xiang had used it to retort against him.

Ye Xiu...

Gazing at the figure onstage, Ye Xiu was quite a ways away and Tao Xuan couldn't see his face clearly. However, as his once upon a time most dear friend, he should have been able to imagine this friend's smile without seeing it, but why was it that his mind was in such a mess? After so long of running this team, what had he gained? And what had he lost?

　

Glory… was never meant to be played alone?

This sentence seemed to be true not only for the battlefield!

Tao Xuan stared for a while and then sat back down dejectedly. He raised his head to look around and saw that all around him, there were people clapping for Happy. Tao Xuan knew there were quite a few Excellent Era fans here, but where had they gone now? How did they feel about this result?

Team Excellent Era...

Tao Xuan gazed at the stage. Excellent Era's team logo stood tall here at Excellent Era's bench. On a stage without a spotlight, it seemed dulled.

The award ceremony had long since been prepared for, the only thing that would need to be changed was who to give it to. The ceremony had already begun by then and the MC naturally had to go and interview Happy a little bit before bringing the trophy up.

"Happy's victory is, for most, an unexpected and shocking event. How do you feel about this?" The host threw the question at Happy's captain, who was also Excellent Era's ex-captain, Ye Xiu.

"Excellent Era was a formidable opponent, but Happy won the match. We are the champions. This is our glory." Ye Xiu said.

The opponent was strong, but we won the match.

This was more like a courtesy in a pro match, but here, no one would take it as just that. This was because Excellent Era truly was a powerful opponent, far stronger than Happy, but Happy still won.

That's right. It was just that simple.

That was what competition meant. That was what Glory meant.

You're stronger than us, but we won the match.

So, we are the champions.

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

Ye Xiu has officially returned to the scene with Team Happy!!! It's been a long journey, and now a new one is about to begin! So sit back tight, we've still got 700 chapters to go :^)

Chapter 1053: Reopening a Can of Worms

The entire stadium was filled with applause. This sort of finale made all those spectators who were hoping to witness a miracle feel that their journey was completely worthwhile. Applause, screaming, the host, having only just gotten the chance to ask one question, couldn't continue amongst this noise. He had to wait a full minute for the noise to die down. The host hurried to grasp this opportunity, throwing out a second question.

"Next is a question about you, personally. As the ex-captain of Excellent Era, winning this match, I think many people are curious as to what your feelings are right now."

This question was like a signal and the entire audience immediately fell silent. The MC's words weren't exaggerated at all; everyone was immensely curious about this topic.

"Nothing really. To me, victory is the most important," Ye Xiu said mildly.

"Then is there anything you want to say to Excellent Era?" The MC was obviously unsatisfied with Ye Xiu's answer. He wanted to hear something more juicy regarding the relationship between the two.

"Continue to work hard," Ye Xiu's answer was still as calm as ever.

The MC gave up on that train of thought and could only continue with the next question. "There's another thing everyone is curious about. In the past, you never revealed yourself to the public, but how come you've changed this habit with your return?"

　

"Heh, no reason in particular. I guess I was just going with the flow," Ye Xiu replied nonchalantly.

The three successive questions hadn't elicited any interesting information and the MCcouldn't accept this! He just really couldn't. He wasn't some randomly assigned newbie, he was a very professional Glory reporter and had interviewed countless pro players. He knew which Glory pro players were hard to deal with in media. However, after these three questions, the MC understood; friends in the media, don't think for a second that Ye Xiu accepting interviews is a boon. There's probably going to be another player placed on the list of impossible-to-interview players.

"Alright. Next, let's welcome the chairman of the Glory Alliance, Mister Feng Xianjun, to hand the trophy to Team Happy, as well as the certificate of qualification to the pro league!" Seeing that the award ceremony preparations had finished, the MC didn't continue the interview. Out of the four questions, three were directly at Ye Xiu personally and were topics that were popular prior to the match.

　

Feng Xianjun walked up the steps and onto the stage, smiling in a relaxed way and coming to shake the hands of every member of Happy and congratulate them.

In Happy's lineup, there were two that were familiar faces for Feng Xianjun.

"You can still play?" When shaking Sun Zheping's right hand, the chairman intentionally used more strength than necessary, smiling.

"Not much, but it's still enough." Even facing the chairman, Sun Zheping was still the same as ever.

Feng Xianjun smiled, nodding, and ended the conversation there, continuing down the line to shake hands. Wei Chen was a player from the first two generations and back then, Feng Xianjun wasn't the chairman yet, so they weren't really too familiar. They conversed normally before he finally arrived in front of Ye Xiu.

"I shouldn't have expected anything less from you," Feng Xianjun said, shaking Ye Xiu's hand.

"Heh," Ye Xiu chuckled, "You didn't write the wrong name on the certificate, did you?"

　

"You should be careful to not write the wrong name yourself," Feng Xianjun retorted, smiling.

　

The quiet conversation went unheard by anyone else. Outsiders only saw their peaceful smiling faces. Then Feng Xianjun turned and grasped the trophy, handing it to Ye Xiu.

Ye Xiu accepted it and raised it high as the crowd exploded into applause once more. The MC loudly announced the champions, but in truth, the value of the Challenger League wasn't in the trophy, but the beautifully printed certificate Feng Xianjun then handed over.

　

The qualification certificate to the pro league.

With this, it meant that Happy had the right to enter the pro league next season, and that was what everyone was truly fighting to take..

Champions of the Challenger League? That was never the final destination, but a starting point, one that started from this very certificate.

Ye Xiu accepted the certificate and saw Team Happy printed there. The certificate had been prepared long ago, but the team name was only printed after the final result had been revealed. Happy's other members had already clustered around and Feng Xianjun stepped to the side, letting them share their joy and leaving the celebrations to them. Tonight, they were the main characters.

　

As for those side characters who had failed, they wouldn't be completely ignored. Feng Xianjun then went over to Team Excellent Era and gave a few words of comfort and encouragement. As for the reporters, they were already looking at Excellent Era like tigers watching their prey. They had already prepared who knows how many questions, waiting to launch them at Excellent Era. They had already been told that this Challenger League match had a press conference afterwards. Never had this been arranged for the Challenger League before. It was clear how much importance the Alliance placed on this year's Challenger League match in comparison to the past. However, the reality was less grandiose: not enough popularity. However, this year, with the topic of Ye Xiu versus Excellent Era, they had arranged for time to gossip afterwards.

The first to appear at the press conference was Team Excellent Era. The manager Cui Li, as well as Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, and the other Excellent Era players all attended the press conference, sitting on the stage dumbly. No one initiated conversation. They were all silent.

There was complete silence and the reporters were looking at each other as well.

Losing the Challenger League was probably even worse than losing the championship match, especially for a powerhouse team like Excellent Era. The reporters felt sorry for them, but their professionalism wouldn't allow them take mercy on Excellent Era just because they were sorry for the loss. After sitting in mournful silence with Excellent Era for half a minute, some reporters probably felt that they had met a quota for their sympathy and raised their hands to ask questions.

The members of Excellent Era were still sitting there numbly. In the end, it was an Alliance news manager who began to choose reporters to ask questions from the side.

"During the match, Su Mucheng suddenly declared that she and Excellent Era were over and sat on Happy's side of the bench. Could you explain why this is? Is there any bad blood between Su Mucheng and Excellent Era?" Upon asking the first question, the reporters had chosen a difficult question for Excellent Era.

However, they were all people who had experience with worldly situations. Cui Li glanced at the reporter and said without emotion, "Su Mucheng is still a member of Team Excellent Era and Excellent Era will convene with the players before making decisions regarding their futures. Before then, there's nothing to say."

"Then may I ask how Excellent Era convened with Ye Xiu when he announced his retirement? From the match today, I doubt that anyone would believe that Ye Xiu is a player who should retire. He's in a surprisingly good state that doesn't lose to any of Excellent Era's players." The question that followed hit an even sorer spot for Excellent Era. This was a problem that Excellent Era's PR had wanted to disperse. Since Ye Xiu refused to accept interviews, it had made things convenient for Excellent Era. It was more or less whatever they said that goes.

Yet now this old can of worms had been reopened after the finale of the Challenger League. When Ye Xiu had originally announced his retirement, everyone wanted to know the reason. However, since he was a very private person, no one was able to gain first hand knowledge from the man himself. Excellent Era was their only source of information to gain this information from. Under this situation, it was easy for Excellent Era to guide the discussion. They had to first cover up the truth of Ye Xiu's retirement and then mix in the truth of Excellent Era's slipping performance. That Ye Xiu's skill was slipping had been a logical excuse. With Ye Xiu's habits, quietly retiring wasn't unexpected. The fans might be sorrowful, but they still accepted this truth.

They had thought it had all blown over. Who would've expected that Ye Xiu would build up another team from scratch after leaving Excellent Era and then fight them in the Challenger League?

This wasn't something Excellent Era had planned for. After creating a lie, they could only weave more lies around it to prevent it from falling apart. It was a good thing that Ye Xiu refused to appear in public, so Excellent Era held the reigns of the discussion.

Ye Xiu had never come out to say anything. Even after qualifying for the offline matches in the Challenger League and accepting some interviews, he had never expressed any form of concern towards these problems. Even so, upon seeing Ye Xiu accepting an interview for the first time, Excellent Era had panicked. They made preparations of all sorts of public backlash, but it was all for nothing. What they worried about was nothing to Ye Xiu.

Even now, Ye Xiu still didn't say anything.

　

However, he won the match.

Nothing was more convincing than this. You say Ye Xiu's skill has slipped? Then defeat him if you can! He had beat Excellent Era with a grassroots team. Never mind not being able to see any slips in his ability, even if his ability had slipped, no one would believe it after seeing such a conclusion.

Had Ye Xiu's state worsened to the point of needing to retire?

No one was more clear on this than Excellent Era.

The reason they wanted Ye Xiu to retire was precisely because they knew that Ye Xiu was still skilled, terrifyingly so. They wanted to give up on Ye Xiu, but were afraid that Ye Xiu would be a threat to them after becoming an opponent. They took more than they were given, and the situation had spiralled out of control.

Now, with this powerful reality as evidence, this question was like a knife's edge for them.

Even worse, Ye Xiu no longer refused the media and soon enough, he would be sitting in this exact same place, facing the same reporters, and possibly answering the same questions.

The days of being the only voice in the discussion had gone and would never be back.

When Excellent Era had wished Ye Xiu would walk onto the stage and get close to the media, promoting the team and himself, Ye Xiu had refused.

Now, when Excellent Era hoped that Ye Xiu could continue keeping his head down and refuse the reporters, he decided to stand up.

He hadn't said anything yet, but just the fact that he was willing to accept interviews caused Excellent Era to feel like they were sitting on pins and needles. Then, that last victory was an even stronger, clearer slap to the face.

"Manager Cui? Team Leader Cui?"

In his trance, Cui Li seemed to hear a voice calling out to him. He wanted to respond, but his body was no longer in his control.

"Doctor, is there a doctor here? Call an ambulance, someone's fainted!!" The press conference descended into chaos.

Chapter 1054: The Fate of a God

In the end, Cui Li was carried out on a stretcher, accompanied by an entourage of flashes. After the press conference had been disrupted, Excellent Era's press officer charged in, stopping the reporters that would like nothing more than to follow them all the way and take pictures.

"Sorry everyone, but with this incident, the interviews will end here today." The press officer said, ignoring the complaints of the reporters and herding the attending members of Excellent Era out.

The reporters loudly objected, but Excellent Era was steadfast in their decision, leaving a "we'll be holding another press conference in the near future, so you're welcome to come and ask whatever inquires you have then." In the blink of an eye, all of Excellent Era's people had left.

The reporters couldn't do anything about Excellent Era's steadfast decision, which ignored any way they could condemn them with their words. However, while they only had the chance to ask two questions, they managed to elicit very interesting responses. A question that could cause the answering side to faint? How much information was Excellent Era hiding in regards to the answer behind this question?

Though they might not get an answer today, the reporters wouldn't be discouraged. A monk might be able to run, but his monastery couldn't. It wasn't like such a large organization such as Excellent Era could disappear overnight. The reporters were all formulating their plans for the following interview.

Excellent Era might have escaped, but the press conference would continue. No matter how famous Excellent Era was, or how much there was to talk about, the champions were the true main characters of the night.

　

The reporters waited patiently. If they couldn't get their answers from Excellent Era, then they would get them from Happy. The central figure to all of these questions was a part of Team Happy, after all.

Yet after waiting for a long time, they were still left without their targets. That was when the press officer of the Alliance walked in with an awkward expression on his face. His originally impeccable suit was wrinkled all over.

"Sorry everyone, but the press conference today will have to end here." The press officer walked onstage and, seeing the anxious gazes below, announced with embarrassment.

"What?" All the reporters crashed to the ground.

"You've got to be fucking kidding me!" Someone hollered.

"What about Happy?"

　

"That's right, Happy's players haven't arrived yet!"

"Happy's people, they left…" The press officer also sounded depressed as he informed the others. After the award ceremony, all the employees had come to clean the place up. There was quite a lot of chaos. Pro players all knew what to do. For example, Team Excellent Era's players went to wait for the press conference backstage without prompting.

As for Happy? Well, they left.

Yup, they left. They didn't tell anyone, and no one noticed. This was because this was impossible to anyone with common sense. No one would be on guard for the team that had just finished a match.

Thus, Team Happy really did leave. It wasn't until the press conference was ready to start when the Alliance realized that only Excellent Era was present, while Happy was nowhere to be seen.

The employees looked for them everywhere with all their might, but they couldn't find anything. In the end, they asked around before finally getting word that a large group of people had left, yelling "we're the champions!"

Happy's player? Or Happy's fans?

They didn't know. All they knew was that Happy's people had left. They had stood up the press conference.

It was a good thing that Happy was going second, being the victors, so the Alliance still held a slither of hope. They hurried to find a way to contact Happy, rushing to get Happy back before Excellent Era's press conference ended.

Who would've thought that Excellent Era wouldn't be so cooperative either? It was only the second question and someone had already fainted.

The Alliance couldn't stop them from ending the press conference with this reason. However, on the other side, they hadn't even found Happy's contact info yet!

Chairman Feng Xianjun, having been informed of this, was stunned. No way? In the past, it was Ye Xiu who refused to attend these kinds of events, could it be that the entirety of Happy would refuse to attend these events now? That was too against the rules; that was most certainly not allowed to happen.

　

"We must find him and figure out what this is about!" That was the order the chairman gave.

They had found Happy's number and hurriedly called, but no one ever picked up. The Alliance was helpless in this situation and they couldn't have the reporters wait there forever, so the press officer had to go and announce that the press conference was over.

The press officer knew how awkward this situation was and was prepared to be surrounded and bombarded by the complaints of reporters, but Happy had left and they couldn't find them, so what could they do? The press officer could only face things with a strained smile.

The finals of the Challenger League, the press conference with all the juicy information that the reporters had been waiting for, yet it had been stopped with the fainting of a single person?

No one would accept that.

The media stands had all began to plan out their next steps. The media groups with idle soldiers stationed in H City all moved their troops out towards Happy Internet Cafe and Club Excellent Era. Do you really think you can escape us?

But the next day, Club Excellent Era suddenly announced that they would no longer be answering inquiries from the media. The reason, they explained, was because losing the Challenger League had brought their development to a grinding halt. Now, they had a lot of problems to deal with and didn't have the time or energy to deal with the media.

This reason seemed rather legit. Team Excellent Era had never thought they would lose the Challenger League. Their plans for the past year were all in regards to the Pro League and winning the championships. Now they had to stay in the Challenger League another year. The second coming of such a disaster was really more than they could deal with. Even disregarding that, Sun Xiang, Xiao Shiqin, these Gods, who had stayed with Excellent Era in the Challenger League for a year already, wouldn't accept having to go another year. Not just these Gods, but Zhang Jiaxing, Shen Jian, these pros, who could easily find a place in the Alliance, wouldn't be willing to continue to play in the Challenger League. There was also the rookie, Qiu Fei, who, according to the media of City B, was being sought out by Team Tiny Herb, who was looking for a chance to negotiate his transfer with Excellent Era.

This news came from a small, local paper and wasn't necessarily trustworthy, but it clearly showed that the Challenger League was a waste of even Qiu Fei's talent. Could Excellent Era keep these players?

There were, indeed, many troublesome things that Excellent Era had to deal with, but right now, the media wouldn't believe that they refused to respond to inquiries because they were busy.

　　

They were busy, but the reason they didn't want to face the media was because they had something to hide.

　

The more they had to hide, the more interested the media would be in digging up their secrets. Excellent Era might have closed themselves off to the media, but the media was omnipresent and would always find a way to attack from a different angle.

First of all, they found out from one of the receptionists at Happy Internet Cafe how exactly Ye Xiu came to their Internet cafe. Though they knew that Happy was only a road apart from Excellent Era, running to an Internet cafe after leaving Excellent Era really didn't suit the status of a God of the Alliance.

Yet they didn't think it really was just as things seemed.

　

Happy Internet Cafe's receptionist didn't hide anything, openly admitting that Ye Xiu had come to the Internet cafe and asked for a computer then, seeing the notice that they were looking for employees, applied for the position.

A God of Glory….. after announcing his retirement had come to an internet cafe for work?

Then, the reporters were given a tour of Happy Internet Cafe and the places God Ye Xiu had fought from. There was a small bed and a whole bunch of miscellaneous items in the small storage room; the reporters almost cried.

Was this the fate of the first generation God that built up Excellent Era's dynasty and made the title of Battle God resound throughout the entire Glory scene?

On the morrow, the media was full of pictures of this heartbreaking storage room. The big websites and internet celebs were also all reposting this, and some TV companies even wanted to come and film onsite.

The Glory scene was shocked!

The fans were shocked!

The reason for Ye Xiu's departure from Excellent Era was no longer of importance. Was this what the general, who had poured sweat and tears into taking the team to its pinnacle, got for all his hard work after retirement?

Working in an Internet cafe, living in a doghouse?

"How could they do this?!" One of the randomly interviewed Glory players exclaimed. "I can't imagine that a God like Ye Qiu would receive this sort of treatment after retirement. I can't imagine how Excellent Era must treat its players. Will there still be any pros willing to play for them after this? Oh, that's not right. What pro would be willing to go to a team in the Challenger League?!" This player really could trash talk, wiping a fistful of salt over Excellent Era's wounds.

"Ye Xiu, in this situation, after retirement? This can't be true, right? It isn't some sort of scam, is it?" There were also some who were doubtful.

"This is so hard to believe! What kind of club is Excellent Era? It doesn't matter what they've achieved. Letting the person who brought them to such heights fall into such destitution. All I can say to that is that they truly are heartless. This kind of team deserves to be relegated. Good work, Ye Xiu. I watched the finals of the Challenger League, spectacular, amazing, awesome, fuck!"

"I think this is suspicious. Think of what value God Ye Xiu has. All he did was retire, why is it like he's cutting all ties or something? This is suspicious, too suspicious."

The aforementioned interviews weren't conducted with Excellent Era supports. Apart from the few doubtful ones, the others all cursed openly, unafraid of the consequences.

As for Excellent Era fans? In the face of this truth, they were heartbroken, sorrowful, wanting to explain things for their team but not able to find an excuse.

"I think… It's not as simple as it seems. There must be something more to it." In the hearts of Excellent Era's fans, they still had hope for the better. They all wanted to believe that their God, and their team held love for one another.

"Fuck, this must be Ye Xiu's way of getting pity and intentionally trying to tarnish Excellent Era's name. Who the hell would believe that this is what happened to a God like that? Not me, at least." There were also those who still supported Excellent Era and ignored the truth, deriving things through their own logic.

"I don't know…" And then there were some fans who were like Team Excellent Era when faced with this question. They fell silent, unable to answer. No matter what, all that was left was hurt.

However, most Excellent Era fans couldn't stand this torment and held massive gatherings, protesting in front of Club Excellent Era daily and requesting the club to end their silent and give an explanation.

Chapter 1055: Excellent Era’s Silence

The Challenger League finals came to an end on Friday night. The following evening was the 37th round of the regular season of the season nine Glory Pro League, as well as the second to last round. A few teams had their rankings set in stone by then, but some were still fighting for a place in the playoffs or the right to stay in the Alliance.

Yet on such a crucial match day, there was a blanket of reports on the results of the Challenger League finals.

Happy had truly created a miracle.

The entire Glory circle was enthusiastically discussing this topic.

And on the following Sunday, the pitiful truth surrounding Ye Xiu's treatment after his retirement had elicited another wave of attention and discussion. All of Glory was discussing this gossip. The media fell right to Ye Xiu's side in this argument, all ganging up on Excellent Era together. Amongst the majority of Glory players, Excellent Era also took the brunt of shame and disdain.

The pro circle also placed heavy importance on this. Many media groups used mobile, QQ, and other methods to interview pro players on their opinions.

"This is a disgrace." Han Wenqing, the captain of Team Tyranny, who had already cemented their place as first in the regular season, stated in anger.

"Considering the position Ye Xiu has in the Glory circle, I believe all the pros are bitterly disappointed in Team Excellent Era for the situation that they left Ye Xiu in after his retirement," was Team Blue Rain's captain, Yu Wenzhou's opinion.

"Without a doubt, Ye Xiu has been treated unfairly." Team Tiny Herb's captain, Wang Jiexi, said.

　

"This isn't right," Team Samsara's captain, Zhou Zekai, expressed.

The pro players from the powerhouse teams almost seemed to have discussed this beforehand and condemned Excellent Era for their behavior solemnly.

Team Excellent Era was facing an unprecedented crisis of trust!

As the media group holding the most authority in the Glory circle, Esports Home liberally used up pages to report this shocking news on their Monday issue. On the other hand, the crucial 37th round of matches was only given a casual report of the results on the front page. The contents of the matches were several pages in. The news that took up the most eye catching placements were all on the Challenger League, Ye Xiu and Excellent Era.

　

Esports Home never exaggerated just to attract attention. Excellent Era, which had hurriedly gone silent and hid away from the public, was like a guilty coward in the eyes of the people. From the media to the normal players, pressure was being placed on them from all sides. However, Excellent Era was strangely stubborn with their public relations this time and didn't make any moves to soothe the situation. Club Excellent Era's doors were sealed and the players that gathered at their building never managed to catch a single member of Excellent Era. No one knew what Excellent Era was thinking.

Many people sensed something strange from Excellent Era's inaction.

The protests continued for two days and, Wednesday evening, a piece of news began to circulate online. Someone said they had seen a meeting between the higher-ups of Excellent Era and Samsara in City S.

　

What was Excellent Era planning?

This rumor without proof immediately had people's thoughts spiralling out of control. At such a time, Excellent Era interacting with other teams was a very strange sight. Was Excellent Era planning to give up on itself and throw a clearance sale?

The rumors spread rapidly. Immediately, reporters were sent to Club Samsara to divulge the truth from them. Team Samsara ended up being very open about it, openly admitting that they were in negotiations with Excellent Era about purchases, but they didn't leak anything about the contents of these negotiations.

　

Even after the June sixth Friday issue of Esports Home came out, Excellent Era still maintained their silence and ignored all the requests and demands from the fans.

June 7th was the last day of the regular season, but on this day, Excellent Era finally opened up to the media and what they had to say was a massive bombshell: Club Excellent Era was up for sale.

The boss of Excellent Era, Tao Xuan, told his spokesman to say that after being the head of Excellent Era for all this time, he felt bone-deep exhaustion; it was time for him to change his lifestyle. Thus, he had decided to sell Club Excellent Era and hoped that his successor could bring Excellent Era glory once more. As for him, personally? He would always be Excellent Era's most loyal fan.

It sounded nice, but everyone knew what this was about with a glance. Excellent Era could endure this crisis and didn't plan to try. Boss Tao Xuan was already preparing to abandon ship.

　

However, was it so easy to find someone to accept current Excellent Era?

Excellent Era, having not made any attempt to soothe public relations, only found themselves with more and more dirt being dug out. Now, Excellent Era's name had been completely tarnished and not even their glorious dynasty of the past could save them. Not only was their name dragged through the dirt, they didn't have the qualifications to the Pro League either. Disregarding this though, their hardware was still the cream of the crop in the Glory circle, and this made the selling of Excellent Era very complicated.

In simple terms, Excellent Era's hardware was as spectacular as ever, but its software was nothing but a mess.

Yet it was this software that truly represented the value of the two words "Excellent Era". Now that the software was destroyed, no one would want this anymore. As for the hardware, if anyone wanted it, they could seek out that they needed. With Excellent Era and Samsara already in negotiations, this was made very clear. Team Samsara wouldn't purchase Excellent Era. What were they interested in, seeking out Excellent Era for negotiations? Players? Characters?

After coming to such a realization, Excellent Era's fans panicked.

　

Putting Excellent Era up for sale. This was clearly a clearance sale preceding Excellent Era's disbandment! After this, could Excellent Era still stay alive?

　

For Excellent Era's fans, this wasn't something that they could ever accept. No matter if Excellent Era was good or bad, they had entrusted so much to Excellent Era. That was something that would never change. With what had happened, they were panicking. After all, no one would ever want to see their team in such a state. Some people might leave, but there would always be those that stayed, hoping that their team would stand once more, that they would be able to be at their team's side forever.

Yet now, Excellent Era was facing disbandment and might disappear forever. The team they had poured their hearts and souls into to support, the team they had cheered for for so long, would cease to exist like this?

No!!

Not long after the news came out, Club Excellent Era was surrounded by countless people. They were far more irrational than those who had been demanding an explanation front the team. With time running out, they weren't able to make many preparations. They could only yell again and again to express their feelings.

They didn't want the club to be sold. No matter what, they wanted to walk with their team until the end.

Chapter 1056: At Least They’re Still With Us

Everyone was all up in arms about Excellent Era, but where was the other star of this incident? They had yet to appear after the Challenger League.

Right now, it was the final stretch of the regular season many life and death matches were being fought. Yet, the place where the most Glory reporters had gathered was City H, which didn't even have any teams currently in the Pro League.

The reporters swarmed to take a look around the Happy Internet Cafe, and saw people protesting daily outside Club Excellent Era. But where was Ye Xiu? He was the reason that they came, but no one ever saw him. Ye Xiu didn't appear, nor did any other member of Team Happy. The people working at the Internet cafe didn't know either. It was only until they asked one of the employees to contact the boss, Chen Guo, that they found out that Team Happy was still in City B.

　

After the match, they had never come back.

After winning the Challenger League, Happy was drowning in delight and triumph. They had forgotten everything else. The post match press conference? What was that? Such a thought hadn't surfaced in their minds for even a second.

They had left the stadium directly and had been welcomed by a group of Guild Happy's tenth server members, led by Seven Fields. The massive group of people had gone to find a place to celebrate their victory; everyone was eager to toast God Ye Xiu. Amongst these fans was Sleeping Moon. Every time he thought of his and Lord Grim's first meeting in the tenth server, Sleeping Moon wanted to bury himself. His old friends like Seven Fields and Drifting Water still laughed at him even now: you're very brave, daring to challenge God Ye Xiu?

Sleeping Moon wanted to cry! That God was his idol. If only he had known earlier; it would have been more appropriate for him to go and lick his shoes.

After discovering Lord Grim's true identity, this had become a thorn in his heart. Today, Sleeping Moon wanted to use this chance to properly express himself and wash away the past. Holding his wine and lining up in the queue to toast, Sleeping Moon mentally prepared what he wanted to say. Yet, right after the first toast, someone began shouting, "What happened? What happened?"

　

Sleeping Moon rushed over and took a look at what was happening. Was the God drunk?

　

"What did you put in the drink?" No one believed the truth and mercilessly surrounded the young man who had toasted first. They immediately thought that he was a spy from Excellent Era. Did this bastard intend to poison their God?

"I didn't, I really didn't!" The young man was almost crying, trying to explain himself with the empty glass in hand.

"He… is a bit of a lightweight," Chen Guo explained, remembering Ye Xiu's younger brother, the real Ye Qiu.

He's a lightweight?

Everyone felt that boss Chen Guo's words really were modest. If he really had gotten drunk, then could you call this being a lightweight? This was a One-Hit KO!

The invincible God of Glory was instantly KO'ed by one cup of wine.

Without the star of the show, the party died down quite a bit. The players who came up to toast didn't know what to do.

That was when Sun Zheping came over, tossing the drunk Ye Xiu to one side and rolling up his sleeves, yelling, "Come on! I'll drink with you!"

The party instantly livened up. It was Chen Guo, seeing Sun Zheping about to drink without care, who said in doubt, "But, pro players don't drink, right?"

This was something that Ye Xiu had told her. If you drank too much too often, it would depress your nervous system causing your reaction speed to fall, your body to slow down and your hands to tremble. These were all taboos for pro players.

"That's right! Pro players should never drink." Hearing Chen Guo's words, Sun Zheping turned and smiled a bitter smile before raising his head and downing the cup of wine.

"Nice!!!" The players all cheered, clustering around Sun Zheping to compete.

　

Seeing this, Chen Guo felt melancholy in her heart. Pro players shouldn't drink, but Sun Zheping evidently no longer felt like he was a real pro player anymore. This celebratory event, for him, also held sorrow. He should have been able to do more. What little contributions he had made wasn't enough to satisfy him.

Mo Fan didn't get many chances to play and Luo Ji didn't even appear in the finals, but they had futures ahead of them. They had time and opportunity to compete, but Sun Zheping didn't. He could only end things here, heart yearning for more and victory adding to his disappointment. This was probably the reason he never returned even though he could still manage to play at a pro level with some strain. For him, this wasn't nearly enough!

"What happened, what happened?"

　　

Chen Guo was still over here feeling melancholy for Sun Zheping when a commotion broke out there. She went over to see and found that Sun Zheping had fallen, too.

　　

"How many glasses?" A player who was probably about to strike, holding a glass of wine, asked.

"Three?" A person with an empty glass said incredulously.

　

With Ye Xiu being OHKO'ed before, three glasses didn't seem all that shocking, but the problem was Sun Zheping's bring-it-on attitude from before. Everyone thought he was a great drinker who would take ages to get tipsy, but he fell at just three glasses?

Three glasses wasn't much better than one glass.

Chen Guo felt even worse now. Sun Zheping actually couldn't drink at all, could he? These gods, for their dreams, were always strict with themselves. How many years had it been since Sun Zheping had retired? He was evidently still holding himself to that rule of not touching alcohol, otherwise he wouldn't be down with just three glasses. Drinking ability was like mechanical skill; it could be trained, to some extent.

Yet Sun Zheping didn't. He persisted with the habits of pro players, protecting his own body. Did he hope to one day have the chance to return to the battlefield?

Chen Guo didn't think on it further, silently helping Sun Zheping to the side.

"Another so fast?"

On one corner of the sofa, Su Mucheng was eating sunflower seeds. The blackout drunk Ye Xiu was sleeping askew to one side. Soon enough, Sun Zheping was shoved over.

　　

Chen Guo sighed. When she was just a fan, all she saw was the spectacular performance these Gods had on the field. She would have never considered the amount of effort they had to put in off the field.

"What's wrong?" Su Mucheng would tell how Chen Guo didn't seem very happy. This was a night of their victory. What could wash away the joy of a championship?

Chen Guo glanced at the drunken two, but didn't really know how to explain.

"Don't worry." Su Mucheng seemed to understand upon seeing Chen Guo's gaze. "At least everyone is still with us."

At least everyone is still with us...

　　

Chen Guo didn't know how to react for a moment and glanced at the two again.

That's right. It didn't matter if it was Ye Xiu who had been kicked by his club, or Sun Zheping who could no longer reach his peak, what with the injury to his hand, or Wei Chen over there who had retired for longer than most people's pro careers yet was still doing his all to climb back to the top. Their lives hadn't been smooth, but no matter what, they didn't give up. They held hope in their hearts and charged forwards at every opportunity. No matter what, they were still here.

"These two useless things, my turn!" Over there, Wei Chen looked at the two drunk gods with disdain and rolled up his sleeves, preparing for battle.

The Guild Happy members muttered among themselves, not very enthusiastic about Wei Chen's upcoming performance.

"I bet four glasses and he blacks out."

"I bet five."

"I think I'll bet three."

"No one betting one glass?"

"If no one's betting one glass, I will!"

　

"Alright alright, confirm your bets…" They had even began a betting pool about Wei Chen.

It was doubtful that many would go home sober tonight. Chen Guo originally was going to be strict with herself, but then she drank a little out of courtesy every now and then and ended up tipsy.

Steamed Bun, Wu Chen, Luo Ji and An Wenyi were all swaying about. Even Mo Fan who barely interacted with anyone had managed to drink himself into being unable to walk straight.

　　

"A hundred glasses! I bet a hundred glasses!" Wei Chen hollered as he walked out with the others, all supporting each other. Wei Chen didn't lose face for pro players. He really could drink. If he really managed a hundred glasses, no one would know, but at the very least he could walk by himself with some help from the wall. It was just that after he left, he got on a taxi and asked to be sent back to Happy Internet Cafe. Under the taxi driver's confused gaze, he was dragged back out.

It was a good thing that the girls hadn't gotten so drunk. After sending off wave after wave of Guild Happy players, they got the drunk guys back to the hotel.

When she next woke, it was already noon. Opening her eyes, Chen Guo was immediately blinded by the sunlight.

She glanced around her room. There was no one there. Originally, this was her and Tang Rou's room, but she didn't know where everyone slept after last night.

We… really won the Challenger League?

Chen Guo stared at the ceiling, ignoring the blinding sunlight and suddenly felt a little lost. Drunken nights were always very blurred. With their victory of the championship, it all seemed like a fantasy.

Chen Guo quickly rolled to her feet and went to find her handbag.

　　

The handbag was right beside her pillow and Chen Guo opened it, quickly finding what she wanted.

The qualification certificate to the Pro Alliance.

　

Team Happy.

　

Yes! They really did it. All of this was real. In that moment, Chen Guo felt like she was surrounded with bliss. Last night was full of passion, excitement, energy. Only after giving it a night to sink in did the satisfaction and bliss of getting the championship really flood in.

"Where are the others?" Chen Guo hurriedly got up and charged out of her room.

　

The others were getting up as well, though the others who had been dead drunk weren't nearly as lively as Chen Guo, who had only been tipsy.

"You all alright?" Chen Guo greeted everyone before seeing Ye Xiu still asleep on the bed.

"He's really too weak!" Chen Guo recalled the scene from last night. "I know he's a lightweight, but getting blackout drunk with just a cup just seems unreal!"

"It's not just from drinking," Wei Chen said, "He's exhausted. Let him rest a few days!"

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

We're #1 just like Happy!! The 17 chapter week starts today plus a bonus vid translated by me and veriquity! The MAD is called Along this Journey and is centered around Ye Xiu. We've translated it so that the lyrics are singable too :)

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dl_-6qUNnCA

Chapter 1057: End of the Regular Season

Ye Xiu slept for an entire day. The rest of the team felt sluggish for a day after all the drinking and celebrating. Chen Guo spent her time on the web, surfing through all the reports of Happy's victory in the Challenger League and bursting with joy. Yet, on this day, they also received a phone call from the Alliance. Happy was solemnly admonished for their conduct during the press conference after the competition.

"We forgot! We were so happy that we completely forgot." Chen Guo gave this explanation.

The Alliance immediately communicated that they would not be launching an investigation. However, as one of the new teams entering the Alliance next season, there would be another press conference that they would have to attend. Obviously, Chen Guo had no way of refusing this request. After asking for a date, she found that they still had a week. This press conference for new teams would only take place after the season had ended. They at least had to figure out which teams each of the two new entries would be replacing first!

That day was also the second to last round of the season. Because Heavenly Swords would be preparing for the competition, they only congratulated Happy on their championship over the phone the day before. They obviously didn't have the chance to gather together. This Saturday, Luo Guanning sent over a stack of tickets, inviting everyone in Happy to watch the match.

After that night's match was finished, the two groups pooled together, once again enthusiastically celebrating.

This was partly because Heavenly Swords wanted to make up for the lack of in-person blessings during the previous evening. At the same time, after this round, they also had a reason to celebrate themselves. They had maintained their spot in the Alliance!

Maintaining a spot in the Alliance.

This was Heavenly Swords' goal after realizing their own strength. This was definitely below the expectations that the media often painted for them. All of Heavenly Swords' publicity after their announcement of joining the Alliance had shown off their financial resources, leading many to expect them to be a dark horse. The pre-season forecasts even dared to place them in the number ten spot.

All of this failed to sway Heavenly Swords from their intended path. Every step that they took was sure and steady. In this way, the early stages were unusually tough. The professional league was indeed not as simple as they had once thought.

Luckily, this season, Glory had released an expansion, winning them an opportunity. This kind of change was very good news for low to mid-tier teams. The widespread emergence of Level 75 Orange equipment allowed them to somewhat shrink the character strength gap between them and more powerful teams in a short amount of time. Yet in addition to this, Heavenly Swords was also an in-game ally of Happy. This allowed them to focus their energy on competitions. It could be said that, while many pro players rushed into the game, they were freed from such a burden by Happy's presence.

　

All of this was left unsaid between the two sides, but within their hearts each knew this clearly.

Now, the second to last match of the season was complete. Team Heavenly Swords ultimately locked in 14th place. The outcome of the last match of the season wouldn't affect their ranking. Although this contradicted the pre-season media expectations for the team, Heavenly Swords had completely achieved the goal they had set for themselves. They were especially aware of the fact that had it not been for the expansion, had it not been for the fact that they could continue to concentrate their energy on the matches during that time period, they would be in a precarious place right now. Before this, Heavenly Swords' placement had been just around the relegation zone, their situation an imminent danger.

"To Happy's victory! To Heavenly Swords' continued spot in the Alliance! Let's toast!" Luo Guanning took the lead to cheer. However, Happy had been completely intoxicated the day before, so today they really needed to demonstrate some control. As for Heavenly Swords, they had all been pro players for a year now, so they would also control themselves when celebrating.

　

"Next season, we'll be opponents." Luo Guanning said with infinite sorrow. Interacting with Happy, especially interacting with the God Ye Xiu, had really brought a considerable amount of profit for their Heavenly Swords. If he had a choice, Luo Guanning obviously wouldn't want to give up this kind of friendship and become opponents.

"I hope that in the future, we won't run into a kill-or-be-killed situation against you." Luo Guanning raised his glass towards the ladies and gentleman of Happy. "However, even if this happens, no matter the outcome, I swear our friendship off stage will not change.

"Hahaha, you're thinking too much Little Luo." Ye Xiu laughed, "I'm afraid our two teams have completely different goals. That type of kill-or-be-killed situation shouldn't arise."

"Oh? What's Happy's goal for the next season?" Luo Guanning asked curiously.

　

"Champions."

"Pffff..." Even with all of his etiquette training, and despite his usual unshakable elegance and composure, Luo Guanning spit out the sip of wine he had just taken. He hurriedly apologized to the person he had spit on.

　

Just a while ago, when the five of them had gathered together to create a team, their goal had also been to directly aim for the championships. They had been prepared to take the Alliance by storm. After they met the God, he had helped them realize how unrealistic their goal was. For a team that had been constantly pulling small heists within the game, saying that they were directing aiming to become champions was really too disrespectful to the Alliance!

But God, you, you can't have this kind of double standard!

You called us unrealistic and impractical, yet your team, which has just joined the Alliance, is already shouting about becoming the champions? Isn't that too unconvincing?

Even though you have the strength of a God, what about the other characters and players on your team? Glory isn't meant to be played alone... wasn't this what you said at the end of the competition yesterday?

Luo Guanning couldn't accept this, yet this also wasn't something he could easily say out loud. However, whether or not he said this out loud didn't even matter. The mouthful of wine that he had spit out had already made his thoughts very clear!

"Hahaha." Ye Xiu nevertheless laughed at his appearance, not giving an explanation for his words. He simply raised his glass, also giving a toast: "Everyone come!"

Tonight's celebration was subdued, yet when all was said and done it couldn't really count as any kind of real rest. After today, Chen Guo didn't even call everyone back to City H, instead looking for a resort within City B. She directly dragged the entire team over for some real rest and recuperation.

The place that Luo Guanning introduced was truly a location on the level of The Peach Spring beyond this world.** It was only through his name and connections that Happy's people got the chance to enjoy it. This place was truly detached from the outside world and devoid of distractions. However, going online every day and seeing everyone's reactions to their victory was still Chen Guo's greatest joy.

The praises showered upon Happy and the questions aimed at Excellent Era all made Chen Guo sigh with contentment. She felt especially vindicated seeing that reporters had visited the Happy Internet Cafe, and had been given a tour of Ye Xiu's previous dwelling in the storage room. Their violent denouncements were simultaneously laughable and sad.

Finally, we've won!

Seeing all the different news reports and remembering everything that had happened over the past year, Chen Guo felt very moved. Although she was this team's boss, in reality she really hadn't done much. All of the most demanding burdens were pretty much being shouldered by Ye Xiu alone. In a year and a half, starting from a brand new server and a new account, leveling up, finding people, fighting for materials, upgrading equipment, training the other players ...

Ye Xiu had truly done so much, yet Chen Guo, who was always by his side, had only become aware of it now.

They relaxed in the resort for a week. Meanwhile, the Pro Alliance had reached its final stages. Excellent Era also dropped a bomb: they had entered the scrap market and were ready to sell.

During this week, Chen Guo had also been contacted many times by people who wanted to meet and interview Ye Xiu. She rejected all of these requests. Although she had long wanted Ye Xiu to step out and and give a serious response about the true nature of his retirement, at this time, she just wanted Ye Xiu to get some good rest because she had discovered that this was truly the most important thing to Ye Xiu. He needed to recover his health and adjust his mental state. Only like this could he continue persevering on the Glory stage.

To Ye Xiu, this year and a half wasn't as simple as merely missing the pro stage. When all was said and done, how much did this year and a half of demanding labor shorten the career span of this already aging pro player?

A week of recuperation might not be able to save much. Yet, Chen Guo did not wish to see Ye Xiu spending more time and energy doing other things during this period of time.

He's truly too tired. He needs to rest properly.

Wei Chen words rang true. Chen Guo could only do her best to create for him a good resting environment. This at least was something she could work hard to achieve.

On Saturday night, amidst the dispute and clamor that Team Excellent Era was facing, the regular season of Season 9 of the Glory Pro League officially came to an end.

Team Tyranny did not fail to meet expectations, placing first in the regular season. However, they failed to break Excellent Era's old record score. After all, now was a shining era filled with stars. With the immense improvement in technology, Excellent Era's overwhelming strength from those days was becoming increasingly difficult to duplicate.

Tyranny and Excellent Era, a pair of mortal enemies from the past.

However, Tyranny was the team at the top. Even as people felt sorrowful that such a record could not be surpassed, they also thought about how the record-holding and archenemy team Excellent Era was currently crumbling to pieces on the side. In the interview with Team Tyranny's captain Han Wenqing after the season ended, the question of the captain's opinion on Excellent Era's situation was posed. Han Wenqing did not take joy in his opponents' suffering, yet he mercilessly replied with one sentence: they reaped what they sowed.

After Tyranny, the previous championship team Samsara stood in second place. Their ace player Zhou Zekai was the same as ever, gorgeous and powerful. Although they were nominally second place, compared to the previous season, Samsara was surprisingly even stronger than before. It could only be said that this season, Team Tyranny was more steady and efficient.

　

In third place was Team Wind Howl. Under the lead of their new ace Tang Hao, Wind Howl displayed their strength from the start. Their goal was no longer simply making playoffs; instead, they were aiming for the championships. However, in the end, they still failed to surpass the two teams ahead, although they did manage to beat Tiny Herb and Blue Rain by a full head.

Tiny Herb and Blue Rain stood in fourth and fifth place. The greatest excitement that this pair of old powerhouses brought were their two young rookies. The prodigy Gao Yingjie had officially become a part of the main force of Tiny Herb this season, with many eye-catching performances. On Blue Rain's ride, the 14 year old Lu Hanwen was even more extraordinary, directly filling the gap left by All-Star Yu Feng after his transfer. He truly embodied the saying, the newborn calf isn't afraid of the tiger, radiating all kinds of passion and enthusiasm on stage. Even though he still had many flaws in his playstyle, outside of him there really wasn't a choice for this season's Best Rookie. Gao Yingjie very much regretted that he was already a second year player, and thus no longer qualified for the title of Best Rookie.

After these five teams, Misty Rain, Void, and Hundred Blossoms occupied sixth through eighth place

Translator's Thoughts

Nomyummi Nomyummi

**TL Note: The Peach Spring beyond this world (世外桃源) means a hidden utopia of peace and prosperity. The chengyu is a reference to The Peach Blossom Spring (桃花源记), a fable about an isolated paradise village that a fisherman accidentally discovered whilst sailing down a river. -------------------------------------------------------The UI for Translator's Thoughts seriously sucks. I can't format stuff (put in tabs and new lines) or paste images/videos. If the spirit stones to unlock a chapter didn't depend on word length, I would put my TL notes in the chapter. As a workaround for now, I'll post stuff on Patreon since I won't be limited to length that way. So for more information on The Peach Blossom Spring, check out: https://www.patreon.com/posts/18349699/

Chapter 1058: New Team Press Conference

Overall, the situation in the Alliance hadn't seen much change. Although Wild Howl had surged up the ranks, the other powerhouses hadn't fallen either. Instead, it was Thunderclap and 301 Degrees that hadn't managed to make it into the playoffs after losing Xiao Shiqin and Xu Bin. Team Hundred Blossoms hadn't been off to a good start, unstable for the first half of the season, but after the update, their performance surged. From the team to the fans, they all exhibited a peak in fighting spirit and performed better and better, eventually catching the last bus to the playoffs.

With the rankings set in stone for the regular season, the schedule for the playoffs was released. The most intense clash of the first round was the fourth ranked Blue Rain and fifth ranked Tiny Herb. As these two teams were both champion level powerhouses, this clash would doubtlessly be tacked with the tag "pre-finals" or something along those lines. In addition, with the disharmony between the two teams, and the fact that both teams had very amazing rookies, this match was abundant with discussion and content.

However, if you were talking about hot topics, then the hottest one would definitely be the clash between the first ranked Tyranny and eighth ranked Hundred Blossoms in the first round.

Zhang Jiale's arrival at Tyranny upon his return was still being debated about even now. Now, with Zhang Jiale allied to Tyranny and facing the team he had once led, Team Hundred Blossoms, no drama-lover would miss the war that was set to rage.

The other two battles were Samsara versus Void and Wind Howl versus Misty Rain. Compared to the other two, these matches weren't as hot of a topic, but this was only a comparison. There was no weak team in the playoffs.

　

However, there were always tears that had to accompany laughter.

These eight teams managed to charge into the playoffs, but there were also two teams that had to leave the Alliance. Yet for these weak, relegated teams, not much attention would be given to them except among their fans. Instead, it was the teams that were going to replace them that were hot topics.

　

Team Myth!

After being approved by the Alliance, a whole new team was born. They debuted in the Alliance-held press conference on the first day of the new week and enthusiastically expressed their determination and will. In the past, new teams like this would elicit a lot of attention and curiosity, but today, the reporters all hoped that this new team called Myth would finish their rambling and get lost. The team everyone was waiting for was the next team, the team with God Ye Xiu, the team that had miraculously crushed Excellent Era and charged into the Alliance, Happy.

Under this background, the Q&A session after Team Myth had finished their speech was filled with nothing but very cooperative silence from the reporters. In the end, a few veteran reporters asked a few cliche questions out of courtesy. Team Myth ended up leaving, dispirited, with the Alliance press officer's repeated "are there anymore questions?"

Yet the moment Myth left, the still and low-spirited reporters suddenly jumped up with enthusiasm. Those who were practically drooling as they napped seemed to shine with the glow of being recharged.

"It should be Happy now, right? Where are they?"

Team Myth hadn't even completely left and they saw the response of the reporters, wanting to cry.

"Ahem… Next, let's welcome Team Happy…" The Alliance press officer continued to act as a host.

"They're coming, they're coming!!" It didn't need to be mentioned how excited the reporters wer. As soon as Happy's people appeared, flashes enveloped the room. People were taking photos nonstop until Happy sat in their seats, especially for Ye Xiu. Fuck, they hadn't manage to take photos of him for so long; today they were gonna take their fill.

Ye Xiu was so blinded by the flashes that he couldn't even open his eyes. Even the Alliance press officer couldn't watch this go on and hurriedly cleared his throat and announced that the press conference was beginning.

This press conference was an exhibition of the new teams, so all the members would be attending. However, they had to stay within the rules. For example, Su Mucheng couldn't sit onstage at this time. As for Sun Zheping, he had already bid them farewell and left for Heavenly Swords to prepare for the next season and didn't attend either. As for Wu Chen, Ye Xiu and Chen Guo had asked for his opinion and he had expressed that he was satisfied with being able to take part in such a spectacular match. He didn't have any further hopes for the pro league and wished to focus on the guild completely.

Do you really have no more hopes?

Ye Xiu and Chen Guo didn't ask that because they knew the answer.

Wu Chen definitely still hoped he could take part, but he knew what the reality of it was. He wasn't young anymore and not very skilled either. An occasional striking performance meant little. What was more important was that he knew that Su Mucheng would be joining Happy in the next season. Go and fight over this place with the Number One Launcher of the Alliance? Here, Wu Chen let go of it all. He was a player with limited talent. Being able to perform and help out in this high-level and crucial match, helping his team enter the Alliance, that was his peak already. Aiming even higher was too unrealistic for him.

Wu Chen left the team, but still attended the press conference as Team Happy's guild leader. The Guild Department had always been a very important part of the team and acted as the right and left hands to the team with the R&D Department. Guild leader? A guild leader of any normal guild was nothing impressive, but a guild leader of a club was a very important position.

Team Happy was onstage and the press conference began. First, was the introduction for the team members. Then, the boss of the team, Chen Guo, who was truly the first in the team, had to say a few words. Since the Alliance had informed them beforehand, they naturally had a speech prepared. However, while Chen Guo might be open and extroverted usually, she was still rather nervous in a situation like this. Yet, reminding herself that she was the boss of the team that defeated Excellent Era, Chen Guo steeled herself.

Then, the captain would have to say a few words.

Ye Xiu, after all these years, finally appeared in an event like this. The flashes immediately started up again.

Boss Chen Guo represented the club as a whole. Even though this club of theirs didn't have all those individual departments, they were one in name. As for the captain, he represented the team.

Everyone was eagerly anticipating Ye Xiu's speech! However, as they listened, the reporters with good memories began to scratch their heads.

"No way, how come this speech sounds so familiar?"

"Really?"

"Yeah, I've definitely heard it somewhere. I know it."

"Pick a few keywords and search it up?"

"Yeah, that line just now was too familiar. I'll search it up."

Soon enough, the answer was out. The reporters wanted to cry. Fuck, wasn't this the speech the captain of Team Heavenly Swords had used last year when they entered the Alliance? It's so rare for you to attend a press conference like this; would it kill you to take it a little more seriously?

Chapter 1059: What is Excellent Era

Heavenly Swords and Happy were in completely different situations.

Yet, just like that, Ye Xiu calmly used the other captain's speech, not even making an effort to modify it. Upon finding out, the reporters felt like plastic bags blowing in the wind.

The only saving grace was… this kind of promotional speech was all empty talk, so there usually wouldn't be anything interesting to write about. After listening to this speech while clutching at their hearts, it finally came to the Q&A session that they were most eager for.

　

"Hm, next we have our question and answer session." The Alliance press officer had only just announced this when a sea of hands rose. Thankfully, Team Myth had already left, otherwise they would cry for sure, seeing the difference in their treatment.

Having too many hands raised was troublesome as well. Pointing at a person would cause a group to stand. Then it had to be specified whose question was being answered from that group.

The first chosen one stood under the envious and jealous gazes of the other reporters.

"Hello, I'm a reporter from City B.B City. First of all, congratulations to Happy on winning the Finals of the Challenger League and gaining the qualifications to entering the Pro Alliance." The reporter directed this congratulations to the entire team, but his gaze was fixated on Ye Xiu. Ye Xiu had no choice but to respond for the entire team. "Thanks."

"I don't mean to disrespect Happy, but Happy truly achieved a miraculous victory. However, what I'm more shocked about isn't the result, but the process. In the team competitionTeam Competition, Happy had the initiative the entire way. Compared to simply victory, this is a far more impressive accomplishment. I'm curious as to how Happy managed that." The reporter said.

"This isn't something to be shocked about," Ye Xiu said with a smile, "Opportunity always smiles on those who are prepared."

"Prepared?" The reporter was stunned for a moment, "From what I know of, Excellent Era wasn't negligent with their preparations for this match. From the beginning of the offline matches, they had done specialized research into how to face this final match. In the last week, they even closed themselves off for special training. I believe Excellent Era was very well prepared."

"Unfortunately for them, we were more prepared," Ye Xiu said.

　　

The reporters were going crazy. Was it fun to give us all these vague statements? This was just wasting time!

"Why are you so certain?" The reporter hurriedly asked.

"Because we prepared for this match for a full year." Ye Xiu replied.

Everyone was struck dumb.

One side had started preparing since the offline matches, which could be considered at most a month of preparations, while the other had prepared for a whole year.

This was true!

All the reporters immediately realized this. This was because a year ago was when Excellent Era had been relegated. Even if you used your knee to think, you'd know that this would be an unprecedented boss in the Challenger League, the ultimate final boss. No matter who it was, if they wanted to conquer the Challenger League, they would have to get through this step. They completely trusted that Happy had started researching Excellent Era from that time forth.

A year of research and this research was directed towards Excellent Era that Ye Xiu was extremely familiar with in the first place...

As for Excellent Era? Even though they had known since the start that Happy had Ye Xiu, would they put everything into studying an opponent like Happy? The one they had been on guard against this entire time was just Ye Xiu, no? Yet in that team competitionTeam competition, every single member of Happy had shown their worth. They might not have been the MVPs, but in that match, everyone managed to display their strengths to the fullest.

　

Was this because Happy's players were in a better state?

Now everyone knew that it wasn't the case. This was the result of ample preparations! For this match, who knew how much specialized training Happy had gone through?

A full year of preparations sent everyone into speechlessness for a while. It wasn't until the Alliance press officer called out that the reporters came to again.

The second chosen reporter stood up, but his question was no longer about that match. That match had been a whole week ago. Focusing on it now would be a waste of pages, and there were more interesting things to report now anyways.

"I want to direct this question to Captain Ye Xiu. As Excellent Era's ex-captain, I trust you've heard of the recent news that Excellent Era is being sold. What thoughts do you have on this?"

"I believe that Excellent Era won't fall just because of this. Excellent Era has a shining future ahead of them," Ye Xiu said.

"But from the current situation, Excellent Era is likely to be disbanded and cleared out in a sale. The name Excellent Era might cease to exist," the reporter retorted.

Ye Xiu smiled and said, "With so many people who care for and love Excellent Era out there, do you really think that the name Excellent Era would cease to exist? I believe that a successor to Excellent Era will appear. Excellent Era won't crumble because of one man's decision. This is because Excellent Era isn't an asset to be sold, but a mindset, even a culture. It exists within the hearts of everyone who cares about and loves Excellent Era. They are the true people of Excellent Era. This is something that no one can sell. So long as they exist, Excellent Era will never fall."

"Brilliant!" Someone suddenly yelled loudly. The reporters all turned their heads and saw that one of their fellows had been unable to keep to himself any longer. Those who knew this person knew that he was a deeply loyal fan of Excellent Era's. This speech that sounded simply like pretty but empty words to most managed to move this real Excellent Era fan.

This was because only real Excellent Era fans would know what sort of panic and anxiety that the news coming from Excellent Era during this time had brought them. Now, Ye Xiu's words had awakened him.

"Excellent Era will never fall!" This person said with force, seeming to have come to some sort of decision.

"Yes." Onstage, Ye Xiu nodded his head firmly in response.

The ex-captain of Excellent Era had taken a new responsibility now, and when faced with Excellent Era, he hadn't shown any mercy. Excellent Era's current situation could even be seen as his personal handiwork. However, he was a true person of Excellent Era. He knew better than anyone what Excellent Era was.

Excellent Era wasn't a good or service to be sold, and not something that the owner could destroy with a single decision to sell. So long as Excellent Era's spirit lived on, it would continue to endure. If worse came to worst, they could always copy Happy and create an Internet cafe, rising back up as grassroots. They might not have Excellent Era's ace accounts or ace players, but they had Excellent Era's spirit. So long as they had that, they were Excellent Era.

"Thank you!" This reporter had forgotten his job already and stood, bowing deeply to Ye Xiu who was on stage. Those who knew him well knew that this loyal Excellent Era fan had published many articles condemning and doubting Ye Xiu upon the release of the news of Ye Xiu being at Happy. But now, he had managed to gain an understand of what Excellent Era truly was from this old captain. He felt that he had to give him this show of gratitude.

"You're welcome. Good luck." In that moment, Ye Xiu didn't seem to see a reporter either, but a brother that had once fought by his side.

An unfathomable atmosphere had blanketed the press conference and, in that moment, no one was able to come up with a question.

"Ahem, is there any reporter that still has a question to ask?" The Alliance press officer asked.

Question? Of course they did. The questions that had been begging to be asked had been held back for this occasion. But now after gaining an understanding of Ye Xiu's inner thoughts, they suddenly found that these questions had all been answered in that instant. Everything that had happened between Ye Xiu and Excellent Era in the past had no gossip value any longer. They had already clearly felt Ye Xiu's true feelings.

Chapter 1060: Can’t Understand

The question about Excellent Era caused the atmosphere to die down a little. It was only when the press officer asked for the third time if there were any more questions that a reporter finally stood.

"Hello, Captain Ye Xiu. Your words just now filled us with confidence for Excellent Era's future. However, I still want to hear your personal thoughts on Excellent Era being put up for sale. Thank you."

It was only until this person finished speaking that the reporters realized something.

Wasn't this the same question as before? However, Ye Xiu's response wasn't exactly answering the question. His answer was one that didn't answer the question directly, but followed from it. He had switched topics and left everyone in deep contemplation about it. It was good that there were people who managed to stay clear headed. With this reporter's emphasis and repetition of the question, the other reporters realized that this God, who had never really interacted with the media, would be very hard to deal with.

"Uh…..." Ye Xiu's expression wasn't so calm as it was before, "To be honest, it pains me and at the same time, I feel very disappointed."

Hearing this, the eyes of the reporters lit up.

"By pained and disappointed, are you referring to the decision to sell Excellent Era?"

"Yes," Ye Xiu nodded, "Excellent Era is at its most desperate times and, deciding to put Excellent Era up for sale at a time like this, I think, this is a complete betrayal and abandonment of what they once fought for. In this decision, Excellent Era has become nothing more than a commodity."

Ye Xiu didn't mention a specific name in his speech, but who else could make the decision to sell Excellent Era? Only the boss, Tao Xuan.

However, the reporters wouldn't lose out from making this all clearer. Immediately, someone asked, "So the one that caused you this pain and disappointment is actually the boss of Excellent Era, Tao Xuan, right?"

　

"Yes." Ye Xiu nodded. "If it was for the continued and better growth and development of the team, no matter in what shape or form, I could try to understand. Since everyone looks at problems differently, they would naturally come up with differing solutions. However, excuse me if I cannot bring myself to understand the decision to sell the team.

"But you just said that, no matter what, Excellent Era wouldn't fall."

"Yes, Excellent Era will never fall, but some people already have." Ye Xiu replied.

This time, no reporter stood to ask for clarification on who this person was. After these questions, everyone had more insight to what Ye Xiu meant. Excellent Era did belong to Tao Xuan, but this was only from a business standpoint. From an esports standpoint, Excellent Era was a team that existed in the hearts of all its fans. Even though Excellent Era belonged to Tao Xuan in name, he could only have the commodity. When he put Excellent Era up for sale, he had completely left the true Excellent Era that existed in the hearts of the people.

This time, the reporters truly understood. Some people were thinking to themselves quietly. Others had already opened up their laptops and started typing, and those who were more used to pen and paper started jotting stuff down.

With something to write about, the reporters seemed to be afraid to forget something, already beginning to draft their articles and forgetting their current situation.

The Alliance's press officer had attended countless interviews and press conferences, but this was the first time he had seen reporters forget where they were and start drafting up their articles. He was stunned for a long while before managing to react. "Ahem, are there anymore questions?"

His question managed to bring these reporters back to reality. Everyone snapped out of it, feeling unsettled by their actions just now. It was almost like they had been bewitched. They all hurriedly composed their thoughts. It wasn't until the press officer asked again that some people finally sat straight, focusing on Ye Xiu who was on stage.

Everyone was already very satisfied with what they had managed to elicit from this press conference. However, the one onstage right now was Ye Xiu. After all these years, this was his first time ever attending a press conference. They couldn't just let him go like that. After so many years, there were too many questions they had for Ye Xiu about all sorts of matters. They had to make the most of today. Even if they couldn't think of any big questions, using some small meaningless questions to drag things out was good, too.

Thinking of this, there were immediately some reporters who raised their hands. The one who was picked probably had yet to think of a good question to drag things out and made a few noncommittal sounds before gathering his thoughts and asking, "May I know why Team Happy didn't attend the press conference after the Challenger League?"

The reporters all stared at him.

This question was one that the reporters who had been stood up were desperate to know, but these reporters weren't so docile and well-behaved to wait until today to ask. They had already pried for an answer from the Alliance after the press conference came to an end with Happy's lack of attendance.

The Alliance made up a reason for why Happy didn't attend the press conference that day, so it was no longer a problem anymore. Now this person was asking again; this was rather tactless! The press officer that had given them the reason before was right there. Hearing this, he might think they had no more questions and end the press conference. That couldn't be allowed to happen!

It was a good thing that while the problem was resolved for the Alliance and media, it wasn't unexpected for Happy. This time, it wasn't Ye Xiu who answered, but Chen Guo.

"First of all, I'd like to apologize to everyone who came to the press conference that day." Chen Guo imitated a professional, official tone. "As everyone knows, Happy is a very ordinary grassroots team. We've never attended a pro match before and don't have any experience with this. That day, though we received the call about the press conference, we were delighted upon winning the championship and forgot. I really am sorry."

This explanation was more or less the same as the excuse the Alliance had given, but the reporter, looking at the stage, suddenly felt that something wasn't right. He gazed at Ye Xiu who was on the far right. "But, God Ye Xiu…" The reporter had only gotten there before his words got stuck. Ye Xiu, on the other hand, smiled and responded, "What about me?"

"No… nothing…" The reporter was about to say that God Ye Xiu had a lot of experience with pro matches, but then he remembered that while Ye Xiu had much experience with the matches, had he ever attended a press conference? Never! With the other's meaningful smile, the reporter decided to not bring it up.

With that problem settled, another reporter was called to speak. "May we have some information on what plans Happy has for the next season? For example, is Happy planning anything in the summer transfer window?"

"We've already settled a transfer," Chen Guo replied, tone serious.

"Can you give us some specifics?"

"Su Mucheng has confirmed that she will transfer for free to Team Happy next season," Chen Guo said.

This was something the reporters had guessed already with their sharp senses. However, an official announcement was still far more meaningful. With this, Team Happy wouldn't be just held up by Ye Xiu. Would the best partners in the Alliance resurface in Happy?

"Could we have some details on the contract Su Mucheng will be signing with Happy?" Since the transfer of pro players was a hot topic, reporters were interested in the contents of contracts, too. Logic said that an All-Star player like Su Mucheng wasn't someone an internet cafe team like Happy could keep. However, there was already an even bigger god residing there, so people couldn't judge Happy through this usual logic.

"Uhh we're still discussing some details, so we can't leak anything yet." Chen Guo's response was rather well formulated, but the awkwardness in her expression that had appeared in that split second didn't go unnoticed by the reporters. Pay and treatment was something Chen Guo worried about. They had managed to get through the Challenger League, but now it was the Pro League. Everyone was a pro player now. She couldn't have them play pro matches with just board and food in repayment. What sort of contract should she give to them? The very thought gave Chen Guo a headache. She had too little experience because no grassroots team had ever managed to slaughter their way to the Pro League before.

The thousand something RMB in being an Internet cafe employee? That definitely wasn't appropriate! But, going by pro player standards? Chen Guo had gleaned some understanding of it. Currently, the income for pro players was very high. For example, Team Tyranny's captain Han Wenqing had earned thirty million in three years. That meant ten million per year and two hundred thousand per week. In Chen Guo's eyes, Ye Xiu was an existence beyond even Han Wenqing, but, let alone something higher, just Han Wenqing's income would cause Chen Guo to cry to death.

However, Han Wenqing's contract ended this year. He'd have no problem renewing it, but his pay might decrease by a lot. After all, he was a veteran past his peak. His current record of having the highest salary might come to close this summer.

The most common contract in the teams of the Alliance was a three year contract. And, for the Golden Generation who had joined in the fourth season, most of their contracts would come to an end this summer after the ninth season. They were all at the peak of their forms as well, and then if you considered the growth Glory had gone through with the teams all flourishing, a new record for pro player income might appear this summer.

Under this circumstance, Team Happy dealt with their player's wage through board and food. This was extremely unscientific.

The reporters acutely sensed Chen Guo's awkwardness and they immediately keenly posed another question. This time, their target was no longer Ye Xiu. They focused on Tang Rou. She had already caught the attention of countless teams and was an extremely valuable player in the eyes of most.

"Ms. Tang Rou, may I ask, are you familiar with the current income situation of pro players?" The reporters asked.